<item>
<title>Out of Blue</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1098103196385\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hE8Gg6FUtZmERm4V1zUUP3a4wTX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Detective Mike Hoolihan is called to investigate the shooting of leading astrophysicist and black hole expert, Jennifer Rockwell, she is affected in ways she struggles to comprehend.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Pretty Little Liars: The Perfectionists</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1097218132705\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eRwTePABqHHYofflK6CFZ6ik3wl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of three college friends struggle with the stress of being overachievers in a seemingly perfect town, but in the aftermath of the town's first murder, each Perfectionist hides.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wave of Crimes</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1088218008289\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bfp0mNktF2FXkzMSpjqdTkeH5cf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A desperate housewife tries to cover up her son after he kills his father.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Finding Steve McQueen</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1087129062113\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uhmNHWTVniHHYKTsWSvSir19K1z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1972, a gang of close-knit thieves from Youngstown, Ohio attempt to steal $30 million in illegal contributions and blackmail money from President Richard Nixon's secret fund.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Triple Frontier</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1084471577313\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aBw8zYuAljVM1FeK5bZKITPH8ZD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five former Special Forces operatives reunite to plan a heist in a sparsely populated multi-border zone of South America. For the first time in their prestigious careers these unsung heroes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Big Shot</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1083334003425\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nNUFt1aZLjhWb6YKo30iIKqA8Ve.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A car fixer jumps off stairs after illegal demolition. Police officer tries to find the crime and catch the evil boss.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Among the Shadows</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1075516017377\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j3OBG9Td4jnXGn7m4LuNJtzskH8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A private investigator must unravel the murder of her uncle while keeping the secret that she is a descendant from a line of werewolves.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>L.A. Beat</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1074384997089\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ykDKHVMt0LQoxOojuwp6cSIJPn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While taping an episode of a popular police reality TV show,  L.A. Bea, a cop and a film crew are taken hostage by a vigilante hell-bent on revenge. Disguised as.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Leal, solo hay una forma de vivir</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1071973075681\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qRhycSTyRJX0VwAm10fNuzUc0iX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Former Colonel Fernandez is appointed Minister of the National Anti-Drug Agency (SENAD) and purges the special forces to fight the first of many battles against drug trafficking on the border.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Love Shot</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1069530090209\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ot08Kj6iGoE9THMn7qo1lkS83oL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A hitman in Koreatown meets a Karaoke hostess only to find out she is his next target.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Message Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1069530155745\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m7AxzI74tPt7S1oqVLANGebo7Ok.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A retired assassins past catches up with him and his brutality surfaces as he goes on a final killing spree to make things right.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Panic, With a Hint of Hysteria</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1864434387537\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4pZQT8i5ryc4YD0fJsh5Cad1LiS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A timid accountant tries to earn his living as a rather unsuccessful hitman, until an accidental killing of a mobster makes him a target for the vengeful mafia boss, murderous.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Purity of Vengeance</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1863710018129\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c8292MoL8qZ6f9uh0C3TMMuIhIT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A series of mysterious disappearances in 1987 are all eerily connected to the same person.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In Critical Condition</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1858810939985\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5cynjEASrZWg9rYdSf351zg7Htw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Johnny, the loyal number two of a powerful sociopathic crime boss, leads other members of a small town mob scrambling to keep their business alive while trying to find the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Purgatory Road</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1849367398993\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nFiVM93JAFHyHZFkrhsI2xaL52j.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the highways of Mississippi, a psychotic priest and his brother are on a crusade to absolve sinners with their own brand of murder.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>High Note</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1841055730257\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjAwNmI0YjktODA3OS00ZGIwLTkzZGQtZWM2YWQ4NTk3NGQ3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODI3MTc2NjI@._V1_UY268_CR5,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Best friends Cliff and Otis plan to get rich quick by stealing from some of the most dangerous foes in the business: drug dealers. Going against the plan, the two.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Project Gutenberg</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1838375635537\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hM7PkXjn4Xr4t8laIsW40NRZtZo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Hong Kong police are hunting a counterfeiting gang led by a mastermind code-named  Painter. In order to crack the true identity of him, the police recruits gang member Lee.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Everybody Knows</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1829328718417\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1TuuM451os3NaltCwGfPCVL2BST.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Laura, a Spanish woman living in Buenos Aires, returns to her hometown outside Madrid with her two children to attend her sister's wedding. However, the trip is upset by unexpected.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>West of Sunshine</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1827133917777\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rJKjVzLf5QnjVmqbRaHAiYEe226.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Separated from his family and caught in a cycle of gambling and debt, Jim has less than a day to repay a violent loan shark. His day is turned upside.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Menkoff Method</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1825090701905\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cCSdmjIVNazMQrDj5yB34CewK1r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this surreal workplace comedy, an Australian bank comes under the sway of the mysterious HR guru Max Menkoff and his revolutionary new 'method' that is guaranteed to increase productivity..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>City of Lies</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1819947108945\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pK7IYQdtdWtMDBJZfMqDxgMjXEt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Russell Poole and Jack Jackson investigate the murders of rappers Notorious B.I.G. and Tupac Shakur.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Marvel's The Punisher</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1818567051857\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/s2YM9zHF3tf2coi8t0UEzYrOHg8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A former Marine out to punish the criminals responsible for his family's murder finds himself ensnared in a military conspiracy. After the murder of his family, Marine veteran Frank Castle.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Girl in the Spider's Web: A New Dragon Tattoo Story</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1815174974033\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w4ibr8R702DCjwYniry1D1XwQXj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Young computer hacker Lisbeth Salander and journalist Mikael Blomkvist find themselves caught in a web of spies, cybercriminals and corrupt government officials.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Petal Pushers</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1813997292113\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM5NTY2MTUxNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTY0MTY3OTE@._V1_UY268_CR2,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Reminiscent of  Arsenic and Old Lace this kooky dark comedy has two sisters in the flower business facing off a suspicious step-father as a smitten detective discovers love doesn't mix.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Milk and Honey: The Movie</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1812753943121\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dWIT3tP362PWShZQerOesrRoHEK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Milk Hon£y is about Marcus King, an old school gangster, a crime lord, who has left behind old school crime. He has manoeuvred his business into the leafy lanes.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Come Up</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1809015835217\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9xQYN2XTzgyWKYj0HFb3I67muuT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Prequel the the successful 2016 film 'The Intent'</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nightmare Best Friend</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1784506747473\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjMwY2FiNjQtMTNmMS00ZDdhLWFmZDItZmM0NWRhNDIzZTU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTAwNDg0Njk@._V1_UY268_CR147,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At first Katy is happy to see her old friend Gina. At least until she realizes that Gina and her boyfriend are planning to rob Katy and willing to hold.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Lawyer</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1777857727057\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/581dC9mS15NXArdaguGzi9A80Tw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Frank Nordling is a young and exceptionally promising defense lawyer. When Frank learns the truth behind his parents' death, his whole world unravels. As children, Frank and his sister Sara.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ghostbox Cowboy</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1770483157585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4hNWnDkjNt8ZYKFG066hNrNAeR9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A dullard Texas entrepreneur reinvents himself as a cowboy in China's tech wild west, but finds himself at the mercy of corrupt American expats looking to reinvent him once more.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Saint George</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1770484140625\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hPrccfqOfB36XHpw3NTY8XMgWIK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An unemployed boxer turned collection agency employee deals with the deplorable methods they have to use when collecting bad debts.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Crimi Clowns 2.0: Uitschot</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1770484271697\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5rp9UlTFHCJZhdxDrpPxPnRkqpz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Tersago family isn't your average family business: clowns by day, thieves by night. They get arrested following a robbery homicide in a villa in Brasschaat, but let off for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mason Brothers</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762749909585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oPLXJtadwwukN5VOcp5sUeKwXKM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of outlaws attempt to reveal their brothers killer from a neighboring gang after being set up during a bank heist.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bitter Melon</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762186365521\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z2AMTiF6pkn4OSiLQJxfUQwRg7g.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bitter Melon is a  home for the holidays dark comedy where a Filipino-American family plots to kill an abusive member.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Black Ghost</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762187545169\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3UAJidWenKgKXSnGHT7QmKsdrrT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary> Black Ghost is a crime/thriller set in modern day Perth, Australia. Following the life of an ex-commando living in a city that is controlled by criminals; The Northside Crew, The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>White Boy Rick</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1754590612049\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/376lzYd3vE04qBA5Js93UAKrnvj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of teenager Richard Wershe Jr., who became an undercover informant for the FBI during the 1980s and was ultimately arrested for drug-trafficking and sentenced to life in prison.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Crossroads: One Two Jaga</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1750764358225\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pW40ks6djRubaRvx2g3ss2CJTzD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the outskirts and back-alleys of Kuala Lumpur, several individuals with money problems struggle to get their lives straight, finding their paths unexpectedly intersecting . with fatal results.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The World Is Yours</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1750240856657\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/b8l0pdMuVgqIYXBvNUr4TXdpmFj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A small-time dealer dreams of another life but can't afford it. To escape, he must accept one last job involving Spain, drugs, the Illuminati and his overbearing mother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Christmas Catch</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1749717224017\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7gRwH4w0gihgoDGAPJ5rcYFEZO0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Detective Mackenzie Bennett is hot on the trail of Carson, a suspected diamond thief, and goes undercover to catch him in the act. While undercover, Mack not only falls for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Under the Silver Lake</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1747019106897\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jDiPSt9oMcJbNzf8FZRtvU4rR98.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sam, intelligent but without purpose, finds a mysterious woman swimming in his apartment's pool one night. The next morning, she disappears. Sam sets off across LA to find her, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Pinch</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1743792441937\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9kcpXVrxZ8MDOQtiRdJGl2qemr9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Pinch (crime / thriller) . When a low level mobster is nearly rubbed out by the boss, he decides to take the bonus he was promised by force, so.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Strangeways Here We Come</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1743792245329\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/32Kt6IKrKy3qLjN30RC8GuGFvGZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A comedy in which the tenants of a high rise work together to defeat a cruel loan shark.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fight the Good Fight</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1741665077841\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nd1NoWe1xYkGLaFOl1UHc4MVALE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After his eldest son is murdered in a gangland hit, an absentee father desperately tries to protect what's left of the shattered family he abandoned.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Trouble with You</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1731876751953\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mr6Daq6iaiZp3bnWgZfPW8KB6MM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a town on the French Riviera, detective Yvonne is the young widow of police chief Santi, a local hero. When she realizes her husband was not exactly the model.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Broken Contract</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1730104986193\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aKkUiScmW4aEvSg6ypvzB0icJuw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Max, a down on his luck strip club owner, has his life and livelihood threatened by local gangsters, he turns to his wife's connections for help and hires a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Texas Cotton</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1728485984849\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kH1AiyoGcD8df2zoHDaANEkkJpW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An aging lawman is convinced a mysterious stranger arrested in his small town is innocent. His investigation stirs up a hornet's nest that will change the town forever.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deadly Signal</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1728010193489\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hNl7P53qm28lDwv10Uc1gB25lmP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a women's husband is brutally murdered and casterated, she enlists the help of a paranormal expert to analyze strange phone calls from his phone and her investigations lead her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Intensive Care</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1718649358929\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tGW3U7qJMMZ1NOeya1UrPM6vYt1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Three low-life criminals attempt to rob an elderly dying woman's home, but her live-in nurse turns out to be much more trouble than they bargained for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In Echo Park</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1718728264273\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTg5NGRiM2ItOGQ0MC00OTdhLWEwMmMtYzYzNGYwNTI2YWI4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQ2OTU2OTQ@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The lives of a street punk, a millennial couple, and a Salvadoran teenager being recruited by a local gang collide, forming an interlocking story of class and identity in Echo.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alcatraz Island</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1718648441425\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xRRKZab1vGwbzsW1sqwo44Nxwi7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of prisoners, led by an armed robber and a gangster, attempt to escape from the infamous Alcatraz Island.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Desperate Cowboys</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1718649031249\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTEyMWNiMjUtZTI2Ny00ODMzLTg1Y2QtMjg4YzVkNDVhYzAyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjI1NzIzNg@@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A terminally ill attorney, Burch, is in need of a hear transplant which he cannot afford. When an opportunity arises that could pay for the operation he calls on his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fly on the Wall</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1710648789585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qPtQPxj7xEfa5PpZxti05PCchO5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young man uses a bug camera to spy on his ex-girlfriend, then witnesses her abduction.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>100 Bullets</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1710648068689\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wXgAmWV8T7TziytLSndivpI140Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five years ago Frank Phoenix robbed The Firm. Betrayed by his own crew and murdered, the stolen gold was never found. Now someone is planning revenge.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fever (2014)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1710648527441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kAfUdsXeqrbj0T4Unu5mcwk6bkq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Damien and Pierre, two high school students, murder an unknown woman previously spotted on the street.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mr. Long</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1709255297617\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6xbuK3Y8zonLCuce89gbjXlRcdw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Taiwanese hit-man goes Japan to kill a man. But nothing turns out in the way he expected. He finds himself in a dumpster and with neighbors' helps he gets.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The White Orchid (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1708479220305\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/viTQS035XbUrBSxDxHQmZzbRPMT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A shy social worker must cross personal and professional boundaries in order to help solve a brutal murder in a small town.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Writers Retreat</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1705183218257\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qvRtjzsuHjNiXL95aFAi9T6YigR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At a writers' retreat on an isolated island, novelist Zandra joins a group of strangers confronting their darkest secrets. But when a member of the party mysteriously disappears, they realize.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Queen of Hollywood Blvd</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1694444423761\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wCrlBJweeRrbtUPu66nwRIzLy1m.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the eve of her 60th birthday, Mary, the proud owner of a Los Angeles strip club, finds herself in hot water over a twenty-five year old debt to the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Rookie</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1694444489297\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eh5fbHwK8GgBuib8vG8Ntok7ZAR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Starting over isn’t easy, especially for small-town guy John Nolan who, after a life-altering incident, is pursuing his dream of being an LAPD officer. As the force’s oldest rookie, he’s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sentence</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1686774942289\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7tZTCLQDnktQVZjHgWl6TAZorSu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cindy Shank, mother of three, is serving a 15-year sentence in federal prison for her tangential involvement with a Michigan drug ring years earlier. This intimate portrait of mandatory .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>22 Chaser</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1635149220433\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ufVCyUIfnoPgpKA578wADEDPTqc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>One of the city's last decent tow truck drivers risks everything on a desperate quest to become king of the road and provide for his struggling family.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Blizzard</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1607252380241\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/e0i69CQSgOZvLoXhaNCJSyrobob.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Liu Haiyang and Song Chao were best friends at Police Academy. After witnessing his trusted friend escape after the murder of his father, Liu Haiyang embarks on a quest for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ashes of Eden</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1606844353105\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6o7ke6fYZtgGZURYyn1mxjbIh9d.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>No man can serve two masters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Betrayed (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1602199620177\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTNkZWFhMjQtYjA1NS00ZDhlLTgyZjItMTNhNWI1ZmExNDY5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDg3NzEyMzY@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When the Cartel comes to Detroit and tries to push the Russian Mafia out things don't go as planned and more people end up dragged into the middle of things..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Above Ground (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1594643712593\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGJiYjAxNTgtMGI5NS00Y2ExLWI3YWQtNzFjMDdiNzAxZGUwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzcyODg2Ng@@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A divorcée's love for her ex-husband pulls her into a deadly crime ring when he goes missing, and the local authorities refuse to search for him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An American in Texas</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/789029325375\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gZvwcUzonxBKtWjBBpOZOfnyMWC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on a true story, and set in late 1990 against the backdrop of the first gulf war, An American in Texas is the story of lifelong friends as they.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>We Are Young. We Are Strong.</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1584470690385\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Etatd2baXtgvvW9uOUEAwy9ISj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On 24th August 1992 in the eastern German city of Rostock a rampaging mob, to the applause and cheering of more than 3,000 bystanders, besieged and set fire to a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Leakers</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1582045137489\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9UCdpI5wU2bMtcx5Z2c4HmQNiP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After mutated Zika epidemic happens in Malaysia, illegal hacker group 'The Leakers' network with Hong Kong police David tries to disclose pharmaceutical company AMANAH Malaysia's conspiracy and crimes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deadly vows (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1580015946321\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fY5lDqSVWigPCdZZcQ69fLqcZKa.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pastry chef Helena poisons men who don't meet her high standards. Her fiancé Charlie has nothing to worry about, at least until his sister Becca becomes suspicious of Helena's culinary.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Furthest Witness</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1580015815249\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmIyOGU2NDMtMWYyMi00MjA1LWI0ZWUtMzI1NGMzM2RiNmNkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjY1NTg0Njk@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Kyle Braddock has spent the last decade moving witnesses over the border to Mexico and has always avoided confrontation or suspicion until now. Not only has he been framed for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Girl in the Box</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1579757079121\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1GwGESCZ34kaulttLwSBRj7h1vY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>May 1977. 20-year-old Colleen Stan is hitching from Oregon to California to visit friends. With a little over 40 miles of her journey left, she accepts a lift from a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Delinquent (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1579756751441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1ANtdyxa9ralMe0CNg45LNFXeMW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A rebellious teen is sentenced to serve time on his uncle's organic farm, only to learn that there's much more to the farm than meets the eye.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Girl in the Box</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1579757079121\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1GwGESCZ34kaulttLwSBRj7h1vY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>May 1977. 20-year-old Colleen Stan is hitching from Oregon to California to visit friends. With a little over 40 miles of her journey left, she accepts a lift from a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Delinquent (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1579756751441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1ANtdyxa9ralMe0CNg45LNFXeMW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A rebellious teen is sentenced to serve time on his uncle's organic farm, only to learn that there's much more to the farm than meets the eye.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Danger One</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1577188592209\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ep2U0KpvNt4LNI9tEHKWroRLwyw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While transporting a dying man to the hospital, two paramedics find a million dollars in cash sewn into his clothing. When the man dies, they decide to keep it, setting.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Krays: Dead Man Walking</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1573406050897\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7fUGHX8O9bSSopkKeEwthuPq2qv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inspired by true events, the shocking story of London's most feared and notorious brothers Reggie and Ronnie Kray as they break Frank 'The Mad Axeman' Mitchell from Dartmoor Prison in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Loop (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1572081306193\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/v02WGwrG7QflHmCmQzST1tt25oZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A drug dealer and his girlfriend betray their boss on their last mission, and the lead gets stuck in a timeloop.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killer Son in Law</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1566472931921\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGFmMzg4NjktOGI0Mi00MTdiLTk5Y2YtNTY5M2ZhMzEzMDJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzM4MjM0Nzg@._V1_UY268_CR166,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Nicole is stunned when her daughter Cameron returns from a vacation in Mexico engaged to handsome Brent. But Brent has a secret girlfriend, Lexi, and together they're planning to kill.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Who Is My Husband</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1566292773457\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYmMwMDg2YWEtOTZlZi00ZTQxLWEyNTgtYjU3MzdkNjliNjhlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTYyNTgyMjc@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Sabrina suspects her husband Fletcher's possible infidelity with his numerous business trips to Paris, she discovers he has another wife and reveals illegal business dealings with his father-in-law, which.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Pitbull: Last Dog</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1560905124433\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eNfFE5psykzVr8IbdUQMa75P3In.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A policeman gets killed and the short-staffed police chief sends for a few experienced officers to support him in his fight with organized crime. Meanwhile, a conflict between local gangster.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Making a Killing</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/759856106047\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vDZPlVb41RFaeg9xtEobj2nQYHr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A special investigator (Michael Jai White) is assigned to a murder in a small southwestern town, but soon finds that underneath the surface is a foundation of lies and greed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Price</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/753549183551\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uSm4woSrLVErGNBZCCLOkBVjJjk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Seyi, a 24-year-old Nigerian-American, works on Wall Street. Desperate to succeed because of his outsider status-due to class and race-he commits a crime, insider trading, which brings his entire world.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>American Animals</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/751709391423\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aLbdKxgxuOPvs6CTlmzoOQ4Yg3j.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four young men mistake their lives for a movie and attempt one of the most audacious heists in U.S. history.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Skyscraper (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/748094097983\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5LYSsOPzuP13201qSzMjNxi8FxN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>FBI Hostage Rescue Team leader and U.S. war veteran Will Sawyer now assesses security for skyscrapers. On assignment in Hong Kong he finds the tallest, safest building in the world.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Barn (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/741619206719\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTk2NDhjNDUtMTQxMi00ZDY1LTk2MTAtZWIyMThkZDAwOGM4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDkwNTA3Njg@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A serial killer strikes Sugar Grove, Virginia. A rising journalist comes to town to cover the story : her investigation will soon lead her to the town's darkest secret, at.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Brij Mohan Amar Rahe</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/741263477311\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uaR0c0n3wXAZhKNfhuyb3ojkSk4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Brijmohan fakes his own death to escape his humdrum life. He gets the money and the girl until the inevitable hand of Karma gets him sentenced to death for his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Breaking In (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/733503359551\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bKH7H4f5LPBQ5KOmHPcYtxCo7Od.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman fights to protect her family during a home invasion at a house designed with impenetrable security.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stray Bullet</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/730822347327\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9EQjSc6pAih7QdBL4GT8CG4bQdM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A powerful and painful quest for justice after the death of 12-year-old Genesis Rincon, killed by a stray bullet in a gang shootout in Paterson, a poor New Jersey town.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beauty and the Dogs</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/729295817279\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ezh0cl1OxUINcXnT04z8cGUJiAG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During a student party, Mariam, a young Tunisian woman, meets the mysterious Youssef and leaves with him. A long night will begin, during which she'll have to fight for her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Vanished Family: Aurora Teagarden Mystery 4</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/724384221759\</link>
<thumbnail>https://s8.postimg.cc/w6hl2e3xh/ec_NXMTs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Aurora Teagarden is a beautiful young librarian with a passion for solving murders. After an exhaustive search for the perfect home, Aurora finally purchases her dream house, unaware of its.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kings (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/710640994879\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tA1mXJF75y57MvsZv2gDhbi0B4x.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A foster family in South Central a few weeks before the city erupts in violence following the verdict of the Rodney King trial in 1992.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sweet Country</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/707079375423\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h84IQ35u1na9nSuo5dHrzJhz9AI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Australian western set on the Northern Territory frontier in the 1920s, where justice itself is put on trial when an aged Aboriginal farmhand shoots a white man in self defense.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dark Harvest (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/704281250367\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mq5oAocgajiwW2OMe5JljHaHwQO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the eve of legalization, a marijuana grower is brutally murdered. His best friend, against the advice of his mentor (Cheech Marin, Up in Smoke (1978)), teams up with a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shades of Blue</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/703251483199\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AeBqFCOiX8orwIHbr6vzoFPAu17.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Detective Harlee Santos (Jennifer Lopez) is a single mother from New York City, New York. She joins the FBI's anti-corruption task force, whilst dealing with her own financial problems by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Billy Boy (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/698449660479\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m5brZceFpxortoInmpF51z4fHZo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When an angry teenager (Blake Jenner) discovers a close friend has been killed, grief jeopardizes his future and he finds himself engulfed in danger.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Billy Boy (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/698449660479\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m5brZceFpxortoInmpF51z4fHZo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When an angry teenager (Blake Jenner) discovers a close friend has been killed, grief jeopardizes his future and he finds himself engulfed in danger.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>7 Days in Entebbe</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/695019637311\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hKbZWIMyMThZ5rXrwlImXYpXMMo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four hijackers take over an airplane, take the passengers hostage, and force it to land in Entebbe, Uganda in 1976 in an effort to free of dozens of Palestinian fighters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killer Ending</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/689635592767\</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/RFQX8EJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Agatha Sayers best-selling novel becomes her worst nightmare when her daughter is abducted in a copycat scenario tangled with an obsessive assistant intent on stealing her identity. Emmanuelle Vaugier, Chelsea.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Red Army Hooligans</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/682717678143\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZWE2MDRjOGQtMTU4My00YWY3LWE1NGEtYTA3ZjI5OGUyODI2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzU5NzU5OQ@@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tony was the leader of a notorious London Hooligan firm, but whilst fighting a Russian ultra he sustains a head injury and must sit out some of the fun. The.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Violent Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/664054139455\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lcQyQe9B55k5F9nMNOMDtErZ8XM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A struggling mixed martial arts fighter finds himself in a fight for his life after his one night stand is found dead in her home.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wetlands (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/647817792063\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIwMTc0NDE3Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzcyNTMyMzI@._V1_UY268_CR1,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man attempts to make a new start in Atlantic City with the help of his daughter and a new business partner.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hooligan Escape The Russian Job</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/645811079743\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aroPZxFSOuI87fE0ztOF4Si5KKs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five British men have been arrested following some trouble with rival Russians. After being gassed and kidnapped, the group awake and realise they have been taken from their cells and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Things We've Seen</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/635953613375\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTVkMTU1ZGQtMmU5NS00MzcyLTg5ZDYtY2M3NWY4MThjN2FkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjkwODYxNDE@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Accusations of guilt turns a father into a fugitive, leaving his son to find and bring him home after struggling to put the pieces together.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Memoir of a Murderer</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/fpbwt9nVySE/\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/saLYJZlzilcDoi9YmwT0K0A9ql7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A former serial killer Byung-su gets diagnosed with Alzheimer’s and when a series of murders occur near his town, he worries whether the killings are his doings. Then, he comes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Outrage Coda</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/633036409407\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pAgXu3sjuqeJDoaHRfbZG3F5CcU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ôtomo gets involved with new Yakuza battles after he comes back the Yakuza society.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Seen in Idaho</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/629903919679\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDY4NzhjZDktNmI2Ni00NGVkLTg4MDctZTczNGJiZDdkNmZjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg0ODE1ODE@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman awakens from a coma after a car accident and begins having shocking visions of her future murder. It's a race against the clock as she tries to solve.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killing for Love</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/627802245695\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dE30flsJRAf4d2eFEAgEU7mvOYN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Derek and Nancy Haysom were brutally murdered in their house in Lynchburg, Virginia, on March 30, 1985. Suspicion fell on their daughter Elizabeth and her boyfriend Jens Söring. They flee.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In the Fade</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/NGJjf12F7hw/\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jYD4ajXIpBfk8YTPsNqvfm60jN0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set in the German-Turkish community in Hamburg, a woman takes revenge for her family in the aftermath of a bomb explosion.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Body of Sin</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/624513387071\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOWU1ZmIzMzItZTgyYy00YzhmLWI5NjQtODE4ZTA2NWE2MTJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDA1NDA2NTk@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two women use seduction to steal from straying men. But when they discover one of their victims hiding millions in diamonds, the score of their lives becomes a run for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Revelation Blue: Prisoner of Hope</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/623443118655\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGViMzJlY2YtMTI1Yi00YWFkLWI2NGItODA1ZDk4MDVkZTAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Often troubled by conflicting feelings on leaving the ministry and entering the hard edged life of being a homicide detective, Devon Blue now faces the conflicts of corruption while enforcing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>May God Forgive Us</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/361691613814\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4TfKiRHBEJvGTyuGO05OPcHm226.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Madrid, summer 2011. Economic crisis. 15-M movement and 1.5 million pilgrims waiting for the Pope’s arrival live side by side in a Madrid that’s hotter and more chaotic than ever..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dead Bullet</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620961073727\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lI9wj7cjoCauzPlU4xahJUveJ5p.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Desperate to turn his life around, a hard-luck gambler risks everything to sell stolen casino chips to a ruthless gunslinger. It's the worst bet of his life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dirty (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620959697471\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zmbKs6pRHWy2FjlCoDXCwSnpWdb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two dirty cops find themselves relieved of over two million dollars in stolen drugs and money, forcing them into a bizarre and mysterious investigation to recover it.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Ciambra</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620171168319\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bIkDmCWDIWyHAQgKCZpuD5d8kKl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pio Amato, a 14 year-old member of a small Romani community in Calabria, is in a hurry to grow up. Pio follows his older brother Cosimo everywhere and from him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dirty Dead Con Men</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/617884617279\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/76g7EZVU456aOv1s3kG3oE0Y661.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A cool and dangerous neo-noir crime film that revolves around the disturbed lives of two unlikely partners: Mickey Rady, a rogue undercover cop and Kook Packard, a smooth and charismatic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lowlife (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/616426441279\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jIcH1hh3WwItOu5FVEXoo6ouMB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The lives of an addict, a Luchador, a cartel organ smuggler, and an ex-con collide in this wildly original crime/drama/blacker-than-black comedy/thriller that’s as informed by Mexican subcultures as it is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 4th Company</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/616425916991\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/o3AfT6wxJRogy3NqUo0wUiY0hBg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Zambrano is a young criminal with the only hope of joining the legendary prison American football team known as The Dogs of Santa Martha. His hopes end up involving him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The King (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/615733201471\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7KRtopot0azhfRMZxfbK6sjKpC1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Born in a poor family, Tae-su learns that the power is the most important thing in life and decides to become a prosecutor, the biggest symbol of power in the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deep State</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/615486786111\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lkKL5yAw6aFoTZNWIluVnB8lSyO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>What happens when a man who believes he has retired from MI6 is called back to do one more job to regain his life, only to discover that this job.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Beautiful Ones</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/613364795967\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kjy1obH5Oy1IsjTViYVJDQufeZP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A retelling of Romeo and Juliet set within the Los Angeles underworld.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killing Joan</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/611791604287\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eIgxZqu4TzTq3dGJ5uaipZKu43s.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An enforcer for the mob enacts revenge on those who wronged her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Trouble Is My Business</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/611799730751\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4dw0z5Uh2NbabdGk2u6wdyJvMg7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Private eye Roland Drake cracks cases and romances femme fatales in 1940's Los Angeles while corrupt cop Det Barry Tate rules the city. A tale told in the classic style.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Lost Brother</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/610276805183\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rpLsI0JNJkJlCqwpNKXPMXpCAHw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cetarti is drowning in nothingness. With no job or purpose, he spends his days inside watching documentaries on television, until one day he is informed that his mother and brother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Commuter</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/610265074239\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rDeGK6FIUfVcXmuBdEORPAGPMNg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A businessman on his daily commute home gets unwittingly caught up in a criminal conspiracy that threatens not only his life but the lives of those around him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Ever Change</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/x1Y0BZfC8IE/\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lSQSoN1xCPgUVGlGPSc7YR8mEYt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The reunion of a woman and her estranged daughter is interrupted by a man with an unusual request.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Outsider (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/581160602175\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m2riQcEzjVrkP8wKHDXwC5EQpHQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An epic set in post-WWII Japan and centered on an American former G.I. who joins the yakuza.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Roman J. Israel, Esq.</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/492122671679\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8e5IGlLrVjwrlDcRtzSQkXhJFWl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>INNER CITY is a dramatic thriller set in the underbelly of the overburdened Los Angeles criminal court system. Denzel Washington stars as Roman Israel, a driven, idealistic defense attorney who,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bright (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/423496321599\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9WRLBBbdWyvMS1OtmXZnBQQ2BtV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In an alternate present-day where magical creatures live among us, two L.A. cops become embroiled in a prophesied turf battle. Set in a world where mystical creatures live side by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rise of the Footsoldier 3</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/385981549119\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDc2NjU2MDktNGJkOS00MmY5LWE1MjUtMDE2YTI0ZGRkYjQ3L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ3MDYyMDY@._V1_UY268_CR3,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Notorious gangster, Pat Tate, rises through the ranks of Essex's criminal underworld. A prequel to the Rise of the Footsoldier' franchise.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Moon</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/345150917183\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lvSa2tlvXCUvk4dtKk0oK6lgmrt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cold Moon takes place in tiny Babylon, Fla., where the granddaughter of Clark’s character is murdered by a mysterious assailant, her body sunk into the black waters of the Styx.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blow a Kiss</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/345146853951\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTA3NjBiNjktNmFhOS00NmUzLTg2ZGEtZjBmMmVmMmYxNGNkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman down on her luck stumbles into a bar run my a local meth dealer and finds herself accepting an offer that will change her life for the worse.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hounds of Love</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344013867583\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/b4niGo8hpxIpmAZsGkpZK4mXiDo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vicki Maloney is randomly abducted from a suburban street by a disturbed couple. As she observes the dynamic between her captors she quickly realises she must drive a wedge between.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Permanent (2014)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/342520433215\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc4MTg5NjA0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTIwNjY3NjE@._V1_UY268_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Six unrelated people must push through their past and the mob underworld to discover what has controlled each of them all these years. Sex, Drugs, Guns and God have created.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Diamond</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/93347318414\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nT9JFpsCEGSkJzu677iuiaEEqWj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Simon has just been released from prison and is on parole. His friend, Albert, lures him back to his old ways for one more hit. To steal the priceless diamond.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killer Assistant</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/93379365518\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tFEUy0VFYVujEvb0ZwtoWgkTxCs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A magazine editor's life and career, simultaneously begin to unravel, after she takes on a new assistant, with secret motives of his own.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stomping Ground (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/367408384654\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTZmYTQyNTYtOTgzNi00ZmE1LWJiYWMtN2VkNDM1ZmJkNzhhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDE3MTg4Ng@@._V1_UY268_CR87,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paths that should have parted years ago and the secrets which drive us apart.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blood Brother (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/346469304974\</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/STijEuQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Blood Brother takes place on the mean streets of a city in decay, where a recently released convict begins to take murderous revenge against his childhood friends, whom he believes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Way to Live</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/346467142286\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1h2RarsV9CBvCPz4Yw4l7S3RGR9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An interracial teenage couple in the 1950's American South, rob and steal to escape their oppressive town, but when violence erupts they are forced to confront their own dark secrets..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I'm a Killer (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344680434318\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gTahmz59BI4zx5cJKZe6sdXw1M1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jestem morderca Inspired by true events from the 1970s, the story revolves around a young detective who becomes the head of a police unit focused on catching a rampant serial.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Spoor (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344527669902\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3URcxp6EnCLVqapsyJynn7WizVc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pokot A story about Janina Duszejko, an elderly woman, who lives alone in the Klodzko Valley where a series of mysterious crimes are committed. Duszejko is convinced that she knows.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Catching the Black Widow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/338710694542\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w3YiWLnL18pn7ZIZ2Lwb6d4Nm7Z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The courageous story of a tenacious New Zealand woman who would stop at nothing in seeking justice for her brother's murder.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Persian Connection</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/337346300558\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pw2Q0CWkFEg0JbsDcUR7QnQjRpb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Loner After being wrongly accused of stealing from his former boss, an Iranian gangster with girl problems must hunt down stolen drugs in this neon-noir fever dream set in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bad Days</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/327247137398\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTYzYzJiMmUtNmJiMy00NWM1LTlmZjktNzYyODJiYTM2YTg0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzI5NzMxNDI@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Malos Días Emilia and her mother, Lucia, are forced into isolation after her stepfather, The Turk, steals a highly coveted cargo of emeralds. The unexpected arrival of two hired assassins.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Pickup (2015)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333449661070\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjU2NzU3NjI4MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTUwNzE2NjE@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While in the employ of Mr. Worthington, James, Mickey and Whitey have made several successful and uneventful pickups, but one last pickup will prove to be an adventure and the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Saint (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333451168398\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n8tsrPLem70exhXHfSausV7FlPx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>International master thief, Simon Templar, also known as The Saint, is asked by a desperate rich man to find his kidnapped daughter. However, in addition to evading the authorities, Simon.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>S.W.A.T. Under Siege</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333305547406\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sGcDltZ2aUgLV7oFxGlpO1oGmc0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A SWAT compound comes under fire from an international terrorist who relentlessly and violently pursues a mystery man who was apprehended by Seattle SWAT after a raid went horribly wrong.</summary>
</item>