<item>
<title>The Photographer of Mauthausen</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1088133532385\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1GzwDodNHSQM7Wu8VIbvTmYXJQB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on real events, Francesc Boix is a Spaniard inmate in the Austrian concentration camp of Mauthausen who tries to save the evidences of the horrors committed inside its walls.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Olavi Virta</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1082568084193\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fcp3pPWQPy5w6IeTzeWPyleMnUf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The life of Finnish singer-actor Olavi Virta.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>100 Years of the RAF</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1071177075425\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h4crriug8sVaTZitmV0mrpc0Lrb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For 100 years the Royal Air Force's courage, perseverance and innovation have secured freedom, survival and safety for the many , at home and abroad. Since its infancy, the RAF.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Maestro</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1860140534353\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3s9fCk37kQk2uPN9FaPwBZitwRh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After the Second World War, budding film composer Jerry Herst moves to Hollywood to study with infamous master teacher Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Isle (2019)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1841058286161\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r4XDWsBWMzpoNm5fUMjr9cyY5rI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1840 and another ship crashes on the rocks of an almost deserted island in Scotland. Three sailors survive the wreck and make it to shore where the few locals take.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Goyo: The Boy General</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1829296212561\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjBlMjEwY2ItMDFkZS00MmEwLThkYTYtMmU1ODFiZjUzZjY5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTI5NjIyMw@@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of Gregorio ,Goyo' del Pilar, one of the youngest Generals during the Philippine-American War who fought in the historic Battle of Tirad Pass.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Resistance at Tule Lake</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1827134310993\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fIaf5wmnxos4mQfFslih3k4bHol.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Resistance at Tule Lake tells the long-suppressed story of 12,000 Japanese Americans who dared to resist the U.S. government's program of mass incarceration during World War II. Branded as ,disloyals'.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ashes in the Snow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1809015966289\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wRMgle7vPFvSMq5R76JhsH54W4S.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1941, a 16 year-old aspiring artist and her family are deported to Siberia amidst Stalin's brutal dismantling of the Baltic region. One girl's passion for art and her never-ending.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Captain</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1807560346193\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l1otiFXq8h8q9vsiY8Dsh4kihxv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the last moments of World War II, a young German soldier fighting for survival finds a Nazi captain's uniform. Impersonating an officer, the man quickly takes on the monstrous.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Vice (2018)</title>
<link>https://vidbom.com/embed-xxlhqn2tfm2g.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/e0NZxqQ4B8YZ6kRrZish2DPqtdi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of Dick Cheney, an unassuming bureaucratic Washington insider, who quietly wielded immense power as Vice President to George W. Bush, reshaping the country and the globe in ways.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Get the Picture</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762186627665\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a8KJcTbr94Q3ue6JzgAnVWYIE1F.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Meet John G Morris, 95, a legend of photojournalism, whose unerring eye for the best shot has moved and changed the world. Morris, former Picture Editor of Life Magazine -.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Panic: The Untold Story of the 2008 Financial Crisis</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1757759146577\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vBNIwAPonhmIgYP4DfhFezMG2Ix.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary looks at the factors that led to the 2008 financial crisis and the efforts made by then Treasury Secretary Henry Paulson, Federal Reserve Bank of New York President.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dreaming of a Jewish Christmas</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1750455093841\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/o9EQQyK9zTXUWoZtJXQqxpDTcwg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The amazing story of a group of Jewish songwriters who wrote the soundtrack to Christmas.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Colette (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1746963925585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pGiUIkcTOEn2CwE5CUBFxWkcyxO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Colette is pushed by her husband to write novels under his name. Upon their success, she fights to make her talents known, challenging gender norms.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Laugh or Die</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1739828300369\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7L0QhTjs5dmOxbPUt5GCsrn0OF1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a detention camp in 1918, a group of Finnish actors are sentenced to death. When an important German general arrives, the camp's vicious commandant forges out a cruel plan:.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A War Over Reality</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1732704733777\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODE5MGYxNjQtNDYzOC00OGUwLTg3NzgtMTIyNWM0YTE5ZTcwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTc0ODg5NTQ@._V1_UY268_CR13,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For millennia mankind lived upon this planet without the need for electronic devices. No smart phones, tablets or gadgets running our homes. We knew about the cycles of nature and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gold (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1723528841809\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xCcdW6nHRcrKWraErYV5g3tut7Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set in 1948, the historic story of India's first Olympic medal post their independence.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death of a Nation</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1723528514129\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ayUSOpmiPZOARCklJdDnIWPa2QE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary draws parallels between the dramatic fracturing of the nation over Abraham Lincoln's presidency and the presidency of Donald Trump.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Robin Hood The Rebellion</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1716621085265\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t6zrohpaGgDPh2bcQ8y6ws7wyR2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>With his true love captured by the villainous Sheriff of Nottingham, the legendary Robin Hood and his crew of outlaws execute a daring rescue to save her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Prominent Patient</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1708564548177\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aR6RbvJYmP3Go8gZDEh9vHT9muO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A period in the life of diplomat and politician Jan Masaryk, who was the son of Czechoslovakia's founder, served as the country's minister of foreign affairs and is believed by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Love Between the Covers</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1687778822737\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jzLWXaUjiMQ6RvEoVxvXSF0zAZb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Love Between the Covers is a feature-length documentary film about the little-known, surprisingly powerful community of women who read and write romance novels. Romance fiction is a female-powered engine of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Chinese Widow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1683109120593\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g9nLgciMQ2iY02KjoIQ27r9eAhm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1940s, the Japanese attacked Pearl Harbor and this destroyed the Americans morale. The president of America, Franklin Roosevelt, decided to risk it all to bomb Tokyo raising more hope.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mademoiselle Paradis</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1681758227025\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xGMDmXLj6G3M5btGrLLVMgUDMKO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A blind pianist living in 18th-century Vienna forms an extraordinary relationship with the physician who is trying to restore her sight.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Operation Finale</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1602179762769\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nlIdPeH5IrR1qRErschnVQeZAQu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A team of secret agents set out to track down the Nazi officer who masterminded the Holocaust.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Scars of Nanking</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1590924479057\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjFhNzJkOWMtZDNhMC00NzUxLWJiZGYtNDRmZjk5ZGNkZWU1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTI0Nzg1OTY@._V1_UY268_CR147,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American missionaries struggle to save Chinese civilians from slaughter and rape at the hands of Japanese invaders and also smuggle out evidence of the infamous Nanking Massacre of 1937.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>We Are Young. We Are Strong.</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1590493383249\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Etatd2baXtgvvW9uOUEAwy9ISj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On 24th August 1992 in the eastern German city of Rostock a rampaging mob, to the applause and cheering of more than 3,000 bystanders, besieged and set fire to a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Summer of '67</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1579757013585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/layX7XFhJD24MN7vyVek34KfOvo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on real life events, Summer of '67 brings to life the turbulent times of the sixties and the struggles faced by the men and women impacted by the Vietnam.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Pagan King</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1569852688977\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h1dH8MmGfeTqbLh8ZoIZaq64bkg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On his deathbed, the reigning king bestows power to an unexpected heir who must find strength within himself to unite his people against the violent crusades which threaten their freedom.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Edgar Allan Poe: Buried Alive</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1567083268689\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bk7JuHfFj4aOd9ZnXwMmRQ6TalJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>How the inventor of the detective story became his own greatest mystery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Poverty Inc</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/761054300735\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzVlYmIyNmEtNTkwOS00YTM2LWI4NWYtMGJjNTliNjE4MWI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjQyOTUzNjA@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Poverty Inc., traces the history of capitalism, examines corporate globalization, exposes a failed economic system and focuses on America's descent into third world status driven by the new amoral predatory.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Princess and the Matchmaker</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pF-V0hcbtcs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ov3MQvtvT1lIaRcuZldJz8NUw5K.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Princess Songhwa refuses her fate of marrying someone who matches her marital harmony. There are 4 men on her future husband list with different fate signs. Refusing her fate, she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Servant or Slave</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/743238863423\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/autiNSrySRaK0R9eVNNsJT2l4VB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bringing to light the heartbreaking experiences of Rita Wright, Rita Wenberg, Violet West, Adelaide Wenberg and Valerie Linow, Servant or Slave is a film of courage, strength and the fortitude.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>This Is Congo</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/731015612991\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fnni4EGsD180uC3FgyhEprbXbIp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>THIS IS CONGO (working title) is an unblinking and unfiltered look into one of the world's longest standing, ongoing wars and those who are surviving within it. With over three.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bring Us Your Women</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/729077910079\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bOYyo9BhMPq8q7KnMuWnJAXaDL2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bring Us Your Women is an international anthology dedicated to women and the pursuit of divinity and freedom. The project seeks to tell existing and re-imagined stories of historic and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Queens - Cowboys: A Straight Year on the Gay Rodeo</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/729079351871\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Z5z17kcNKvmvHweryH7khcW1IL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>QUEENS - COWBOYS: A STRAIGHT YEAR ON THE GAY RODEO chronicles a complete season of the International Gay Rodeo Association. Roping and riding across north America for the past 30.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shock and Awe</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/725376502335\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mCEuPynAI11KaIi3E8GUyxCkU8s.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of journalists covering George Bush's planned invasion of Iraq in 2003 are skeptical of the presidents claim that Saddam Hussein has =weapons of mass destruction.,</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Woman Walks Ahead</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/713472739903\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qI5NcQHR0nsykPqlG2qnfFyMgW6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story follows Catherine Weldon (Jessica Chastain), who moved from Brooklyn to the Standing Rock Reservation in Dakota Territory to help Sioux chieftain Sitting Bull keep the land for his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>7 Days in Entebbe</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/695019637311\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hKbZWIMyMThZ5rXrwlImXYpXMMo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four hijackers take over an airplane, take the passengers hostage, and force it to land in Entebbe, Uganda in 1976 in an effort to free of dozens of Palestinian fighters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Lost Viking</title>
<link>https://oload.download/embed/wDDuixc5gNI/</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjJhZTIzMGYtNTBiMC00ZDVkLTkzOWEtMGY5ZmYyYzMyMjM2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA5Nzg5OTQ@._V1_UY268_CR3,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young Viking called Vitharr arrives in Britain with dreams of conquest and adventure, but when his family and clan are ambushed and killed, he must survive alone in this.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mad to Be Normal</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/680953645631\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g9j4FgzyPIoaGAWzC2qogmUvq6h.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of Scottish psychiatrist RD Laing and his unique community at Kingsley Hall, East London in the 1960s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Youth (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/694807759502\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/k6d6OOdAoQXrDKOMrDn6ZnSA0jk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Performing art troupe members each face their own trials and tribulations in Chengdu; from escaping a family scandal to dealing with unrequited love, each experiences rejection that shapes their lives.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Glossary of Broken Dreams</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/665273764415\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iDI7V7Djubtti5bJ08s3W4Reh6P.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Puppets! Pixels! Anime! Live action! Stock footage! Lumpennerd Johannes Grenzfurthner gives an ideotaining cinematic revue about important political concepts. Everyone is talking about freedom! Privacy! Identity! Resistance! The Market! The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>RAF at 100 with Ewan and Colin McGregor</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/664058137151\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7zbn93Qq8nf8W3ia5MQ8NQ680r1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>To celebrate the centenary of the Royal Air Force, Ewan and Colin McGregor take to the skies in some of the world's most iconic planes. These are the planes that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Things Left Behind</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/635125172799\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3sBlnQjW9cvc5ZPr1nYNcsthOk7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Things Left Behind explores the transformative power of ,Hiroshima,' the first major international art exhibit devoted to the atomic bomb. The exhibition, at the Museum of Anthropology in Vancouver, Canada,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Black Prince</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620973328959\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uFAOFgFO0jzpzNHS0Yqetwt5iz3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Black Prince, a historical drama, is being directed by Kaviraj. The film follows the story of the last Sikh Maharaja — the son of the powerful ruler Ranjit Singh.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rough Road Ahead</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/617978726975\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gfBjM50B4Kdp4Lw4gIpgqk2zCWd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Germany, 1967. Ruby & Martin, a young couple, are rehearsing their uprising. The price is high: expulsion from school, parental violence, and ultimately institutionalization. But they are ready to take.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hearts in Exile</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/G1JhVjsz36c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Two Sons of Francisco</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qRlGVXuUqYs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2vYfnWXxfgXfDe5OwoAUG8zUa9j.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of Francisco, a very simple and poor man whose dream was to see his children become country music stars, and who made all the efforts to make it.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>72 Heroes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/B-zAMlxaioE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2W4Wqp32ZUafIoQPPoJ3XW4YdqP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Remembering the Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/369603709582\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yXeLpNO3BbB02BJWHkcQKSTJ60s.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At an exclusive Catholic boys school in Melbourne 1976, Tim Conigrave and John Caleo fell madly in love. Their passionate, tempestuous, operatic romance lasted for 16 years, facing disapproval, temptation,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>American Weightlifting</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/366853425806\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc3MTY1ODk0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjYyMzczMDE@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ultra-independent , a one person production start to finish , this movie looks at the passion and dedication of American athletes and coaches in the Olympic sport of weightlifting. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Seventeen Moments of Spring</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wHgcJ5Fb_70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uctTqg7Q9graNOWUvffghOtmENw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A 1973 Soviet twelve-part television series, directed by Tatyana Lioznova and based on the novel of the same title by Yulian Semyonov. The series portrays the exploits of Maxim Isaev,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Secret River</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BDepKiFIt5A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hktitLCyDuHnZnMAvMYdRGpZBLy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>William Thornhill, an illiterate Thames bargeman and a man of quick temper but deep feelings, steals a load of timber and is transported to New South Wales in 1806. Like.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The First World War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OSN3EaJPhvU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r2Pg78Chdlx7EYtFnEFxFOVOKYN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1914, decades of building European resentments and rivalries finally exploded into a massive total war that became much larger and bloodier for far longer than anyone could have imagined..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>From the Earth to the Moon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_3CH_azOMh4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yECLq6UpcldfblPTd2OJmqMDOEC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The twelve episodes follow the Apollo space program from a variety of viewpoints: (1) =Can We Do This?, maps the origins of Apollo and its Mercury and Gemini roots; (2).</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Take Me Home</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/351355865742\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1dDcJTSeEPmOA7Dgby0fta2zKJz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary focusing on the wales national football team and their first Major Tournament since 1958 at the Euro's 2016 in France. going beyond expectations and reaching the Semi Final, Making.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eva Hesse (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/346724960910\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/myy9w0j7b91p0P1ml4OwJINypzv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>German American artist Eva Hesse (1936 – 1970) created her innovative art in latex and fiberglass in the whirling aesthetic vortex of 1960s New York. Her flowing forms were in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I'm a Killer (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344680434318\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gTahmz59BI4zx5cJKZe6sdXw1M1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jestem morderca Inspired by true events from the 1970s, the story revolves around a young detective who becomes the head of a police unit focused on catching a rampant serial.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mental: A History of the Madhouse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oswUssXzFlY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Telling the intriguing and poignant story of the closure of Britain's insane asylums.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>How the States Got Their Shapes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/F6p0YFJRfBs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Every shape on the map tells a story about our past. Why does Oklahoma have a panhandle? Because of shifting borders for slavery. Why does Missouri have a boot? Because.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Target for Today</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oqxYGVsiPHE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Ny8in3isHpmTvvf1OgSE9tX10X.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary about one bombing mission over Germany by the American Eighth Air Force, from the initial planning for the mission thru finsl completion of the mission, with all of its.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Barking Island</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y3vIEcTXIwU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/58gQOjwaXn9EuD6plQQ4iEb4IbI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Constantinople, 1910. Too many stray dogs in the streets. The newly installed government, influenced by an occidental model of society, calls in European specialists to get rid of the dogs,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Tread on Me</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/H4BDQde4XnI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>From the Tea Party Movement to State Legislators, the American people are drawing a line in the sand. On what side of it will you stand? Has the government our.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beating the Bomb</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b15INIVCs5Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>This is a film about the biggest weapons of mass destruction ever created. It is about the people who use them, more importantly it is about the people who fight.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Pompeii: Back from the Dead</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1DXfBUaaqco\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>As destruction rained on Pompeii, 74 men, women and children hid in a dark cellar. They clung to life as Vesuvius raged, only to become the last people to die.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Slavery by Another Name</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KPlk41mNDuM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nXPRuKygCSPazXz1b1zcCqN8Iep.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary that recounts the many ways in which American slavery persisted as a practice many decades after its supposed abolition.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Edward VIII's Murderous Mistress</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b34Q0D4l2vc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/x8jfofbzHVojQAkPRLpFAtvs5S7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The extraordinary story of Edward VIII's first love affair, involving a murder trial, a secret cache of vanished letters, and a cover-up to save the reputation of the future King.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Isaac Newton: The Last Magician</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dkuj_dQ_0lM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3BF3cHguOAqoU9rSBAyQgONmEA8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Newton's third law of motion</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Heist: Who Stole the American Dream?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jlhYk1Y4ftk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rUZiXixCo9Nx0o0apauesc4Ak2P.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Heist: Who Stole the American Dream? reveals how American corporations orchestrated the dismantling of middle-class prosperity through rampant deregulation, the outsourcing of jobs, and tax policies favoring businesses and the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Aswang Phenomenon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ePhqoyLpXQ#action=share\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iXsqM7g1nZOpfLUuxFD56OuPFCn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>What would happen if a country of 97 million people were taught at a young age that the boogie man was real. In the Philippines for the last 400 years,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Next Black</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XCsGLWrfE4Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>An exploration of the future of clothing, profiling forward-thinking companies who are at the forefront of redefining how and what we wear.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fidel Castro Tapes</title>
<link>https://www.thevideo.me/embed-0gsz1v3ch8t7-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sMwhNz46UqzzB9VXB10cBUwmkPQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>From PBS , In 1959, Fidel Castro rose to power in Cuba. He has been one of the most controversial figures in the world ever since. This is the story.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Viceroy's House</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/335608613518\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jDZLd4fgnpmtvNdGDE2c0asfkO9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1947, Lord Mountbatten assumes the post of last Viceroy, charged with handing India back to its people, living upstairs at the house which was the home of British rulers,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hostage to the Devil</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333448022670\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aFre2RqFH7AcUHqjergi9nmiVQM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A child possessed. An exorcist locked in combat with an ancient evil. In the battle for saving a soul, just who really is the ,Hostage to the Devil'?</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mary, Queen of Scots</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qlc4Ng5Koz0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9elxwBrLIsMNO8297Scu6Hlv47L.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mary Stuart, named Queen of Scotland when she was six days old, is the last Roman Catholic ruler of Scotland. Her cousin Elizabeth Tudor, Queen of England and her arch.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Islam: Empire of Faith</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yX3UHNhQ1Zk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6srXtZFOg85vST5vnJwIECu0BoU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Let Him Have It</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/f7kjmN2SFGo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kTrltrhJqn2Crl5E15KxjBxWkH5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1950s England, slow-witted Derek Bentley falls in with a group of petty criminals led by Chris Craig, a teenager with a fondness for American gangster films. Chris and Derek's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Attack in the Pacific</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/w5gi873N844\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>There are over 10,000 islands within the Pacific Ocean located between Asia and America, the vast majority of which possess little geopolitical importance in periods of peace , but during.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hitler's Search for the Holy Grail</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lfdOu3366Wc&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rs70W2CU73N35avWJeXy1WTUgxk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The worldwide Nazi search for archaeological and historical support for their beliefs in the Aryan (German) master race.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>911 Mysteries Part 1: Demolitions</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2O7LwySqtr4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bb0c97ooMKXhvPTpSvsCUXrlHVk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>911 Mysteries is a documentary that attempts to tell the people what really happened. It systematically deconstructs all of the propaganda you have heard about the twin towers, and replaces.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Winter War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7ELfMprEbrI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cdGgk9a8b6wctMoH11BMMBPwzuC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set during World War 2. After Nazi Germany invaded Poland in September 1939, Russia attacked Finland in November 1939. Finnish reservists leave their homes and go to war. The film.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I Wish I Knew</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eX6StN157IU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8O0KEMVoDcYHBKeKPmHBkrZJWPT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Focuses on the people, their stories and architecture spanning from the mid-1800s, when Shanghai was opened as a trading port, to the present day.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Journey to Mecca</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FXxFy-SkTmo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4DPI0BRt6oj7pwpMqmxJe6fNl2a.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>One of the greatest travelers in human history, 21 year old law student Ibn Battutah set out alone to Mecca from Tangiers in 1325 and returned to Morocco almost 30.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Orphans of the Storm</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wDSBEqabQdA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vcZKajKPL4Xtjzmov9tJY3IYhS6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Henriette and Louise, a foundling, are raised together as sisters. When Louise goes blind, Henriette swears to take care of her forever. They go to Paris to see if Louise's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Source: The Story of the Beats and the Beat Generation</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/k6JqjCB_7_I&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3C6B4u9QIQqmvtw3YHTcx2ubsXj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Traces the Beats from Allen Ginsberg and Jack Kerouac's meeting in 1944 at Columbia University to the deaths of Ginsberg and William S. Burroughs in 1997. Three actors provide dramatic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gandhi to Hitler</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/r1csUS0wLHk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5HU64iI1THSLSlIORXWG3Wr3Jwi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Chancellor Adolf Hitler assists Azad Hind Fauj, led by Subhas Chandra Bose, which include a group of Indians who are frustrated with the Gandhian manner of non-violence to compel the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Titanic's Final Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kdbnAyeUjt8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kEEkfS7o1Jw1RuimbMRXXlJpSYk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The documentary looks at the reasons behind the sinking and lack of rescue of the RMS Titanic, and sees Tim Matlin, author of several books about the Titanic travel to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Flame and the Arrow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dTXnQawQzOk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jyoHsEeKBIWmxrIurQ2G6hjKT6J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Twelfth-century Lombardy lies under the iron heel of German overlord Count Ulrich ,The Hawk', but in the mountains, guerillas yet resist. Five years before our story, Ulrich stole away the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bert - Dickie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5Dd9pbsQUxM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9jncDDDHkzmr0M7QVAJcEebW2mn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1948 a London beset by rationing and austerity measures has six weeks to go before the first Olympic Games after the war. With athletes having to supply their own.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>We of the Never Never</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jvXAalUrpRw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dywJwauC7Uu0AHLhIzk1TI1Vm9t.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jeannie Gunn faced being the only civilised woman in an uncivilised land. A story of personal triumph about one woman who reached out in a hard, hostile, prejudiced world and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Ungentlemanly Act</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8HgPba1iHas\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qR3cDshkYnyuafrzrV8cVJnBrhq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on actual accounts, this film portrays the days and hours before and during the invasion of the Falkland Islands by Argentina, which eventually lead to the Falklands War. As.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Perfect Human Diet</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-nltk1ftn9qd8-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1XnLEE2KM15UGtQUppa7ylarr3w.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Perfect Human Diet is the unprecedented global exploration for a solution to our epidemic of overweight, obesity and diet-related diseases , the #1 killer in America. This film, by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Maritime Silk Road</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-gaz5zndcqan7-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A young student of Shiraz university joins Captain Soleiman on a maritime journey to China in 11th BC.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Daniel Project</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-wq6z0iw0lxom-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Ancient documents are unlocked by scholars that reveal an astounding panorama of future events that will touch the lives of every living creature on planet earth , yet they claim.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Execution of Mary, Queen of Scots</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XgDG_wc19aU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/28eVQfY7IbAp4ufSBBr0kNURfI7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A short film depicting the execution of Mary, Queen of the Scots. Mary is brought to the execution block and made to kneel down with her neck over it. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Queen Christina</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/icS3e2IFxBk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/reF0KERj5TtCZMlbPni361Vbuj6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Queen Christina of Sweden is a dominant European ruler in the 17th century, and has never thought of romance. However, she accidentally and secretly falls in love with an emissary.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Scarlet Empress</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gY9ZYy6PXV4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xa4t3CU168cVaNYL2g2dRMtSMDH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Young Princess Sophia of Germany is taken to Russia to marry the half-wit Grand Duke Peter, son of the Empress. The domineering Empress hopes to improve the royal blood line..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last of the Mohicans</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/roVEH5QKEJA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xaZTxzuNf8dB1gJW0LDf6KuHgrk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the year 1756, Fort William Henry on Lake George is under siege by the French and Hurons under General Montcalm. Alice and Cora Munro, young daughters of the British.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Firefly</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ox26rL7UVpk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hapt4Ms3Qn8lkG9TGUVYBvRPmQt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Nina Maria Azara is the beautiful and alluring singing spy for Spain during the Napoleonic Wars. Her mission is to seduce French Officers, in order for them to reveal Napolean's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Oklahoma Kid</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ISPOZ39bBbM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vj0GpGEDjN2CLmJySuZEoqOBUQ9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>McCord's gang robs the stage carrying money to pay Indians for their land, and the notorious outlaw =The Oklahoma Kid, Jim Kincaid takes the money from McCord. McCord stakes a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Private Lives of Elizabeth and Essex</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BsiqwtO8b5g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/EBrjn7NdA9ZstiRpWZmY1kG72Y.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This period drama frames the tumultuous affair between Queen Elizabeth I and the man who would be King of England, Robert Devereux, the Earl of Essex. Ever the victor on.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Real Glory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jc_dxKE7sng\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/niy1RNZSnwI4EhWsgtN10wYMNCz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1906 the American army pulls out of Mindanao leaving a handful of officers to try and get the Philippines Constabulary into shape to protect the native population from ruthless.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Virginia City</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oqWMDmFx4lo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wpyQi9LWHvxHnZj6sDZuppP015.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the American Civil War, Captain Kerry Bradford escapes from a notorious confederate prison. He and two of his men are sent to Virginia City where Confederate sympathizers are prepared.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Abe Lincoln in Illinois</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/C0QbwOwFCiA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mYAkUJWaKuqzflBK5gk2eNRPAr3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Biopic of Abe Lincoln, 16th President of he United States, from his early days in backwoods Kentucky to his election as President. After a time running livestock to New Orleans,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>That Hamilton Woman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/evl7ldotkRI&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mWwIwq3WeCO8xmQfEyrSCkaVdJi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sir William Hamilton, a widower of mature years, is British ambassador to the Court of Naples. Emma who comes for a visit with her mother wouldn't cut the grade with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Measuring the World</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jy2nuPUdLCk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wnkE7gkXhyKDHkRtnQVLEaOAiVT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Germany in the early 19th century. =Die Vermessung der Welt, follows the two brilliant and eccentric scientists Alexander von Humboldt and Carl Friedrich Gauss on their life paths.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Substance: Albert Hofmann's LSD</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/688565258815\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w0gRFVOdMjnR1oVXCGZIIbAAjOC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1943, the year in which the first A-bomb was built, Albert Hofmann discovered LSD, a substance that was to become an A-bomb of the mind. Fractions of a milligram.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Orange Witness</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-xx1zcspf1dml-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hJ85uZA8v5V1HKzJfzLJS0AtkR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Orange Witness documents the marginalized voices of people who have been exposed to, and affected by Agent Orange. The film paints a bleak picture of the damage caused by the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Make Hummus Not War</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-v98orlb3vclv-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/x5FNwSPOsxCuUplHQk5h2ftpF56.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Filmmaker Trevor Graham is an Australian ,hummus tragic'. Every week in his Bondi Beach home he observes the hummus making ritual, mashing chickpeas, lemon juice, garlic and tahina. But when.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Henry V</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9tWLrmBu1vM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eAisr20DvaKJeHvjDN0oHSx0l7u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the inspired Olivier concept, Shakespeare's play begins as a performance in the Globe Theatre, shifting in broad cinematic terms to an epic narrative of Henry V, who had developed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Julius Caesar</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DcGenSlgwAM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oVxPED3bkDuJhYsqSzcp6JeCk62.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Brutus, Cassius, and other high-ranking Romans murder Caesar, because they believe his ambition will lead to tyranny. The people of Rome are on their side until Antony, Caesar's right-hand man,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Master of Ballantrae</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cNvm0-ngIyo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jQg88egLRqVIU7IKW41r9wxsq4b.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Buckle on your swashes for this swashbuckling adventure with a highlander who fought for Bonnie Prince Charlie who, after various escapades, becomes a pirate.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Young Bess</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/R34x4Yf2baI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7734ya3jx0ZBO4AjNNfn7D9K88G.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Chronicles the life of queen Elizabeth I, before she became the queen of England. Apart from taking part in the court intrigues, she is unhappily in love with admiral Thomas.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gate of Hell</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DAwhQRDSzBk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jAea0bSKrpV5aBjt6gAVhRoGfq5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1160, in the Heian Period, Lord Kiyomori travels with his court to another feud and his Castle Sanjo is invaded by two other lords, in a coup. The loyal.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Crucified Lovers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cXPXBbaFa8s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eMur2Zu72pSc3EDVeU8B3bsly8e.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 17th century Kyoto, Osan is married to Ishun, a wealthy miserly scroll-maker. When Osan is falsely accused of having an affair with the best worker, Mohei, the pair flee.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Warriors</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_jDZGDEf9j8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kzUHxNjDAlJaBwkj1wEUoePPuyU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the 14th century, the Hundred-Year War between France and England ends in a truce. The English army occupies French Aquitaine, but rebel French knights vow to continue the war.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Land of the Pharaohs</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i4SbkdM7dfk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4oUDFzkRwNrRyQGwWzlZLf64dly.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A captured architect designs an ingenious plan to ensure the impregnability of tomb of a self-absorbed Pharaoh, obsessed with the security of his next life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night and Fog</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5qGQTFJx-t0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2iWYQia8enOai7QEO3TvenleD7r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>One of the most vivid depictions of the horrors of Nazi Concentration Camps. Filmed in 1955 at several concentration camps in Poland, the film combines new color and black and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Helen of Troy</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Od6ftla5q-8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9ahx0eneGJTqoJCHPfIqB7YFyRi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Prince Paris of Troy, shipwrecked on a mission to the king of Sparta, meets and falls for Queen Helen before he knows who she is. Rudely received by the royal.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Johnny Tremain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/I1fsL7IoscI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fX6lTE9CaUD7xzSa0vfeF5tDtom.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In colonial Boston, a young silversmith's apprentice injures his hand, and finds himself befriended by the Sons of Liberty and caught up in events of the American Revolution.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The FBI Story</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jb81VfF-rp0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/q1sQSiMrfXnYkWPArUlKLXi9pO6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of the FBI unfolds through the eyes of one of its agents. During his career he investigates gangsters, swindlers, the klu klux klan, Nazi agents and cold war.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nefertite, regina del Nilo</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rOXlGJEh6hY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pFzQtSbEdeFpB9ktIrrx7L4MDpi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Chronicles the rise and fall of the woman who eventually became known as Queen Nefertiti.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Human Condition III: A Soldier's Prayer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZZLPybUl0B0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/svdKfhT9WLfrC8zgOWmZt4mgyK0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Part three of a trilogy. After the Japanese defeat to the Russians in the last episode, Kaji, the Japanese soldier and humanist protagonist, leads the last remaining men through Manchuria.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Colossus of Rhodes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0sz84kXJBec\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7eQo6dj8B89BS1xC25UvJICia8f.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Greek military hero named Darios visits his uncle in Rhodes in the year 280 BC. Rhodes has just finished constructing an enormous colossus of Apollo to guard its harbor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tom Jones</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rbH96NJ_VIQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7pn0MuzLX0tkBnNymdJtF52QQZV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In eighteenth-century England, =first cousins, Tom Jones and Master Blifil grew up together in privilege in the western countryside, but could not be more different in nature. Tom, the bastard.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Triumph Over Violence</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fw1G1jgK4aA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a7iuT5vxlVVe7P4AsniCLPs6AfZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary about the rise and fall of fascism and the effects of Nazism on German society.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Monterey Pop</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xNrygTqx0FA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/atn7VcxC6XlkH9ssms7VpcU4ta4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Legendary California music festival (pre-Woodstock) that launched the state-side careers of several performers, most notably Jimi Hendrix. Check out Mama Cass being absolutely blown away while watching Joplin sing. Here.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fellini's Satyricon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/m3LolS8d8wM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ut4IHS77neVrn4YGRcCZI08taDd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In first century Rome, two student friends, Encolpio and Ascilto, argue about ownership of the boy Gitone, divide their belongings and split up. The boy, allowed to choose who he.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Colonel Wolodyjowski</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0OZSTter5H4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c0YUZbBlGUrIFzeZVxtYb0V2MkH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1668 the Ottoman Empire decides to attack and invade the Polish-Lithuanian Commonwealth which is one of the few major European powers to still stand in the destructive path of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hidden Killers of the Victorian Home</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-xlzgszi01fow-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Start the Revolution Without Me</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/weuuQ9pMHwU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/abw7BKoi50gtDexKuGjDZ94cZH0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An account of the adventures of two sets of identical twins, badly scrambled at birth, on the eve of the French Revolution. One set is haughty and aristocratic, the other.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Confession</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0cM79wbjaZI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gr1AZRYZGVFMISxItlmqEZ2XJMV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Anton Ludvik, aka Gerard, is vice-minister of Foreign Affairs of Czechoslovakia. He realizes he is watched and followed. One day, he is arrested and put into jail, in solitary confinement..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Molly Maguires</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0_XZzA1-24k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AqRyswbmYImwT3UIlDR6w6LXSR2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Life is rough in the coal mines of 1876 Pennsylvania. A secret group of Irish immigrant miners, known as the Molly Maguires, fights against the cruelty of the mining company.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Emigrants</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7QfS0FlLQmE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qzRbryq6swsFgN3cKnmshjno2GO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the middle of the 19th century, Kristina and Karl-Oskar live in a small rural village in Smaaland (southern Sweden). They get married and try to make a living on.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Decameron</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/26oTFDutvn0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iWzX9MlNU6yzIWPMIcDagcdlsJw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An adaptation of nine stories from Bocaccio's =Decameron,: A young man from Perugia is swindled twice in Naples, but ends up rich; a man poses as a deaf-mute in a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sniper: Deadliest Missions</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-grf81khg7aoe-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/EXqMjQ5iQlfZy4XKGMa08LEPmX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>He's the deadliest weapon on the battlefield, but his next shot could be his last. Outnumbered , Outgunned , Behind enemy lines , What happens when the tables are turned.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Edgar Allan Poe: Love, Death, and Women</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-zzd32y9bcnnm-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/b9Qgd4cvVbdFIC2fe5jkOJveEM2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Our Generation</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-tqq3inyz3vzk-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary on the Australian Aboriginal struggle for their land, culture and freedom , a story that has been silenced by the Government and mainstream media. Featuring the stories of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Winter Soldier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3262\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bOeXRPH0NjwSrad98fJYNAHhQWo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For three days in 1971, former US soldiers who were in Vietnam testify in Detroit about their war experiences. Nearly 30 speak, describing atrocities personally committed or witnessed, telling of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Enigma of Kaspar Hauser</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tzxreLUzuUI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jkbnlcex3xfndksKuwVeI0EmuhW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Herzog's film is based upon the true and mysterious story of Kaspar Hauser, a young man who suddenly appeared in Nuremberg in 1828, barely able to talk or walk, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Kung Fu Invaders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fAaL3piw9xc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/34QBuJb850FwAHuK1G97lCZoi4T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hung escapes Shaolin after the temple is attacked by the Ching, only to be jailed with the help of Fang (also of Shoalin) who mistakes him for a bandit. Fang.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sandakan 8</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8h5yqpAVH24\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/csT18jpVGhRpX8ujTFLOZpa240i.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A journalist interviews an old woman who was forced into prostitution, just like many other Japanese women working in Asia outside of Japan during the first half of the 20th.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fire in the Night</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-1x9qij2smis6-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3pz18DvIT6MALNfNgyzCGrkc1CP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Fire in the Night relives the tragic events that occurred on the Piper Alpha rig on 6th July 1988. It was a catastrophe that killed 167 men and left only.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>High Tech, Low Life</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-k2sisj6pnkrf-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/liWd80lGl2QgG8H8qBEae0wo8Uq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inspired by a search for truth and the potential for fame, a young vegetable-seller from Hunan province challenges the boundaries of free speech by reporting on censored news stories in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hue: A Matter of Colour</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-hbfglzbbgmnu-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cDp1tcBhY6TUpbfLsQLGlw7Etmm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hue, by renowned director and cinematographer Vic Sarin, is a personal, heartfelt investigation into the history and often tragic effects of colourism, the phenomenon whereby people within the same ethnic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Goltzius and the Pelican Company</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-b7t8jj8xog0f-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/k2IndZpTsLeoUAeYc9CxYKvItxi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hendrik Goltzius, a late sixteenth-century Dutch printer and engraver of erotic prints, seduces the Margrave of Alsace into paying for a printing press to make and publish illustrated books.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hoe duur was de suiker</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-d547m0ch0ihy-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ylAWvQ9T068GcgFJYKONP96poK4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Price Of Sugar tells the alternately gripping, romantic and heart-wrenching story of Sarith and Mini-Mini as they grow up on the sugar plantations of Suriname in the latter half.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tula: The Revolt</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-zanw9fe29q1y-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zeOcrTj5FYdZsNKqzwup2lF1ibz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Tula, The Revolt' is an international English spoken feature length movie about the leader of the big slave uprising on the island of Curacao, a Dutch colony in 1795. ,Tula.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Capturing Oswald</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-d0eg89ui7wcb-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>All This and World War II</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nx_Wa-hpbjI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w0JrPLsHFmCmj2rFifQb188lzRN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Beatles' =significance, pushed to the breaking point in this bizarre documentary that juxtaposes their songs (sung by a number of rock stars) with World War II newsreel footage. Helen Reddy.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Marquise of O</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FWqacYqZBGk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AmXPUCdQKWmO13B3WuUcy1OZZgg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the attack on an Italian town by Russian forces, the Marquise of O., the daughter of the colonel in charge of the defence, is attacked by a group of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tree of Wooden Clogs</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/v6LAOc3M6b0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oRxVdHuWjlHJZwZI1nI2HXGRyUG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The life inside a farm in Italy at the beginning of the century. Many poor country families live there, and the owner pays them by their productivity. One of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Shooting Party</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MobGaRVgQIU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3MFXKInc45j06nFxMBVcJptdQrP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>You can't make a heart love somebody. This gospel is well known to the young Olenka. Born in a poor family, she has to marry a rich man to escape.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Partizanska eskadrila</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9cNPq_RM2ps\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kP2kDveJ4NDsnaiBeln6LpMfrII.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An epic film of all time. It is one of the greatest spectacle that was filmed in Yugoslavia in the 20th century. In the spring of 1942, the German air.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sea Wolves</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BTUkODzl4DI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4wv3LpQ14SDnKpFIxMZHn1MWqKv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In March 1943, in the World War II, the Germans use the neutral harbor of the Portuguese colony of Mormugoa to transmit information to a U-Boat about the allied ships.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bushido Blade</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QPPeWuWcWkk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bWtCZgz67W3SIdB5abykE6gvIrS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A steel samurai blade that was to be given to the American ambassador by the Emperor of Japan is stolen. American sailors and Japanese samurai are sent to find it.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Man of Iron</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/B7GU98L4Ml0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sBE5uTURQ7m0CtidhjaSdSz2POQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A worker becomes a =man of iron, forged by experience, a son comes to terms with his father, a couple fall in love, a reporter searches for courage, and a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Another Way</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TzES5Bc0PvI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w69UnM83Mf4MEqYtFOTwJnNHZX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Political and sexual repression in Hungary, just after the revolution of 1956. In 1958, the body of Eva Szalanczky, a political journalist, is discovered near the border. Her friend Livia.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Woman Called Golda</title>
<link>https://www.thevideo.me/embed-f9zvxab2g87z-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/moqt2fwhvP5IATvU8jkdyNkH4zh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of the Russian-born, Wisconsin-raised woman who rose to become Israel's prime minister in the late 1960s and early 1970s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Times of Harvey Milk</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jet-Ubwk5l8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6vAAcRmJiUmcmufSk8bn2zVbZJs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>2 Members of the San Francisco Board of Supervisors Harvey Milk - San Francisco Mayor, ,George Moscone (I)' were assassinated by recently resigned Supervisor Dan White on Monday, November 27th,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Before Stonewall</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/atrlRznk4Z4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zqsaSd1wdWjQu7Viy5UBD6P8Ki0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>New York City's Stonewall Inn is regarded by many as the site of gay and lesbian liberation since it was at this bar that drag queens fought back against police.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Black Arrow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/boOfv0g8G6c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AlXvlEct5pCLNCCrh2VvaQ9k67b.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In England, during the 15th century, many lords and noblemen vie for the throne.Among the contenders, two of the most powerful nobles fight a bitter war among one another.Sir Daniel.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Undergångens arkitektur</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7MRsq_iApng\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zwGBLAwjtld90DXh1hE4sKnp4PV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An absorbing and chilling documentary about the National Socialist aesthetic, and how attempts to create the Aryan Ideal caused the extermination of millions. Aspects covered include: .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Comic Book Confidential</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z5ZvKnLNZpg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1hMe2nNxk0uKfu9E1PNJzUmUwn1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the 20th century, no artistic medium in North America with so much potential for creative expression has had a more turbulent history plagued with less respect than comic books..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lenin: The Train</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bGYRa-rTtzw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ztgfofQAnSvrEnyVhgfBhLzmlb5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>March 1917. The first world war is already a couple year to pace. A sealed train with Russian emigrants keeps on driving from Germany and Sweden to Saint-Petersburg. The outlaws.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Edward II</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zCmT99luGRE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/seUbeTeMzw9atOr7wwyRMhT5vwb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this Derek Jarman version of Christopher Marlowe's Elizabethan drama, in modern costumes and settings, Plantagenet king Edward II hands the power-craving nobility the perfect excuse by taking as lover.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Baby of Mâcon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yU5IjY32rhg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zVi0nVoVWiOcF4YwbFwGiju6ajK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A movie about the corruption in all levels of society. A baby is born from a supposed-to-be virgin woman, so a chain of hysteria about divine intervention in the birth.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Wonderful, Horrible Life of Leni Riefenstahl</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/91607Aqn-mo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lTiL9emewC7DLS9A9O5aZf7Ywum.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary recounts the life and work of one of most famous, and yet reviled, German film directors in history, Leni Riefenstahl. The film recounts the rise of her career.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Race to Freedom: The Underground Railroad</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-6Hg-aiZHBI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2pV4Y6ihUJy2Ykzn9MXp3KgpOPd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In pre Civil War America, slaves are prepared to risk everything for the chance of freedom from bondage. This films relates the story of a group of slaves who decide.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Some Mother's Son</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6Xfw_2FAm5I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rdORRGJMGfYFuZWhuvrai8TyogE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on the true story of the 1981 hunger strike in a British prison, in which IRA prisoner Bobby Sands led a protest against the treatment of IRA prisoners as.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Arrow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1NLfEnfKBmw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ifUbKmM2gPnoSkvQUxz8j5LiTwj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This series tells the story of the world's fastest fighter plane ever built, in 1950's Canada, and how the project was dropped due to political pressure from the United States.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Waco: The Rules of Engagement</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HQT-0umIo6Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eKHB7yftbvdY3OYd5QvZCHvEJcF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This controversial documentary about the stand-off between an unorthodox Christian group , the Branch Davidians, under the leadership of the young, charismatic David Koresh , and the FBI and ATF.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Riding the Rails</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOjQFyvqGTg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2VVkrLPTaqJ0aa2A93T0N9M4fIr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Riding the Rails offers a visionary perspective on the presumed romanticism of the road and cautionary legacy of the Great Depression. From ,middle class gentility to scrabble-ass poor,' the undiscriminating.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Barber of Siberia</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GzeuxbthFg8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xganmHk2g5PnzENlkGvg7brbbbM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Douglas is a foreign entrepreneur, who ventures to Russia in 1885 with dreams of selling a new, experimental steam-driven timber harvester in the wilds of Siberia. Jane is his assistant,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nukes in Space</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dIslrlzawzQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6e80GMw4IJgbAdlWkcdFvnpk6hq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>U.S. nuclear tests in space, and the development of the military intercontinental ballistic missile (ICBM).</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hunley</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QQXcP2tESdk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hk1OkofmgYMdu6x5veMTyzdj0zH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>CSS Hunley tells the incredible true story of the crew of the manually propelled submarine CSS Hunley, during the siege of Charleston of 1864. It is a story of heroism.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sophie's World</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/j5rJVaktAVo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vhjkECS4foeUBitYdtmGf9aJCOn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sofie is an ordinary Norwegian girl. One day she recieves a video tape on which a certain Alberto Knox talks directly to her from ancient Greece. They then start to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Paragraph 175</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i4SfaW708xY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jpWAael8IHvFJe50WZ1dTOY1kip.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>By the 1920's, Berlin had become known as a homosexual eden, where gay men and lesbians lived relatively open lives amidst an exciting subculture of artists and intellectuals. With the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Into the Arms of Strangers: Stories of the Kindertransport</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/J6asjV9r41s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r439Z4Yp6HQe0nsVITUfc2H8OPA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For nine months prior to World War II, in an act of mercy unequalled anywhere else before the war, Britain conducted an extraordinary rescue mission, opening its doors to over.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Barkley Marathons: The Race That Eats Its Young</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fuaGY6qA-RY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a8d1qMy4Vp3VkAxGR3SHsNsb6Bc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In its first 25 years only 10 people have finished The Barkley Marathons. Based on a historic prison escape, this cult like race tempts people from around the world to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Victoria - Albert</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MjHU_Mas4z0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Q4PRt9E27Ar3HiJ70CdR9KVjPK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The passionate love story that was Queen Victoria and Prince Albert's lengthy marriage. Beginning in 1837, the year of King William IV's death and 18-year-old Victoria's ascension to the .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Good War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ilh0xXI2JQA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5LFxc5p4JMXGOdBacZjGECbhl4u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on a true story its the untold story of Italian World War II POW,S in Jan 1946. Luca Zingaretti stars as one of over 50,000 Italian Prisoners of War.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bible Code</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/U-HVlpnPEfI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Good Morning, Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2C0VdCSeDOM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/o5pe9nAodf8IbbzXnefrY1VJyxq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The movie is based on a true story. On 16 March 1978 Aldo Moro, the former Italian Prime Minister was kidnapped in Via Fani by the Brigate Rosse (Red Brigades),.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>First Invasion: The War of 1812</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/c7Hh8W69cos\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5o9dlQQ1lP3yX2dUStosbf100Jc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tying the Knot</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zjgucqbUYsQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bYXhNd32YfNoI9GLmlQtfNN6P5T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A look at the debate over same sex marriage in the USA. The reasons behind it are illustrated with real life couples that have run afoul of current laws despite.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Operation Valkyrie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sNvReY8clSU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/baQ235XeFZbIBXvinXR5VrNTRtb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1944, in fear of a complete German defeat in the World War II, a group of high command officers plot an attempt against Hitler, and one of the leaders.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Lion in Winter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WH8TrFQn5QY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pfAqFEZVa1KmXX5M5PdcKGJTr0k.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>King Henry II (Patrick Stewart) keeps his wife, Eleanor (Glenn Close) locked away in the towers because of her frequent attempts to overthrow him. With Eleanor out of the way.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sharpe's Battle</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-buan19w6ldld-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/szYRDjfUtNSPdxQUYSu1wztilUU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Sharpe is ordered to whip the King of Spain's Irish Royal Brigade into shape, he faces dissent from the men who believe the British are slaughtering their relatives in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Roswell Incident</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/LgbLK2epJe8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary made on the alleged crash of an alien spacecraft in Roswell, New Mexico in 1947, after the now infamous footage of an autopsy of an alien was published.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>EXPO: Magic of the White City</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UjVdhhfMwVo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tDZQAYz6OcCE9voglSwmaVDdHAs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Narrated by Gene Wilder (=Young Frankenstein,, =Blazing Saddles, and =Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory,), =EXPO , Magic of the White City, brings the Chicago World's Fair to life. Experience.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The King and the Clown</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fix5tXcy3Hc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/49FHitJrLWADPXi1ofeIkrk7rny.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Soul mate minstrels Jang-sang and Gong-gil eke out a living in 14th century Korea through bawdy stories presented in a tightrope act; however, sexual interests of the rich over Gong-gil's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>9th Company</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TcHD9VEQ7C8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8LqqdxD0Ol7PslyRyP6sCqoIxqm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film is based on a true story of the 9th company during the Soviet invasion in Afghanistan in the 1980's. Young Soviet Army recruits are sent from a boot.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>One Hundred and One Nights</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NB0ZYARj7zQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/i2gWZwbXuKoS1dq8guuOgfJV5Ys.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Monsieur Cinema, a hundred years old, lives alone in a large villa. His memories fade away, so he engages a young woman to tell him stories about all the movies.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Goebbels Experiment</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eCbbr3YZVqc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/syZoWk2b6rAMAYLQ8oak0OwmsKj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Nazi propaganda mastermind behind Hitler speaks in first person as actor Kenneth Branagh reads pages of the diary kept by the chief of propaganda, Joseph Goebbels, revealing the man's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Siege at Ruby Ridge</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IrNGkDlbdF4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7TwYVCADYjbcCbUCxI7ygQ6f6V1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A mini-series dramatization of the controversial 1992 attack by federal agents on the Idaho home of Randy Weaver, a white seperatist. The ten-day siege, begun over a minor gun charge,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man Who Captured Eichmann</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XEH06oFfJSY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h5A2qbauzn4LP5ND63cjWkNdQ8Z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1960, the Israeli Secret Service learns that former SS-Lietuenant Colonel Adolf Eichmann, who was one of the key figures in the Jewish holocaust of World War II, is living.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yv6aU-_9xQ0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/y92NEfzeDJYlyXjn4TnPWIqK72G.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A portrait of the one of our greatest social reformer of our times , Ambedkar. The film documents the period between 1901 and 1956. The film delves more into Ambedkar's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Romanovs: An Imperial Family</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fKd-Di88Uxk&feature=channel\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vuMQqrnb3XtJoavfIABSoWb2jTd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of the last year and a half of Tsar Nicholas II and his family from the February Revolution of 1917 to their execution in July 1918.</summary>
</item>
<title>The Dish</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/1NRV1IqSdz8/The.Dish.2000.mp4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zG83o1wpU3p7QTd382K4HtctLq0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the days before the July 19, 1969 space mission that marked humankind's first steps on the moon, NASA was working with a group of Australian technicians who had agreed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sharpe's Waterloo</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-ox3mtpan5zmk-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xx7h4BYzIbs8JLu0c4LCV1tXupI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on the novel by Bernard Cornwell, =Sharpe's Waterloo, brings maverick British officer Lt. Col. Richard Sharpe to his last fight against the French, in June of 1815. Sharpe is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hitler's Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ih5GGKQUd6E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pT4N0LJc6SQOfQ6NjgqaoQhsxzf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>London, Spring 1941. Columns of Wehrmacht soldiers make their way along the Mall, swastikas hang from Buckingham Palace and Junkers scream low overhead-a potent symbol of Nazi victory. The Germans.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deep Water</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tC007qozN-g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oSOMJMDOef9AuviQCzc3S1iTAji.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary about the disastrous 1968 round-the-world yacht race.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>José Rizal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6PoMrRb_ocQ&feature=PlayList&p=DA02E6046ECBB8E1&playnext_from=PL&index=0&playnext=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qkJq8EbHk0Wz7FEKU3w5fC44t6K.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jose Rizal's life and works are recounted through a series of non-linear flashbacks which reflect on various aspects of his life , as writer, propagandist, lover, friend, brother, doctor, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Rape of Europa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tK55VI23uXs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8fzUE7GieCSwBvJFZdFQElLJGx7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>THE RAPE OF EUROPA takes the audience on a journey through seven countries telling a story of greed and warfare that threatened the artistic heritage of Europe. For twelve years,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rang De Basanti</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/l-BTOTtcGmk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bAzCzOpJ6lkDDjmhnxsLbIloH9P.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young idealistic English filmmaker, Sue, arrives in India to make a film on Indian revolutionaries Bhagat Singh, Chandrashekhar Azad and their contemporaries and their fight for freedom from the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Terror's Advocate</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MAqhvkUr-8g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8ltDi3cp9Y2cBCpHt5v5IKFsJ7I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An examination of the career of Jacques Vergès (1925- ), attorney for members of Algeria's FLN, Palestine's FPLP, the Khmer Rouge, Carlos and associates, Klaus Barbie, and other revolutionaries and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Muoi: The Legend of a Portrait</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Oq_0b6E2L9E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tUzvclJrG2BUeqoc0wjmtfOFp3V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>=Muoi, charts the path of a Korean writer who travels to Vietnam in search of stories for her second novel. There she learns about a mystery centered around a century-old.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>With Fire and Sword</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qn5jrtdLOZ0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7MyTGmHSNRDZN8hUKqZ0ZeaGqml.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1648 a Cossack rebellion in the Ukraine threatens the sovereignty of the Polish-Lithuanian Commonwealth over the Cossack nation. The Cossack rebellion also known as the Khmelnytsky Uprising is pitting.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Star of Bethlehem</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0mWELJ08-9g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dIvRw9PXkfobuSyRs6wgCnxQJyb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>=We saw His star in the east and we have come to worship Him, (Matthew 2:2) The biblical report in the Gospel of Matthew tells a story of wise men.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Heartbeat Detector</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6Tk0lIRC6r8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xAjb0Bx21THVQm0Nn9ts5eQT9cO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paris today. Simon works as psychologist in human resources department of petrochemical corporation. When Management gets him to investigate one of the factory's executives, Simon'perception goes disturbingly chaotic and cloudy..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Super Monkey</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZJ1Tl5ucar4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lT9UDXetFLTRRqy0Y2n48URfQl2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the way to India to get some holy scrolls, priest Tripitaka and his followers are led by Monkey and implored by a princess to protect her people from a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sovereign's Servant</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Bo20Dt8nwD4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/594sYVzkkql87E4BoFmZCODOWvW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Europe, 1709. Russia and Sweden are at war. Two French duelists are exiled by King Louis XIV of France: one to the side of Czar Peter the Great of Russia,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>H.H. Holmes: America's First Serial Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/y5HRa9nEVVU&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1bapLOzH5JRFsgjumzRV1GkqS8t.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Depicts the entire life of Herman Mudgett, AKA Holmes, and his castle of horrors. Also known as the torture doctor, Holmes designed his own building, complete with torture chambers, where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Evil Twin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vcHEHRDegp8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3oOADU7Ll0JygYbFSvEPAGH2ljc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>(Korean with English subtitles) So-yeon awakens from a 10 year coma, with no memory of the tragic drowning of her sister. As ominous events and deaths accumulate, So-yeon begins to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Time of the Comet</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kmQaxJGQ4fs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fKfPsuMKzOqZeuYUt1tfLrwlrSV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young man is searching for the war to free his country and establish freedom. Instead of war he finds the love of his life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Downfall of Berlin: Anonyma</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xEZxcSf9HwM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c1ILatDxfakmEYJmtdU7AW8V6ED.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A nameless woman keeps a diary as the Russians invade Berlin in the spring of 1945. She is in her early 30s, a patriotic journalist with international credentials; her husband,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Brothers Warner</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NzAzK02Hb8A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zHWvP9jvXP08Ywni0WzDMVrsns8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Intimate portraits of brothers Albert Warner, Harry M. Warner, Jack L. Warner, and Sam Warner, the siblings who were close knit at the time of Warner Bros. Studios founding, but.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 2nd Assassination of JFK</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nUL6d73mVt4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>,The film focuses on the historical and future significance of American manned space flight and the importance of the United States remaining on the forefront of space discovery. ,The 2nd.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Winter in Wartime</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YrtnYwQXr6Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5U48dtSLUTRwg1he8Ggbl67N8wI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Near the end of World War II, 14-year-old Michiel becomes involved with the Resistance after coming to the aid of a wounded British soldier. With the conflict coming to an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Burma VJ: Reporting from a Closed Country</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/V08EBWQLzyU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lGEHFtj4YPBdKWVuScL55JDPZqP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Using smuggled footage, this documentary tells the story of the 2007 protests in Burma by thousands of monks.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Founding of a Republic</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/o_H17moBp2o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jZB9ZcOJSCNm5f7DBFUKPUsa7kU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inspired by true events, Founding of a Republic weaves a rousing tale of one man who fought against the tyranny of a ruler and led his people in battle in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>City of Life and Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9td_3P3w1S4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zCzNvesRkmkmlK0g2Abp4y4zhb0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1937, Japan occupied Nanjing, the Chinese capital. There was a battle and subsequent atrocities against the inhabitants, especially those who took refuge in the International Security Zone.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Electric Purgatory: The Fate of the Black Rocker</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zrdEHvREfdI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary on the struggles of the black rock musician and the stigma they face in the black community and the music industry.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stolen Eyes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bQOm5obB-_U&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bl57gtp3iYfqznuHHZrwSaxBApP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This is a story of strange, impossible, inexplicable love between a Muslim Turk woman and a non-Muslim Bulgarian man. Ivan (the Bulgarian) is a pure and romantic young fellow, who.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Decoding the Past: Nazi Prophecies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/d1wglnBlD_I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>SHINOBI: Winds of the 34 Generation</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JO3eJeamyk0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>This in-depth and comprehensive documentary chronicles the events and history behind the legendary ninja warriors of medieval Japan, and the viewer is treated to rare interviews with world-renowned ninjutsu authorities.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Assassin of the Tsar</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gL_JyqScpvQ&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/QFtKvNNmQdWcBpfUNVKUCwlkKd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A patient in a modern day mental institution believes that he is the man who assassinated Tsar Alexander in 1881 and Tsar Nicolas II in 1918. He and his doctor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sixties: The Years That Shaped a Generation</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mUc2eLe-ruI&ntz=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Vlad Tepes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VqbagKqtbAQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xG2x6ulJ7T715d826Nr9FyuMGci.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vlad Tepes, otherwise known as Vlad the Impaler and Dracula, fights the Ottoman Turks on the battlefield and the Hungarian Boyars in his court.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hitler Family</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zZaPlrwwKAU&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>This film provides history about members of Adolf Hitler's family of origin and surviving members of his family up to the date of it's release. It highlights suspected reasoning for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Inside the Twin Towers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QzXp9IZo59U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vvSAnVvtaysxC07FQiZMOWVJht.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On 9/11 2001 two planes American 11 united 175 hit the World Trade Center and many people died and jumped to their deaths some survived until the tower fell.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Somme: From Defeat to Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/S1q-Qp2Klws\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m3DpA5RY4jjAa17E5TuQ9qg79ad.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on diaries, records and eyewitness accounts, this is the story of the two Battles of the Somme from the perspective of British and German soldiers. It shows how the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Jonestown: The Life and Death of Peoples Temple</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/D7IxGGfpSWk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aS3YuTg36vSO4GHXcWWYLHC8Jm9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Featuring never-before-seen footage, this documentary delivers a startling new look at the Peoples Temple, headed by preacher Jim Jones who, in 1978, led more than 900 members to Guyana, where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Conclave</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CVz1TWIOqIU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1GDzYk2f87sUfK9L99fwhZnKlxA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Conclave is a courtroom-style drama that takes place in Rome in 1458, five years after the fall of Constantinople to Islam. It follows the story of twenty-seven-year-old Cardinal Rodrigo.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Communist</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sTM0BwgDXn8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ynaWGt1ElO1lTuaIKlxRdL9vB69.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A travel documentary essay, interspersed with specially composed songs, about the early life and legacy of Chin Peng, exiled leader of the banned Communist Party of Malaya.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Egypt: Engineering an Empire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/EjTmG1H4_Io\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 10 Conditions of Love</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_eBlu1ULA_4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/YSMbX7MHxHs5kRWzE20KFWvc7W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The 10 Conditions of Love follows the personal and political struggle of Rebiya Kadeer, the most galvanizing leader of the Uyghur people in 60 years. The Uyghur are China's Muslim.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Taras Bulba</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fkOHSmDFDFQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zdwZUBFcVpg4ficCyZ2u6UIYruB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set in the 16th century, this is a story about Ukraine's Cossack warriors and their campaign to defend their lands from the advancing Polish armies.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Time that Remains</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZmUPHXAC3Lk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ncINxlOnHtt9xG3bW4TJay1oVVX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An examination of the creation of the state of Israel in 1948 through to the present day.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Corporation</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xHrhqtY2khc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7S5rkHsVfMAQEHFQavx3nm74hNH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Since the late 18th century American legal decision that the business corporation organizational model is legally a person, it has become a dominant economic, political and social force around the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Holy Grail in America</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IorksKF6B6g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/693DsQ2ezoTcsCm0wmMpgjbF3NE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>By the Will of Chingis Khan</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JeDIVeYYOxY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lWHY1BYP5a4DQpotAYnppTDdijt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Traces of a Dragon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/O54kF3nQZYM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fG9k7e7LuvIEgzOLNuwkYejWYYb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A surprising look at the past of movie star Jackie Chan and the difficulties of Chinese families during the Culture Revolution.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>City of War: The Story of John Rabe</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Eic4y6DI5Ec\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z8CZ1wHEfFlqDmJeO1vZB72OEAE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After 28 years building and managing a vast Siemens plant in Nanking, John Rabe is ordered by the new Nazi regime to close it down. Before he can pack, the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Warrior Queen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZGkEAE_peTY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jp5himWJ0d7kMCREPc7oC6W21FJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's the first century, and Rome rules the world. After her husband's death, it's left to Boudica -fierce Iceni warrior, wife of a king, and proud mother of two daughters-.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Little Rose</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/l_Ht7hDVW2Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/otVsOPGOZKBnr17UkEvCAgd5uPa.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pressured by his superiors to disgrace public intellectual Warczewski, a professor and respected writer whom they believe to be a =camouflaged Zionist,, rough security-services colonel Rozek enlists his sexy but.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La Rafle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hW2GbaRswGk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iHJtP74X9hie5LZDwmFW7wugX1H.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1942. Joseph is eleven. And this June morning, he must go to school, a yellow star sewn on his chest. He receives the support of a goods dealer. The mockery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Autobiography of Nicolae Ceausescu</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tJEWZ33guH4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bIvh3cQIN5ZC43KDCUKeVsqmSvv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film explores the image of the Romanian dictator Nicolae Ceausescu using unknown official footage from the Romanian National Television and National Film Archives.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ao: The Last Hunter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GjxnclWlFKQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/djThnkzzM37ZwyVQsIivGs07bFh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When his clan, including his wife and baby girl Néa, are massacred, Ao, a desperate Neandertal man, decides to leave the North country where he has been living for the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bruc, the Manhunt</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VO38FhUBNWk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/55a0SniiPA9BM1tT2zYYpBt9euk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1808. The Napoleonic Army suffers its first defeat at the hands of a single man: a drummer boy who used the Montserrat mountains to echo his drums and send the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gobeklitepe: The World's First Temple</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2FbwJyXUzcQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cOCnZGN7AyxrC07H8OqKNRnHZvY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>12.000 years ago there already was a sacred place on Earth.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Nine Muses</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eegtuNM7f70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kAWP4VjYhz96FiaI6FNyW9ajyLy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Part documentary, part personal essay, this experimental film combines archive imagery with the striking wintry landscapes of Alaska to tell the story of immigrant experience coming into the UK from.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>23-F: la película</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gtZwHnnCgXo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fgw1XkdmSaD226KtIKcdNmysb3X.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The failed coup of 23 February 1981, which began with the takeover of the Spanish parliament and ended with the release of parliamentarians, put Spanish democracy in serious risk. While.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Snow Flower and the Secret Fan</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Aa93drpm30E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gAF957pT3g8kXCn8kGgo4FKIgy1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 19th-century China, seven year old girls Snow Flower and Lily are matched as laotong , or =old sames, , bound together for eternity. Isolated by their families, they furtively.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Battle of Warsaw 1920</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZAN6s5RpQ0w\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xhn5S9d415fOJj1FCcZbIcwJ4sA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The First Polish 3D Feature Film! Poland's winning battle against Soviet Russia as seen through the eyes of two young protagonists, Ola and Jan. She is a Warsaw cabaret dancer,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Films of Fury: The Kung Fu Movie Movie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NA59p4KYTNs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g2j27xhuerDgsqXjF1VlNZeoqoV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tells the story of the Kung Fu sub-culture from its ancient Peking Opera origins to its superhero-powered future. From Enter the Dragon to Kung Fu Panda and everything in between,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Banned from the Bible II</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/phyN5tWUIUI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Scriptural scholars and archaeologists spotlight books omitted from the New Testament.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Frozen Flower</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xeB5G_QeHR0&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9W86xM1vrBrWjbK7zJQfwZslu0i.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A historical drama set in the Koryo dynasty and focused on the relationship between a king and his bodyguard.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Jack the Ripper: The Definitive Story</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lUER0ddyNIg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1g5G7mAT6zLPFCnw95NhM7u5dTC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Taking you back to 1888, this extraordinary two-part special goes back to basics, dispelling the myths and misconceptions that have surrounded this case for so long. Reconstructing in 3D virtual.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>9/11: Day That Changed the World</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NniOphwZv98\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ftkiy8fCPgIvy6OtrnhsnB1P5zl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Learn first-hand how our nation's key decision makers responded in the face of chaos and catastrophe on 9/11.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>National Geographic: Hitler and the Occult</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qHxeOT8A6sQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5ToagciIQUXFboUEpMmCcmzwSM4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The world knows how the Third Reich ended. Few know how it began. Mystics now forgotten by history conjured visions of a master race and foresaw peril from lesser races..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Young Indiana Jones: Love's Sweet Song</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FjkAnOkjjX0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fYSPnTsA4Vj8vUWT7tX68PJV7br.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Indiana Jones and Remy Baudouin arrive in Ireland in April 1916 on their way to London where they plan to join the Belgian Army. In order to raise enough money.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Young Indiana Jones: Demons of Deception</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PRRkhjxr1pA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j1l8JzhROQAMzMFGAGHqA3NWWaM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>September, 1916. As Corporal Henri Defense, young Indiana Jones has become a motorcycle courier stationed near the trenches at Verdun. His friend Remy is still in the trenches, and both.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Black Power Mixtape 1967-1975</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/q5WnJcT-Y5E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mvWhjFnlFLtIWgHpNcqFuuY2T6T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Footage shot by a group of Swedish journalists documenting the Black Power Movement in the United States is edited together by a contemporary Swedish filmmaker.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nazi America: A Secret History</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hViE_lZ7rzg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>In a feature length survey of Nazism in the USA, we trace the history from the fairly benign organizations that gave structure to newly arrived German immigrants to today's neo-Nazis.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Battle of Gettysburg</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ikFeQUMxIOI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Enemy to Die For</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JUVGU2M32FY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eTcZKGt21Yd6pzSiMXZWYtygh40.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A German expedition is going to the Norwegian arctic islands of Svaldbard in late August 1939 (back then called Spitsbergen), trying to find proof of the theory that all land.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Under African Skies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/v=jw6eTs8mw70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8A2lrsqYh5CP09XVM5pKYnOsrP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paul Simon returns to South Africa to explore the journey of his Graceland album, including the political backlash he received for allegedly breaking the UN cultural boycott of South Africa.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Linotype: The Film</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/avDuKuBNuCk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8SQ4DG6d5i624SmEM0N4wYujFJL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Linotype: The Film is a feature-length documentary centered around the Linotype typecasting machine. Called the ,Eighth Wonder of the World' by Thomas Edison, it revolutionized printing and society. The film.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Are All Men Pedophiles?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oINFeGsyxBU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/95X1LTJ1HFCPH6K3HL0QZnVrIRg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For the first time in history the tables have turned on men. In the past =Witch-Hunt, was associated with women but now it is associated with men. In an effort.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>National Security</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1MRud2a4zwk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aOK1eD26TpZRejga2ujMBHeKNBm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On September 4, 1984, democracy movement leader Kim Jong Tae (Park Won Sang) is arrested and taken to an infamous interrogation facility in Namyeong-dong. For the next 22 days, he.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Portrait of Wally</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Kl_57zmJRko\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yDtZNbMz0hVi0uMiJBOkS1kvO1r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of a Nazi-looted painting, Egon Schiele's ,Portrait of Wally,' that was discovered on the walls of the Museum of Modern Art in 1997, triggering a historic court case.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Plot for Peace</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kvUVMZApJkw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ofwtP1nes05UDX7RZ7SHOqbUcr9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary that reveals the untold story of apartheid's fall, and the mysterious French businessman who was instrumental in Nelson Mandela's release from jail.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Siberian Exile</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y1UgvqxHVtk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qF0gmkN7TtyJbtiVzsAe2b0C0YW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An epic tale of countless deportations of Poles, Ukrainians and Jews to Siberia during WWII. The fate of the displaced families is shown from the point of view of a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Kiyosu Conference</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KGmrFt0caes\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rK8ilIiUVocx40izaMefaYwiWhX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After the forced suicide of Nobunaga Oda at the Incident at Honno-ji, powerful figures Katsuie Shibata, Hideyoshi Toyotomi, Nagahide Niwa and Tsuneoki Ikeda meet to decide on a successor. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Liberator</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/A6cFA0u5_Io\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aagKkCfOHDDTSv6bI1K3QJGnwn9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Simon Bolivar fought over 100 battles against the Spanish Empire in South America. He rode over 70,000 miles on horseback. His military campaigns covered twice the territory of Alexander the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Normal Heart</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fZxR9XHS0H8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fIf4nLpWHK8BsbH76fPgMbLSjuU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of the onset of the HIV-AIDS crisis in New York City in the early 1980s, taking an unflinching look at the nation's sexual politics as gay activists and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ivory Tower</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XAC9D2xtx4A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qiYiBt8pEaMxXvQwNnmtTtHnWac.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary that questions the cost &#8212; and value &#8212; of higher education in the United States.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Warsaw '44</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KEA76l3tLzM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/k9WOOkVur2Gwo93wuiKzJDm2mUK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A story of love, friendship and the pursuit of adventure during the bloody and brutal reality of the 1944 Warsaw Uprising.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Look of Silence</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/aA_ZHAs4M9k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u1G9PZlHzqBNvdSmjFPQLMVIHV3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An Indonesian man with a communist background named Ramli was brutally murdered when the =Communist, purge occurred in 1965. His remaining family members lived in fear and silence until the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>True Appaloosa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yGF7vZALBQU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cuEycYp4SDgE8ZajJP0ddZlW98W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Scott Engstrom is a life long dedicated breeder of Appaloosa horses , a hardy North American breed known for its colourful spotted pattern. Scott has long been concerned that crossbreeding.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Land of Mine</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4Kao3t0NBMU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7TOYH2VDnYbXpBKlrkdQZUSC3Du.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>SPOILER: In 1945, in Denmark, after the defeat of Germany, the tough veteran Sergeant Carl Rasmussen is assigned by Lieutenant Ebbe Jensen to defuse and remove 2.2 million mines in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Acapulco Gold</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JDAK8lL0WYU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ewT1nvRjqhJQ8rHCD6rQQkHkpiT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Antony and Cleopatra</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/r-VWNul82w0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aNaF1hhK3R8IVlmcFmEfQ5vQbTw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After the murder of her lover Julius Caesar, Egypt's queen Cleopatra needs a new ally. She seduces his probable successor Mark Antony. This develops into real love and slowly leads.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Missiles of October</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dmtp8XosVBE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dDB2qLgCc7b4Sr9BucOTkAlFpj6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based in part on Robert F. Kennedy's book, =Thirteen Days,, this film profiles the Kennedy Administration's actions during the Cuban Missile Crisis.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>To Fly!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/e6araKNbCTc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tuuKSaUTg8MBwxPWI3vM8LlKOAC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The premier film for the Theatre of the National Air and Space Museum, Smithsonian Institution. A brief summary of the history of flight, from 19th century balloons through 21st century.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Friendship in Vienna</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZyYxY8yIDr8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6juB1rgkVrzCRDQeKMJJlDbfScX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inge Dournenvald and Lise Mueller are best friends in pre-WW2 Austria, despite the fact that Inge is Jewish and Lise is the daughter of a Nazi sympathizer. When they are.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Radio Bikini</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qg4dztm4EN0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>It starts with a live radio broadcast from the Bikini Atoll a few days before it is annihilated by a nuclear test. Shows great footage from these times and tells.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Proud Heritage</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/L92niYkUggo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zMLrAWJcgJKv6WfrGwhdbIJKZup.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following the 1394 Battle of Rovine between the Wallachian and Ottoman armies Wallachian ruler Mircea the Elder consolidates his reign.In a small civil war he manages to oust his brother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Age of Stupid</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Gs9nVKbC-F4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pbY7CxwXQ6MnVqilWb6paDJqJQ5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This ambitious documentary/drama/animation hybrid stars Pete Postlethwaite as an archivist in the devastated world of the future, asking the question: =Why didn't we stop climate change when we still had.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Day After Disaster</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WCme_K6MYLY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>American Hot Wax</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NUFIkQtG0Ok\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bdRHGMl3vGugZ1gFV5RdLHPZrVE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This is the story loosely based on Cleveland disc jockey Alan Freed, who introduced rock ,n' roll to teenage American radio audiences in the 1950s. Freed was a source of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Elvira Madigan</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RJc4I6pivqg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tvzhYJES47MQnG39KIXDhRa6BGj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hedvig Jensen is a famous ropewalker and is known to her public as Elvira Madigan. She meets Lieutenant Sixten Sparre, a Swedish officer who is married and has two children..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alfred the Great</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-sasyw4a53xul-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cmx1RSD2E5YUM6gaByzkmShHT2g.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While Old England is being ransacked by roving Danes in the 9th century, Alfred is planning to join the priesthood. But observing the rape of his land, he puts away.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Vampire Secrets</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vsgtXfs6Txw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Trials of Oscar Wilde</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kQWf3VyLu9Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kjZgVFzRJOUd63KEADzTsBSzWlv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At the height of his fame (his plays being much celebrated in London in the 1890's), Oscar Wilde angers the Marquis of Queensberry by having what is whispered and gossiped.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night of the Pencils</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/itB9TDpwzWo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/p1TwMgJ84kC9oI3OOGvNFrp79a7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This films tells the true story of seven teenagers who agitated for reduced student bus fares under two different regimes in Argentina, with tragic results. At first succeeding under the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Gospel According to St. Matthew</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/L2a1gBrca6A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bJy8FbF2FOlli3GZ5AIwnfdwSGn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Along a rocky, barren coastline, Jesus begins teaching, primarily using parables. He attracts disciples; he's stern, brusque, and demanding. He comes to bring a sword, not peace, he says. He's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Optimisticheskaya tragediya</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i82jKH2Dlps\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eW5sNxoFwrmxr7IT39OxSTJibab.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Inside the Third Reich</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-d4zrfq4ccl9m-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/MYPfWgLUJcotEbFUAmof068BkI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A dramatization of the life of Albert Speer, Adolf Hitler's young architect and onetime confidant, and his meteoric rise into the Nazi hierarchy. The film is based on Speer's autobiography.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Drums in the Deep South</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gMZJCgbt2qA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8LQ2xyuem9F2QaBpYcFLQBDFZpU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Best friends Clay Clayburn and Will Denning graduate from West Point only to soon find themselves fighting on opposite sides of the Civil War. When the two men meet each.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Dam Busters</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BhjYuSjLA_s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n6rJ0btb1JyI6oCjwoylUxNcLXn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The British are desperate to shorten the length of WW2 and propose a daring raid to smash Germany's industrial heart. At first the objective looks impossible until a British scientist.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>King of the Khyber Rifles</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-a4zy85o7e351-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/p7JbKOZj8p97m4wuQbdlx0bSLg5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Freshly arrived Sandhurst-trained Captain Alan King, better versed in Pashtun then any of the veterans and born locally as army brat, survives an attack on his escort to his Northwest.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hunchback of Notre Dame</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kUkfOSTsvYg&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zuczgWA9jdWgS9DfA5TnKX8exba.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paris, 1482. Today is the festival of the fools, taking place like each year in the square outside Cathedral Notre Dame. Among jugglers and other entertainers, Esmeralda, a sensuous gypsy,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Scarlet Coat</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-dzy1ondrbq3j-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/by4fUZIyQIuOszmaeSoG7eZlvZe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1780 Major John Boulton is recruited by Colonial intelligence as a counterspy who will feign desertion to the British forces. His mission is to discover the identity of an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Raiders of Old California</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dRRGRaE2Eiw&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cCXd9mMLW8o82FN0TQCyAQiKXAm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following the Mexican-American War, a small group of discharged U. S. Cavalrymen, led by Angus McKane (Jim Davis), stays on in California after the war and, through treachery, seizes a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Count Five and Die</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6MuENZ3Ghp8&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/479Me77PgZ3xS7MwAlHMQ4Zunta.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American and British counter-espionage combine to convince the Germans the cross-channel invasion will be in the Netherlands instead of France.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Miss Stone</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tc86bexe1hM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bBkowVAedFgK8NytGr7x914z2TR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Macedonia on the turn of the century is enslaved by decaying Ottoman Empire. Freedom fighters, in order to raise money for their cause, kidnap American lady who works in Protestant.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Miles of Fire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0Kiml-N0ExU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pMmTEVRRHkr7EDWUdg2O7tEIR63.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Forever Amber</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/G22zna572v4&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xCN2L2RxgcKzV1qMhOQGwj9Tocu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Amber St Clair means to get on in life and despite a poor background knows she has the assets to do it. Husbands, lovers, prison and a liaison with King.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Young Bill Hickok</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rn2qYNB-rVc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pP6T4WKILXsT6KSe7eW6QmxM1Wm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bill Hickok in his early pre-gunslinger years as a freight-line agent protecting a gold shipment from villains out to steal gold and land out west while America is diverted by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ivan the Terrible, Part I</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VQVPNlyJqOU&feature=player_embedded\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AiChTu6aP2RN9I9Rhl3KJx9Ld0r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1547, Ivan IV (1530-1584), archduke of Moscow, crowns himself Tsar of Russia and sets about reclaiming lost Russian territory. In scenes of his coronation, his wedding to Anastasia, his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fighting Lady</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/B5JbXRDOP60&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4ZXkaIGv84P9lHErBiXuyXCfNtP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film follows the WWII exploits of the Essex-class aircraft carrier USS Yorktown (CV-10) (unidentified in the film), in its first major operations following its commissioning in 1943. The life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fight for Life</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/aOKjRBDTNso\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oyNpp7J0zDpjBrzF1fC7jR9r3o6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An interne witnesses the death of a young mother in a maternity hospital delivery room. Disturbed that he might have overlooked something that could have prevented the death, he goes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Destination Tokyo</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HvWPDG2EjCI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5la2xjLbRHfaqMTO2QyvN1sQYHD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Made during World War II, this chronicles a voyage of a U.S. submarine on a secret mission to the very shores of Japan. Much of the film is spent developing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man in Grey</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ek2G7i_yhu8&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l1m1fmdQsYKMno7sFdPofILoNQU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At an estate auction in WWII England, two strangers meet and muse about their families' history and possible connections. Flashbacks reveal the story of the sweet, rich, and beautiful Clarissa.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Royal Scandal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JvbEb3hg1ws\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6HGXhEiJu2S9Ovtpg7M6trywIN0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 18th century Russia,a naive and idealistic lieutenant,Alexei Chernoff, deserts his unit and rushes to the Imperial Palace to warn Empress Catherine the Great of great dangers.Lieutenant Chernoff's fiancée,Countess Anna,is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Joan of Arc</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nuq1D1gAs2M\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ylh5TU7qqLPMukzVhA0ZSLtDey7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A divinely inspired peasant woman becomes an army captain for France and then is martyred after she is captured.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Independence of Romania</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UA9J6funJis\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nyWHNZJa8DtNMsxEvAmkoKtpjgx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The movie depicts the Romanian War of Independence (1877-1878).</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Tale of Two Cities</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2pO2DnAMzos\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Alcoholic lawyer Sydney Carton travels to Paris during the Reign of Terror to rescue French aristocrat Charles Darnay, husband of the woman he loves.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Iron Horse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BkMq_Cs3OUs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fCu61ZeBIKPTZmNFz95SBR93Zl5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Springfield, Illinois. Brandon, a surveyor, dreams of building a railway to the west, but Marsh, a contractor, is sceptical. Abraham Lincoln looks on as their children, Davy Brandon and Miriam.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Battleship Potemkin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IPJ3n4g7DKk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/A5kk0FA4kS9sHLYzC6NI72OOhPc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on the historical events the movie tells the story of a riot at the battleship Potemkin. What started as a protest strike when the crew was given rotten meat.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beau Brummel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CaP4DXPwQN4&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8g3yQB4JeA1fViy0ET70A0B53jy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>George Bryan Brummel, a British military officer, loves Lady Margery, the betrothed of Lord Alvanley. Despite her own desperate love for Brummel, she submits to family pressure and marries Lord.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The King of Kings</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oMwZEsJagj0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1jzkm5gXpFJDxbkjuwNRBzvj3Vs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mary Magdalene becomes angry when Judas, now a follower of Jesus, won't come to her feast. She goes to see Jesus and becomes repentant. From there the Bible story unfolds.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>October (Ten Days that Shook the World)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/EUx9r6htZqA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4GMKWVdMTmu3uQBNy23M62auXXq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In documentary style, events in Petrograd are re-enacted from the end of the monarchy in February of 1917 to the end of the provisional government and the decrees of peace.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Divine Lady</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RB-rkgj97QE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wP0gEHhioKd3BffqFKugI4oJ21e.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A partly fictionalized account of history begins with the arrival of slatternly Emma Hart, a cook's daughter, at the home of Charles Greville. Greville takes her as his lover and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Scarlet Letter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sf9I89ooaDE&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4Kk3j43u9BgRA76xdXNwDAF6sO7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At the end of the 17th century a impetuous woman of noble birth but poor arrives in Boston when it was just a village rather than a city. As she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Tale of Two Cities</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-hoomi4xgm72k-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wKnAUFV9W9K3aYarNE6DBcxc8Fd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An elaborate adaptation of Dickens' classic tale of the French Revolution. Dissipated lawyer Sydney Carton defends emigre Charles Darnay from charges of spying against England. He becomes enamored of Darnay's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nine Days a Queen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/R711hKXCZ_M&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6s2J4KdmBzPN7Cw3yCihcWIK5qC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A dramatization of Lady Jane Grey's short life, from her forced marriage (which she resisted) to her brief reign as monarch of England and finally to her beheading. The film.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lloyd's of London</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pPrTrVe6XlU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xScegqeeYDeaOdfMuteCzgZQ7WP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Blake is in love with an aristocratic woman whose husband seriously injures him. Blake's friendship with Lord Nelson provides the basis for Blake's part in the growth of Lloyd's insurance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Return of the Scarlet Pimpernel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Nkp_6iDmVAc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wE8SGUIBLMj5VCFifHv4E5OYO7c.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sir Percy Blakeney(in the guise of the masked Scarlet Pimpernel), an Englishman who with the aid of a band of his friends, is engaged in spiriting FRench aristocrats across the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>This Is My Affair</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oSqxMJ-JPhQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9ePpM2Kv3UhikrbHPcpwFlqonQI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Navy Lt. Richard Perry becomes an undercover man out to discover the leaders of a group of well connected men who pull off bank robberies during the McKinley administration (early.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The River</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fpz0XI6U97U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/muEv14kOGlHj8tejIDuxsFhEEiC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This short Depression-era documentary describes the importance of the Mississippi River to the United States. It laments the environmental destruction committed in the name of progress, particularly farming and timber.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Story of Alexander Graham Bell</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9WDyKO7GQ70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9dJPFoWZ42rbXZdK7NF7RzjYZXl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Alexander Graham Bell falls in love with deaf girl Mabel Hubbard while teaching the deaf and trying to invent means for telegraphing the human voice. She urges him to put.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stand Up and Fight</title>
<link>https://thevideo.me/embed-xd4bzy6t5vd8-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g9FcQwEDVtv8Eqh34m3zIvkFnVz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It starts in 1844 in Maryland, where R.Taylor, owner a plantation with slaves, is forced by debts to sell his estate ad his people. Then he leaves for Cumberland, looking.</summary>
</item>


