<item>
<title>Out of Blue</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1098103196385\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hE8Gg6FUtZmERm4V1zUUP3a4wTX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Detective Mike Hoolihan is called to investigate the shooting of leading astrophysicist and black hole expert, Jennifer Rockwell, she is affected in ways she struggles to comprehend.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mule (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1091005385441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t0idiLMalKMj2pLsvqHrOM4LPdQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A 90-year-old horticulturist and Korean War veteran is caught transporting $3 million worth of cocaine through Illinois for a Mexican drug cartel.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Crossword Mysteries: A Puzzle to Die For</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1084328512225\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yPVaVtX32yfQ2g56dfWB5lz7UGV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A brilliant crossword puzzle editor (Chabert) finds her life turned upside-down when she is pulled into a police investigation after several of the clues in her recent puzzles are linked.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Happy Death Day 2U</title>
<link>https://vidbom.com/embed-ceqozgk1409g.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j7ODXcLHJi7a6exVH2z4wHuXxcN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tree Gelbman discovers that dying over and over was surprisingly easier than the dangers that lie ahead.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Chronicle Mysteries: Vines That Bind</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1076461701857\</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.postimg.cc/vm128RSF/d6Cyi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The new season of Alex McPherson's true crime podcast leads her and the Chronicle staff to nearby Macklin, where they investigate a death ruled as an accident by the local.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Chronicle Mysteries: The Wrong Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1864434125393\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODFhZTAyZWQtY2Q5OC00OThlLWIwNTAtYjg1MWE5MGM2OTc4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjA3OTczMw@@._V1_UY268_CR24,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Podcaster Alex McPherson seeks the truth behind the tragic death of a young lawyer, while partner Drew finds himself diving into the shady mishaps of a shipping company.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Emma Fielding Mysteries: More Bitter Than Death</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1864434387537\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zppWnnDmt5PnCs2L2WmWOhrSk2u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While hosting the annual gathering of the Association for the Study of American Archaeology at Kenzer College, Emma Fielding is thrust into the midst of a murder mystery when the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Long Day's Journey Into Night</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1861498505809\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8wUxYW7v2sahnFwipwzjRo8Z3sP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man went back to Guizhou, found the tracks of a mysterious woman. He recalls the summer he spent with her twenty years ago.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Laplace's Demon</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1860998531665\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5N5nKIrW3i1hzVADCl5RTSqsZE6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A glass in free fall. Have you ever thought if it is possible to calculate into how many pieces it can break into? After numerous experiments, a team of researchers.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>London Fields</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1849371200081\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Ap6Vqfw2VYHpLnijxCDJq0L8Uuw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Clairvoyant femme fatale Nicola Six has been living with a dark premonition of her impending death by murder. She begins a tangled love affair with three uniquely different men: one.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>August Falls</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1838023445073\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wKGISNlhsjCUgOt9P3PsuwIN6Vi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A late night phone call wakes Anna Ellison from sleep. It's the news every parent dreads: her 20-year-old son, August, has fallen from a high window. A powerful, haunting mystery,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Subject 36</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1837185043025\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vWpcN12KXFjMq09rUrO3GP0pP5g.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Gwen is a reclusive loner with an obsession with stalking and studying strangers, always at a distance. When one of her subjects enters her life in an unexpected way, Gwen.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Evil Inside</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1833281325649\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/p3HuRqRRqYEH9fxxUtnFR2utZWB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the 18th Century, John Cavendish, a Scottish adventurer, arrives in Tuscany and makes his fortune from his expert knowledge of botany and agriculture. In the present day, Marcus Cavendish,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shadows on the Road</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1829331995217\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lfpZ2YZbhhqbCu2f8s6N4XiQuGD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After a violent altercation, a runaway youth goes on the lam with a charming beach dweller offering an easy way out, but once they skip town, she quickly realizes that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Extracurricular Activities</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1829293394513\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hXDPWjbBfMr8ATmLraQXVkwL1Vj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film follows Reagan Collins, a model high school student with ,a killer, after-school job as he arranges ,accidents., When his classmates' parents become too overbearing, self-obsessed,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Based on a True Story</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1822659578449\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/q2CjMmpXL3ivMqwgfdphUSBobc1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A writer goes through a tough period after the release of her latest book, as she gets involved with an obsessive admirer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>City of Lies</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1819947108945\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pK7IYQdtdWtMDBJZfMqDxgMjXEt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Russell Poole and Jack Jackson investigate the murders of rappers Notorious B.I.G. and Tupac Shakur.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Moon Shine Still</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1812753877585\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rHbZckaoNTZK6Pm9chAkJ8uBj66.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a young hiker stumbles onto an isolated farm after losing her way on the Appalachian Trail, she is taken in by a strange yet beautiful couple desperate to protect.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Vanishing</title>
<link>https://vidbom.com/embed-1v9bj4c1iedd.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5HKn2CecRi2OlyC3T6FZz4QqkW5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inspired by the Flannan Isle mystery. A small relief boat approaches the Isle, a tiny isolated island no bigger than a football pitch, 20 miles off a rugged coast. Its.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wakey Wakey</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1797277223505\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oNQnDGNcxG36ctkYXeemGmxNVXT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Josie is a teenage girl on the cusp of her sexual awakening. Her confusion is heightened by her extreme sleep condition, which blurs her dreams into waking life. Forbidden from.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Series of Unfortunate Events</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1796576774737\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/chLSPHjb1dAZRKstpx17lnDbZU9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The orphaned Baudelaire children face trials, tribulations and the evil Count Olaf, all in their quest to uncover the secret of their parents' death.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Agatha and the Truth of Murder</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1770482895441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tlttRXgWVWMy5ZxHYG4AFZg8gS5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1926, with her personal life in tatters and her writing in crisis, a young Agatha Christie decides to solve a real-life murder.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Morning Show Mystery: Mortal Mishaps</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762749319761\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AvZ9pNRENS9ehZLwuuzavsofX8U.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Billie Blessings has gone from beloved chef, restaurant owner, and morning show segment host to the prime suspect in a murder case when one of the executives at the network.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bad Times at the El Royale</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1762185906769\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iNtFgXqXPRMkm1QO8CHn5sHfUgE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Seven strangers, each with a secret to bury, meet at Lake Tahoe's El Royale, a rundown hotel with a dark past. Over the course of one fateful night, everyone will.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The System</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1754590612049\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n10DTSmcxjFT0XVTEYCuipsGcB5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vastly different lives and perspectives become intertwined after a police officer suffering from reoccurring PTSD mistakenly shoots a deaf African-American kid, exposing layers of racial .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Laplace's Witch</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1751771843153\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aHo8352V9gA1y3IE1QCvaNdioz9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An environmental analyst is asked by the police to determine if two deaths by hydrogen sulfide poisoning are an accident , or a murder. But when he meets a young.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Frame Switch</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1749719976529\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDE0ZmU0NTUtMzRjMC00NTYzLWFkZTItYmZjMDkxMDFkMWJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYyMjA5Mzg@._V1_UY268_CR1,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A deadly wildfire leads city auditor Mercedes Lara into a web of corruption after her boss is found murdered. When flamboyant attorney Spencer Sharp reveals his theory about a larger.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>You Might Be the Killer</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1746999904849\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7hPS27PVvA0TdSRZVTOl3yXpKg8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A camp counselor suffering from blackouts finds himself surrounded by murder victims. He turns to his horror movie enthusiast friend for advice, and to contend with the idea he may.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Detective Chinatown 2</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1740282661457\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9JBftHNBnLHgqwHLiojuVSsRNpS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tang and Qin team up to solve a murder in New York's Chinatown.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Clyde Cooper</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1734701156945\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWYyMTVjYjktZDU2Mi00YjZmLWJhMzItMmI3NzIxMjRjNDU1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDk4OTQ2NTU@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A private investigator is hired to track down a missing girl on the run from a mysterious Silicon Valley corporation.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Texas Cotton</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1728484543057\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kH1AiyoGcD8df2zoHDaANEkkJpW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An aging lawman is convinced a mysterious stranger arrested in his small town is innocent. His investigation stirs up a hornet's nest that will change the town forever.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Little Stranger (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1725326232145\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/izPtQ2relqT5LWflL7x4JLTbLxy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In post-WWII Britain, a doctor revisits a crumbling great house called Hundreds Halls where his mother once worked as a nurse maid. The owners are losing the house because they.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bug (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1710648920657\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ck3PYUEsEUfPWxKK0UEtkEAs5yj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bug is a 12 year old girl who finds out that her grandpa, the town's retired sheriff, may have committed and covered up a racially motivated murder years ago. Now.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The White Orchid (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1708479220305\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/viTQS035XbUrBSxDxHQmZzbRPMT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A shy social worker must cross personal and professional boundaries in order to help solve a brutal murder in a small town.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Courting a Killer</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1705182825041\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2YzOWVlN2EtZWVlMy00M2MzLThjMDYtMGU1NTQ2ZjBkYzMyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjIwMDc1NjU@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two graduate students and lover's from USF studying Criminal Behavioral Sciences attempt to secure an interview with an active serial killer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Interview with God</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1703847201361\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vj990CYNcJTlQ78zgtk0BI11g4f.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paul Asher, an up-and-coming journalist, returns home from covering the war in Afghanistan and finds his life is falling apart. His marriage is failing and he's in the grips of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blind Sun</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1698625686097\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jJl1MG9dQwRwSz1vMkJNpIPkQxp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Greece. Sometime in the near future. A seaside resort struck by a heavy heat wave. Water is rare and violence is mounting. Ashraf, a solitary immigrant, is looking after a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gas Light</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1694444227153\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7exoMgBsEnHGIIz7tZr8VpVERJH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A troubled nun attempts to confront the haunts of her past by visiting a former flame in a distant city. Along the way she stops in a desolate river town.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Slender Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1686774811217\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/huSncs4RyvQDBmHjBBYHSBYJbSJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Slender Man tells the story of a tall, thin, horrifying figure with unnaturally long arms and a featureless face, who is reputed to be responsible for the haunting and disappearance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Boyfriend's Deceit</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1673742715473\</link>
<thumbnail>https://i.postimg.cc/R0XVvJyp/index.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While her boyfriend Oliver is away on a last-minute business trip, Annie is pulled over by police for a traffic violation as she is driving Oliver’s car. The police discover.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Between Worlds</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1638705269329\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/csQhofFqJbOrpg5QrG7xPXuyyc3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story follows Joe, (Cage), a down-on-his-luck truck driver haunted by the memory of his deceased wife and child. He meets Julie (Potente), a spiritually gifted woman who enlists Joe.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Body of Deceit</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1614944668241\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Re0KgKBkjgb09TadsuvwGboNvi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Alice (Kristanna Loken) is a ghostwriter for a famous bestselling author. She is half through the work of the his new book, but cannot write anymore. A year before she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Await Further Instructions</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1606143707729\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/afvi5tVi5S3Ux9faZaI32SmPRkj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's Christmas Day and the Milgram family wake to find a mysterious black substance surrounding their house. Something monumental is clearly happening right outside their door, but what exactly ,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>3 (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1592995023441\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yxX0nyQaTE87Odvg91lnqMU7gwT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man and a woman kidnap her rapist in order to extract a confession, come hell or , hell.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Leave Home</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1578556262993\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3Y296xLDoTOsts35P3dGErBrZbL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American artist's obsession with a disturbing urban legend leads her to an investigation of the story's origins at the crumbling estate of a reclusive painter in Ireland.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Watcher Self</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1576013597265\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/keWt9VjNY0yEqjDe6VRpWqo6ZWi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Watcher Self is an unsettling psychosexual chiller written and directed by Matt Cruse about one woman's descent into hell. Cora (Karen French) begins her day facing the consequences of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bad Seed (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1573453564497\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uNDz71NFm0awGDS6Ez5npa5OvCo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Single Parent and the Nanny suspects that their seemingly perfect adolescent daughter is a heartless killer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La femme la plus assassinée du monde</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1572082027089\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qlQv8xcQy6VUViQ9OqUHk5pUiKh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paula Maxa is the Parisian Grand Guignol Theatre's leading lady, famous for being murdered on stage every day. But is there a link between the theatre and a series of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Gentle Creature</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1566277831249\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8EfNuERL9weFWblnMUabinB2Gwb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman lives in a small village in Russia. One day she receives the parcel she sent to her husband, serving a sentence in prison. Confused and angered, she sets.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Garage Sale Mysteries: Murder In D Minor</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1561213733457\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/o8x4KtG1BaiLqhlBW09z1Q2Ulua.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jennifer wins the bid on a vintage self-playing piano at an estate auction. The piano was owned by the late Carl Deats and Jennifer discovers that this wealthy philanthropist has.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Garage Sale Mystery: The Mask Murder</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/751928543807\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/k354ywIDLVGR7mRhyuDRlofTLF3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Garage sale guru Jennifer Shannon (Loughlin) discovers a dead body in the storage locker she and business partner Dani (Strange) have purchased at auction. When further inspection of the locker’s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Adventures of Louanna Lee: The Movie</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/747874486847\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/67r8kRp1rpiaUaTt6FOX2hhr53r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Louanna Lee, America's favorite teenage detective, travels back in time to save her grandpa and the world. Will a teenage girl be able to do the impossible? Join Louanna and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Barn (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/741619206719\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTk2NDhjNDUtMTQxMi00ZDY1LTk2MTAtZWIyMThkZDAwOGM4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDkwNTA3Njg@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A serial killer strikes Sugar Grove, Virginia. A rising journalist comes to town to cover the story : her investigation will soon lead her to the town's darkest secret, at.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Aurora Teagarden Mysteries: The Disappearing Game</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/741619010111\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3XKv2Mr5oFl6oA0ejj2NoMy6obP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When her nephew and his roommate disappear, following the suspicious death of the roommate's girlfriend, Aurora investigates. Enlisting the help of her friends, she is also assisted by her new.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Third Murder</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/738923514431\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t0WEz9ELPl7tag1bzOiK3EQiAuT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A courtroom drama centered around the murder of a factory president.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Narco Hitman</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/738907982399\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tpPoBqyazd5ofpxIwqgjothakH5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A contract killer takes vengeance against a ruthless drug cartel, resulting in a mysterious puzzle that a small town sheriff must solve in order to stop untold horrors.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Crescent</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/725459733055\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lUfUeDvSzCTVyFlROIEOyUUYRWW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After an unexpected death in the family, a mother and son struggle to find spiritual healing at a beachfront summer home.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Noctem (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/718725646911\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/79Xs5xva1wVaufzHGsq2PNBBPq8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Nights in a row, Adrian finds himself in his apartment, with no lights and strange sounds coming from the inside. He asks his friends for help and one of them.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Super Troopers 2</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/715481090623\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/57SZgdugVClIy22rfnANeBJ5KsN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a border dispute arises between the U.S. and Canada, the Super Troopers are tasked with establishing a Highway Patrol station in the disputed area.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Armenian Haunting</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/714880387647\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yWx8068D4PLghuCkQ1Oh84qOirw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An Armenian-American journalist turns into an unwilling ghost hunter while researching the sudden deaths in her family and their connection to a paranormal mystery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Wrong Bed: Naked Pursuit</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/708719544895\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/89Xbj3kL3tnUXgHD97XwWBnQV58.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After losing her job at an insurance company, Stella Williams wakes up in a hotel handcuffed to sexy firefighter Owen Michaels. Messages they left themselves the night before reveal that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dark River</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/705436387903\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hgzMPafOXa4wCGMvHGNpJLbr7Xv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following the death of her father, Alice (Ruth Wilson) returns to her home village for the first time in 15 years, to claim the tenancy to the family farm she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gemini (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/698464602687\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oIltQs7MPk7VQFG3DJfgC63mShU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A heinous crime tests the complex relationship between a tenacious personal assistant and her Hollywood starlet boss. As the assistant travels across Los Angeles to unravel the mystery, she must.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Inheritance (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/698473974335\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cZp9SGcM6tnGjZGVafEpHaojhhs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Ryan mysteriously inherits a house from his biological father, a man he thought long dead, he and his pregnant fiancé travel to the property with high hopes for the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alien Code</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/693206583871\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jMtEs75UTX8Nan6GvsBbA86iAFJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After deciphering a message found in a satellite, genius cryptographer Alex Jacobs finds himself being stalked by government agents and otherworldly beings.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beyond The Sky</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/693142293055\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6cZyzLpCIcZeH7UlDgDZEM7GpNu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary filmmaker travels to a UFO convention in New Mexico where he meets a local artist with a dark secret. As they follow a trail of clues they discover.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hailey Dean Mysteries: 2+2 = Murder</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/689669278271\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3kXR8wGHGeiC1gU5YeuSNg0ptMc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hailey attends her niece's school recital only to learn that the beloved music teacher has vanished. Hailey soon discovers several startling secrets amongst the staff, as well as a link.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Satan's Slaves</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/684860770879\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2XB9EO9L8t0ryipAoB9WlsxXOIl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After Rini's mother died, something is disturbing her family.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>They Remain</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/683358554687\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pCsB2IePfLj5eQXXziGb8Xyxblm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two scientists investigate the root of environmental changes and strange animal behavior at a remote site where a cult committed atrocities. The isolated location, the unraveling of their relationship, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Pale Man</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/668849801791\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BN2M4YjUwNGItYTYzYi00NGRiLTk4NTEtZjc3ZDdlYzU3NWY0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjMyMDY5MTg@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A teachers assistant, trapped in a small town with a strange illness, takes on a local missing persons case aided by a Pale Man down the hall.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Paranormal: White Noise</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/665200560703\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/swghccaPcYwO2tvf1Wv8mpeNLUn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A writer who studies the paranormal believes that low frequency tactile sound is the cause for reported ghost sightings in an abandoned subway station. In an attempt to debunk the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Circle of Atonement</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/660118833727\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ikSwURb4OpMWybtwyFJLPWXr7JL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A policeman discovers a love affair between his teenage daughter and her teacher which leads him back to an unsolved murder case he investigated 10 years ago.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Did I Kill My Mother?</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/659895945791\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZGEwMzg0OGItMGQ0MS00N2IyLWJlMDEtY2Q1ZDI5NWY0NWMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjg1MzM5MDU@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A year after her father’s unsolved, suspicious murder, a young woman’s mother is found dead in the home they both live in. The police think she may be the murderer,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>M.I.A. A Greater Evil</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/659894503999\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzhhMzU3MDUtNjcwYi00ZWU0LTkzY2EtZjNlOGQ4Y2JlNjViXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk3NDA1NTE@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American college students head to the jungles of Vietnam to search for lost gold. They become hopelessly lost, and they may not be alone.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Altered Perception</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/639331797567\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rKFayS6mDP30wetxIaDm4Whh8kR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Blanc-Biehn production centered around the idea of a governmentally designed drug created to help correct or strategically alter perceptions gathered during times of trauma or stress. Slated as being.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gehenna: Where Death Lives</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/639339465279\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uQfpAkBrKSILSzcswtzAFmOubDs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group visits Saipan to search for locations for their company's newest resort. As they find what they think is the perfect spot, they discover a hidden bunker on the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Redeeming</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/637419981375\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6T75zEBrQAuVp4G4hGW7U7qs2OV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A disturbed single mother confronts a mysterious stranger and the echoes of her past to protect her home.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Seen in Idaho</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/629903919679\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDY4NzhjZDktNmI2Ni00NGVkLTg4MDctZTczNGJiZDdkNmZjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg0ODE1ODE@._V1_UY268_CR4,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman awakens from a coma after a car accident and begins having shocking visions of her future murder. It's a race against the clock as she tries to solve.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Red Sparrow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/623617837631\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uZwnaMQTdwZz1kwtrrU3IOqxnDu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Prima ballerina Dominika Egorova faces a bleak and uncertain future after she suffers an injury that ends her career. She soon turns to Sparrow School, a secret intelligence service that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gone Tomorrow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620963826239\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOWJlNGM0MzYtMTg1Yy00OWRjLWI3ZTYtM2M4N2I4OWRkYWE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzE4MjE0MA@@._V1_UY268_CR13,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five years after taking the fall for his younger brother, a tormented ex-con flees parole to find his kidnapped baby niece. One step ahead of the police, and one behind.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bold, the Corrupt and the Beautiful</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/620172675647\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7CvEVro9xb3HHZOJ4alfNkEWryM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Madame Tang colludes and mediates between the government and the private businesses for the benefits of her all-female family. One case does not go according to plan, and an entire.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cover Versions</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/618322790975\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c6lxVgSNVdp9JkcFPVfLRiZrFgq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the eve of their biggest gig ever, the members of synth-rock band Starfoxy throw a rager that ends with a fan mysteriously dead in the pool.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Preacher's Son</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/617882978879\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pIIAdean2jT16LJNbjVDCGjTRru.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When the romantic secrets of his family members become public, the career and community standing of a respected bishop are threatened.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Beautiful Ones</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/613364795967\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kjy1obH5Oy1IsjTViYVJDQufeZP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A retelling of Romeo and Juliet set within the Los Angeles underworld.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Trouble Is My Business</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/611799730751\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4dw0z5Uh2NbabdGk2u6wdyJvMg7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Private eye Roland Drake cracks cases and romances femme fatales in 1940's Los Angeles while corrupt cop Det Barry Tate rules the city. A tale told in the classic style.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ten: Murder Island</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/611797371455\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jCcVc1sWSoR40AM4MSOgXQKNT3e.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of kids travel to an abandoned island for a party only to discover that they are being stalked and hunted down by a dangerous predator.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Commuter</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/610265074239\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rDeGK6FIUfVcXmuBdEORPAGPMNg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A businessman on his daily commute home gets unwittingly caught up in a criminal conspiracy that threatens not only his life but the lives of those around him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Outsider (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/584322058815\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m2riQcEzjVrkP8wKHDXwC5EQpHQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An epic set in post-WWII Japan and centered on an American former G.I. who joins the yakuza.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Malady (2015)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/553449032255\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w85l9uFodwh3jpOXng3yNKxDfq8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>To fulfill the last wish of her deceased mother, grieving Holly seeks out love and finds it in Matthew; their relationship swiftly becomes very close and all-encompassing. After receiving the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ghost Mountaineer</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/539098483263\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zDiRk9bkaxJCH06h4Bg1byW9AaI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ghost Mountaineer aka Must alpinist Movie is a feature film with some hints of horror, based on actual events in Siberia back in Soviet times. A group of Estonian students.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stealing Paradise</title>
<link>https://estream.to/embed-xaxb8w099d4m.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ci5zLkPwbjFLVsA2YL3yA3n9hi5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Amanda, a brilliant engineer, is enraged when her breakthrough design is stolen and patented by her colleague Brendan. When he is found murdered, Amanda is the prime suspect and soon.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Chance Detectives: Mystery Lights of Navajo Mesa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OrDaNkaJiDw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/A0YzyNBXjVAoca1Ugx7kv815php.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Unfamiliar voices through an antique radio, items disappearing and this strange light that keeps appearing; its the job for the Last Chance Detectives to check it out.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>My Neighbor's Keeper</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OE-2SvCS3ss\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jQ5r5C5wxFIrlS33LQHPU677bcZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Kate Powell was a happy housewife with her husband Tim and accepted working with small children in hospital who lack motherly love. When her best friend Ann Harding gets murdered.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Children of the Mist</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ffCNjQwytiw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sq31ortL1GDcr0RTlPvQGkFhgLk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man (Bergin) that is unable to express himself emotionally, loses his eleven year old daughter in a car accident after missing her performance in a ballet due to his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Golden Gate Murders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OyFg291i8Ak\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dteVX2zc0yqQd1P4xuvVTbr9isj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An elderly, venerable priest, goes over the Golden Gate bridge and everyone except his nurse, Sister Benecia, believes that it was suicide. Sister Benecia finally convices the police department to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nightworld: Survivor</title>
<link>https://thevideo.me/embed-iz4v23rdijf4-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pe2FQ7L96zkBaLO9zPqh1IOEBaA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An Arctic oil rig crew discovers something strange far beneath the Earth's surface, which may or may not be responsible for the series of murders that begin to take place.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mother! (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344012950079\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qmi2dsuoyzZdJ0WFZYQazbX8ILj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A couple's relationship is tested when uninvited guests arrive at their home, disrupting their tranquil existence.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Zodiac Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AZ84emK3zoI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eoPS4EaZrvRq3CJ6tAkWKeBjXDq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The San Francisco area is beset by a series of seemingly random murders without motive or pattern. The police are taunted by phone calls and letters. Could the maniac be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Strange Monster of Strawberry Cove</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VzhgJdj9U-U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rKlH2eqp5Bkn8IJanvwoNJv42sk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A school teacher thinks he saw sea monster in the calm waters of Strawberry Cove. Three kids then build one in defense of their teacher and set out to find.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shadow of the Blair Witch</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-JxeNNYbvKE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/q75tCM4pFmUzdCg0gqcOQquCaYf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this true-crime documentary, we delve into the murder spree that was the inspiration for Joe Berlinger's ,Book of Shadows: Blair Witch 2.,</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Kings Row</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dXeIr470Y-M\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fVXoIwDUK0jBvxETwUWoWoCHWS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five children in an apparently ideal American small town find their lives changing as the years pass near the turn of the century in 1900. Parris and Drake, both of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Happy Death Day</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/385828457102\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cTaEIUYTt52ooq9quVbAQ7NpGwo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A college student relives the day of her murder over and over again as she tries to discover her killer's identity.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Moon</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/345150917183\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lvSa2tlvXCUvk4dtKk0oK6lgmrt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cold Moon takes place in tiny Babylon, Fla., where the granddaughter of Clark’s character is murdered by a mysterious assailant, her body sunk into the black waters of the Styx.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Marjorie Prime</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344004037183\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wcIPaT9ktpJHNaMyAiRMcra8NIM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the near future, a time of artificial intelligence: 86-year-old Marjorie , a jumble of disparate, fading memories , has a handsome new companion who looks like her deceased husband.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sound</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/341974452799\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/swghccaPcYwO2tvf1Wv8mpeNLUn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A writer who studies the paranormal believes that low frequency tactile sound is the cause for reported ghost sightings in an abandoned subway station. In an attempt to debunk the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Entertaining Mr. Sloane</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y0C7jgJnJfk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xCSvzJBj43VU8NujjkICxwbgn9N.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sloane, a handsome, sexy and completely amoral young man, joins Kath's household as a lodger and proceeds to manipulate her and her brother, Ed. He is recognized by Kemp (Dadda).</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Witness for the Prosecution</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/03CuUuMS-AY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zmEpGw1e0zLMwERgBF2qV8KYWPo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set in 1920s London, a brutal and bloodthirsty murder has stained the plush carpets of a handsome London townhouse. The victim is the glamorous and rich Emily French. All the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Singing Detective</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DKrC9Tu8gpo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sFSdrg4SM9hl5a86bsW6zrsN4QV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Reworking material from his first novel, ,Hide and Seek, (1973), and folding this into a prismatic blend of autobiographical details, popular music and 1940s film noir, Dennis Potter delivered a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wild Palms</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/http://youtu.be/2J1taQAsHJg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xHiL8D1O9m6nnGzMn8PlkdNIREc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>LA in the near future, Harry Wykoff accepts a job as presidents of a gigantic TV company. Het is confronted with a total new technology called ,The New Reality, where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death in Holy Orders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZYN-CMnL018\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nTYCkoN5P4HSqHOAH7LAbmUx0JU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>New Scotland Yard Commander Adam Dalgleish is asked to have a second look at the death of Ronald Treeves, a student at St. Anselm's seminary. He was killed when a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death Comes to Pemberley</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PhmgTlVXbxw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fBHk6JjRyLbuzNaFSTJLbOzRBsl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Elizabeth and Darcy, now six years married, are preparing for their annual ball when festivities are brought to an abrupt halt. An adaptation of PD James's homage to Pride and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death Note</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/351810292366\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fJAvGOitU8y53ByeHnM4avtKFaG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Light Turner, a bright student, stumbles across a mystical notebook that has the power to kill any person whose name he writes in it. Light decides to launch a secret.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I'm a Killer (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344680434318\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gTahmz59BI4zx5cJKZe6sdXw1M1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jestem morderca Inspired by true events from the 1970s, the story revolves around a young detective who becomes the head of a police unit focused on catching a rampant serial.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Spoor (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/344527669902\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3URcxp6EnCLVqapsyJynn7WizVc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pokot A story about Janina Duszejko, an elderly woman, who lives alone in the Klodzko Valley where a series of mysterious crimes are committed. Duszejko is convinced that she knows.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Braxton Butcher</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/330703768182\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc5NWY4YjItODZjMS00ZDQ2LThhZjktMThiM2JkNDUxMDljL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTI4NTM1Mw@@._V1_UX182_CR0,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Braxton A serial killer returns to a small town on the anniversary of his initial spree, forcing a young cop , himself a survivor of the original massacre , to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>White Wall</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KXIDCfoj8Qw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ipoTbjPegYa0RpxR93u8v3V74.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the near future, everything has changed. Basic human rights have become the rarest of luxuries. No one knows when this started but everyone knows how. The VXII, the deadliest.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Outlaw</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Awcx-YZdp-w&hd=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/skjSOMX4HDWQnkSk89Ia16ItVJc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A detective seeks retribution for unpunished killers and the rest of the cruel world , even if it means going outside the law.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Curse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WpuYP4d5xXQ&cc=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Investigative Journalist Jin Duyen goes to the site of a brutal murder committed the week before. The police have given out few details, not even the victims are known. Upon.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Silent Hill: Lost Innocence</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9566K9Ioqfw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>After the mysterious death of her father, Heather is forced to go into the scary town of Silent Hill. Something dark awaits for her but Heather will learn to face.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Petite anatomie de l'image</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AVTSTbaFomY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>At the end of the 18th century, Florentine artists reproduced in the wax bodies laid bare by the scalpels of surgery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Have Sword Will Travel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MICMaSc2lOA&feature=c4-videos-u\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wxrJkWy7osbDauYn8Ip0FpYGFGY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ying Ke-Feng, head of Peerless Manor, is an expert swordsman whose escort business transports 200,000 taels of silver to the capital each year. This year, however, he is afflicted with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Imperfections (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/337349380750\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/f9C9LIVkXEaMrpiadG9i8tPmZ9J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cassidy is a struggling actress, grinding out auditions, worrying that any chance at stardom may have already passed her by. Desperate to save money to move to Hollywood, she takes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Persian Connection</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/337346300558\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pw2Q0CWkFEg0JbsDcUR7QnQjRpb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Loner After being wrongly accused of stealing from his former boss, an Iranian gangster with girl problems must hunt down stolen drugs in this neon-noir fever dream set in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hypersomnia (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/335080589966\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/A8zgO68TWhR6wdv84Z3RvBXxO54.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hipersomnia A young actress rehearsing for a play about human trafficking begins to relive terrifying scenes that may be dreams &#8212; or an alternate reality. A thriller about Human trafficking.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Phoenix Forgotten (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333304171150\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8GJ9a0FgkCKIqKvGtkppTTALGG3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>20 years after three teenagers disappeared in the wake of mysterious lights appearing above Phoenix, Arizona, unseen footage from that night has been discovered, chronicling the final hours of their.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hel (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/328837696142\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vAFhlwhjZYQbkIwknB36E8QoYI8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jack, an unappreciated American writer in his sixties, comes to the off-season peninsula of Hel in the north of Poland and isolates himself to write a script. He meets Kail,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Busters Mal Heart (2016)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/324969433742\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3FHmgpH9K8wNP1bWJM2U6lfkHHt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An eccentric mountain man on the run from the local sheriff recalls the mysterious events that brought him to his present fugitive state.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The House of Witchcraft</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/g0tP7qi498w\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r2iD4N7mlck7TfTM2n0PjmLFXcW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man has dreams of a house and a witch, his girlfriend suggests a break and and head for her family home unbeknown to him the house is the same.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Big Fix (1978)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qmKLjjhxbyg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/29pLVQ72NlOSBY1j8PXkORf85Dv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Moses Wine, Richard Dreyfuss, at home one night watching a football game that he bet on is contacted by an old flame back from his radical days in collage Lila,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Conjuring 3</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2o2dLdb1UGA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://img.watch4hd.com/2017/horror/the-conjuring-3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ed and Lorraine Warren return to investigate a case in the 1980s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Before I Fall (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/336435219086\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eowzonDJMCuNXoJGVkP9Z7oCmiM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Samantha Kingston has everything. Then, everything changes. After one fateful night, she wakes up with no future at all. Trapped into reliving the same day over and over, she begins.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Human Monster</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jEywLLAwyNk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zPo2f1LlugyPWLxipaiMDaqjNYC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A series of strange deaths takes place in London. All are accidents but the victims are single men with no family and they all have a link to a life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deadly Games</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i0OnDYxdilk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z1f9ScJ5tfGf3CJRxrpINLOYC9J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A town is being terrorized by a masked killer who is murdering women. A young woman is attacked by the killer but escapes. She believes the killer to be either.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Eighteen Jade Arhats</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0WjvD1wkzfE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4lkryPrkNOLnHgzKbsWTmzGncBW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>My World Dies Screaming</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GOABQLdkp4Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ovguZImsKG0N8lyxhuv0eaQIi50.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American-born Sheila Wayne has lived in Switzerland since childhood. Now newly married, she has a recurring nightmare about an ominous old house she can't recall having seen in waking life..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Forbidden Photos of a Lady Above Suspicion</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PCpcX3qTgIw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/htl9sCfdYtBVwsRMo5f6zgwk04u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A triangle of friendship, love, sex, and, perhaps, murder. Minou is newly married to Peter, a businessman in debt as he works to bring a new product to market. They.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bride Wore Black</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oCGVIg1ksYU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iDj7QFYq9YfmUVc1ALanQmYfTaj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After trying to commit suicide, the widow Julie Kohler (Jeanne Moreau) pretends to her mother that she will leave her town. Actually she stays, chases and assassinates the five men.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The X-Files Game</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vmRmyZJ7ZK8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>When Agents Mulder and Scully so missing in Seattle, local FBI Agent Craig Willmore is assigned to investigate. Although his investigation leads him to believe the Agents were killed in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Perils of the Sentimental Swordsman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5225ex8-YiA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pvEhXoFQlW4X59WrvyfsvHeZZFj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bloodstained Shadow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6GU7e9UU8H0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/69PmM18O8gxE49v611rf8UqmfYN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The body of a schoolgirl is found in a meadow. The murderer is never caught, and years later; a young man named Stefano returns to the island and is reunited.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>911 Mysteries Part 1: Demolitions</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2O7LwySqtr4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bb0c97ooMKXhvPTpSvsCUXrlHVk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>911 Mysteries is a documentary that attempts to tell the people what really happened. It systematically deconstructs all of the propaganda you have heard about the twin towers, and replaces.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fast and Loose</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GZCOzRAX73c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2PEucrAlY8RCyVH9tJUlU90dxTL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The scrap of the Shakespeare manuscript is priceless. Nick Torrent owns it and is selling it. But then he is murdered and the manuscript is stolen. Joel Sloane is a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Lizard in a Woman's Skin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wOmQ0TtoBoQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3zkAF5F3HVocNnbYwj9nV8vd0xJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Florinda Bolkan plays the daughter of a prominant English politician who keeps having recurring ,nightmares, in which she makes love to a bisexual nympho who lives downstairs and conducts all-night.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Eleventh Aggression</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xpoR6_Obdqc&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Taken from police archives of a real series of brutal murders that occurred over a period of eleven years, the tense story laid out by critically acclaimed director, Charles Peterson.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Very Little Time</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hIV-TjNEEVc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Going about his normal routine, Ryan Telnifer stumbles across a mysterious box that is buried in the property behind his house. At first, he is intrigued by this strange discovery,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Her Perfect Spouse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ch6TdUxMSO4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lu4WoMoWlEAbLi3DxPWpKUMM9H2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lisa meets widowed author Ty Kellington and it's not long before they marry. At first, everything seems fine, but then Ty begins to resent all intrusions to their relationship and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Door</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-xnj29mbns7gg-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/k8qMyCOdKaHhZt18R5JhmruoBvb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>David Andernach (Mads Mikkelsen) lives non-chalantly at the height of his success as a painter, as a tragic misfortune befalls him from one second to the other. While he is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Plain Truth</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ievmE4LWDKg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/i0hlXk2PsC0hjj9S4dqH9GSRci6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Discomfort strikes an Amish farm in Lancaster County, Pennsylvania when a dead baby is found. When the mother is discovered and confirmed to be eighteen-year old, unmarried Katie Fitch, she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Plain Clothes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ToFguCqKhPg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5oCPnfFsMZbFNECJ5Wby1G2Ujia.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Trying to get his brother out of jail, Nick has to bump his way out again from high school, find the murderer, keep his job as a policeman and run.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Private Detective: Two Plus Two Plus One</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mOaWbXSVP5A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bOwotjsziONjNQPgONm5B8qyc58.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An urban contemporary film about adultery, murder and betrayal in the film noir style. A simple story to which the director imparts a feeling of unrest and disquiet, catching the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Dead Are Alive</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/f36sak8MHvg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dSchhXc73OvRbhuzO4gBsnzdqr3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A photographer on an archaeological expedition digging up Etruscan ruins in Italy begins to suspect that not all the Etruscans buried there are actually dead.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Terror in the Wax Museum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HwdiAKwWJ_Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vIUXPIpbd6ZfAY8McHHkxC5c2Gs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The murder of a Wax Museum proprietor and some other strange goings-on in the vicinity prompt a police investigator to determine whether the killer is one of the principles who.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Case of the Black Cat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BQWsktMW6qU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6GIrRqSJuhifu0T6socOFa1om9V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lawyer Perry Mason is summoned to the Laxter mansion in the dead of night to write granddaughter Wilma out of invalid Peter Laxter's will, to keep her from marrying suspected.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Apartment 4E</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-t0j60f5ah1pf-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2LhmJWvPcIQ0E87SP8t9WIyqhQP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Three months ago, Piper met Mollie online. And Mollie changed everything. Now a knock at the door. John Sharp. Mollie's brother. He was sent to talk Piper out of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Who Dung It?</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-9qao0m6z7bm9-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>An office worker gets accused of a crime no man should ever be accused of (a violent bowel movement), and makes it his mission to clear his name and solve.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gkPdvRontMc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/myK9DeIsXWGKgUTZyGXg2IfFk0W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Francis, a young man, recalls in his memory the horrible experiences he and his fiancée Jane recently went through. It is the annual fair in Holstenwall. Francis and his friend.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Speckled Band</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FUpwMmeT4ZA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iAgpvVljxRIhaSrj65fauQ6T6sA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Violet Stoner dies under mysterious circumstances in her bedroom at the gloomy mansion of her brutish stepfather, Dr. Grimesby Rylott. Because Violet had become engaged to be married, she stood.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night Nurse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MUe1fFdh_eQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jxVxOf0jsyCp7pQi01yWEyj1Zco.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lora Hart manages to land a job in a hospital as a trainee nurse. Upon completion of her training she goes to work as a night nurse for two small.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Love Bound</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qgip2cZz9so\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a0BSn9qCfKB4rkHmaHAazn1RjB8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A gold-digging woman wins a big settlement against an older married man, which threatens to destroy the man's family. His son, discovering that the woman is part of a ring.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Haunted Gold</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pbfX3rcyE78\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cqAR6CSgHJU1o2HpFx6oMLJoWdA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>John Mason returns to the Sally Ann mine to claim his half share. Janet Cater also returns although her father lost his half share to Joe Ryan. Ryan and his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mystery of the Wax Museum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hdl-ycmgyRY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4ErcOurvHrE5Nlh8CNfcmUUZDBU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In London, sculptor Ivan Igor struggles in vain to prevent his partner Worth from burning his wax museum.and his  children.' Years later, Igor starts a new museum in New York,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Charlie Chan in London</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Xpk1le36ZRI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mC3BeyEXYi1qMS4H8RqsbjJ7VXx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After receiving congratulations from the Home Secretary for solving his most recent case, Charlie is sought out by Pamela Gray, a beautiful but desperate young socialite whose brother Paul awaits.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mark of the Vampire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eyvOdKm0eDo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ubyRl59qT5zxLXEROwSOfHOGliR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After Sir Karell Borotin is found dead in his study, drained of his blood, the local doctor determines that he was killed by a vampire. The coroner and police Inspector.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Clairvoyant</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nhfT4noIhRA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xF010ICdSzI9FeECAC6Izy0K0cc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Maximus, a small-time music hall mind reader, has frightening flashes of precognition; but he cannot predict or control them .until he realizes he has them in the presence of Christine,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Satan Met a Lady</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/E1wEoM9sl70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/y71qET72S6jtMSVAlUFUwYDkEKl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sardonic detective Shane, thrown out of one town for bringing trouble, heads for home and his ex-partner's detective agency. The business is in a sad way, and Shane, who has.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>After the Thin Man</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sZuTCnxTXcI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9BGKDCN7kk3W5YWy0sGApXDlc3r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Now back in San Francisco after their holiday in New York, Nick and Nora find themselves trying to solve another mystery. It's New Year's Eve and they are summoned to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>They Won't Forget</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b3WXXVJeHl4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u5mBO1y2Nw27E2dqJIGtfOqu1Om.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A southern town is rocked by scandal when teenager Mary Clay is murdered on Confederate Decoration Day. Andrew Griffin, a small-time lawyer with political ambitions, sees the crime as his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night Must Fall</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qXoHI1G47gE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8VFpWvNRz2AJzLJwZn4803Ud8Vj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Crotchety old Mrs. Bransom hires a charming young man named Danny as a live-in companion. Less charmed by Danny is Mrs. Bransom's niece, Olivia, a repressed young woman who suspects.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sh! The Octopus</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fIwF60gHa_4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fSiGqLLhBuZIxP5v4HgVXn5Nbnw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Comedy-mystery finds Detectives Kelly and Dempsey trapped in a deserted lighthouse with a group of strangers who are being terrorized by a killer octopus AND a mysterious crime figure named.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mr. Moto Takes a Chance</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_WMSda2Cv9s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wE6Tw9gPxV8WxndgoqA6OjOEyLi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Beautiful aviatrix Victoria Mason teams up with Mr. Moto in South East Asia to uncover a murderous village high priest who is trying to overthrow the ruling Rajah Ali.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nancy Drew. Reporter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tkwnlEqk_pg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tHwdQMNXWD3ts4qrugbtI4oNfS6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While participating in a contest at a local newspaper in which school children are asked to submit a news story, local attorney Carson Drew's daughter Nancy intercepts a real story.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mr. Moto's Gamble</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Bz82sPp8V4U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/labhaiszGFh1k1HsawR7uTtu7kZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bad blood exists between Bill Steele and Frankie Stanton, the leading contenders for the heavyweight title, and a grudge match is scheduled. Steele's knockout victory is tainted by his opponent's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hound of the Baskervilles</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gmdBs412qYw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/v1hSYSF3FHOrqXqihorptQmgUct.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On his uncle's death Sir Henry Baskerville returns from abroad and opens up the ancestral hall on the desolate moors of Devonshire. Holmes uncovers a plot to have Sir Henry.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Invisible Man Returns</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Nrxb6tqeiHM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fa9csCs1SdmMDGKiGfbwtQenBMT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Framed for the murder of his brother, Geoffrey Radcliffe is scheduled to hang. After a visit from his friend Dr. Frank Griffin, he vanishes mysteriously from prison. Police inspector Sampson.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ghost Breakers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/F6nF-9YHAKY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r0z7MhF0jV2mNejmRteFPJgKfcd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mary Carter inherits her family's ancestral home, located on a small island off Cuba, and, despite warnings and death threats, decides to take possession of the reputedly haunted castle. She.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murder Over New York</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i1r3cmXIFss\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hwqe8SKXSVYppuQSK5GR7fAdrvj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Coincidence like ancient egg, leave unpleasant odour. Canary unlike faithful dog, do not die from sympathy. Number 2 son very promising detective, promise very much, deliver very little. Nut easy.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Topper Returns</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yUVyg12Dynk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/i6uG19h7LDH103B3iWIbUVIWaEp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Topper is once again tormented by a fun-loving spirit. This time, it's Joan Blondell, who was accidentally murdered while vacationing at the home of her wealthy friend, Ann Carrington (Landis),.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night Monster</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eoaL3ClDuX4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Apa4S7koJ3fvCOd1QEWWvwsJDpb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dr. Lynn Harper, psychologist, has been called out to the old Ingston Mansion, a dark and mysterious place with a very bad reputation, in order to make an assessment of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eyes in the Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JylLN47E3Jw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9Afd54EmSZ0BLCoaSDYiDMnQjEx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Blind detective Duncan Maclain is visited by old friend Norma Lawry, looking for help in getting rid of one of her old beaus, who is courting Norma's 17-year old step-daughter..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dr. Renault's Secret</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/N1OjvtMih8E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/daObizXzEiLsAgBS9zw0pAkZFKH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young man visits his fiancée in a remote French villa where her scientist father resides. There he meets Noel, Dr. Renault's mysterious assistant, who has a strange attraction to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Night Has Eyes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lwts14_PIlc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zb53FFPceWqViJSIwkgC3RJE962.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two teachers, man-hungry Doris and restrained Marian, visit the Yorkshire moors a year after friend Evelyn disappeared there. On a stormy night, they take refuge in the isolated cottage of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The G-string Horror</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-clew0xozgvfs-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l05dvyqQDhoO8kb3qmrLq1Khudp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a production company starts shooting a horror film in a 100 year old.and actually haunted.Sid Grauman built movie palace turned strip club in San Francisco, the  inhabitants' revolt and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Seventh Victim</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/P9H7rUJi7NQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5uBUc7guJ0fWrFSismvPPg9QZzh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When her older sister Jacqueline disappears, Mary Gibson is forced to leave her private school and decides to travel to New York City to look for her. A bit naive.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ghost and the Guest</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UegwaIDUpuU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/43amuvoLCHmzpXiB73j5Fl3nP9K.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A newlywed couple winds up spending their honeymoon night in an old, dark, spooky mansion.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fallen Sparrow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TjiopPetVSU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pyW2dryFIaxR8NiavjQBDrDnkYO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A former Spanish Civil War prisoner, John McKittrick arrives in New York to find the truth behind the death of his friend Louie Lepetino. He finds himself being chased by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Scarlet Claw</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3HGESZRExYU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bxSNJPcF8dd1au7maOatScDPkEI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While attending a conference in Quebec City, Sherlock Holmes and his good friend Dr. Watson are drawn into a murder investigation in the nearby village of La Mort Rouge. Holmes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tall in the Saddle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rt6bvg8N7L0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gvLZw3AciIyXTR4pIKSVGZp3Cl1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a stranger arrives in a western town he finds that the rancher who sent for him has been murdered. Further, most of the townsfolk seem to be at each.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Spider Woman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uLvE45e_lzs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1nAQZjoUNLrfMCCNL9i5PjZoIfV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sherlock Holmes takes on a case that the press has dubbed the pajama suicides. Eminent men are going to bed in the safety of their own homes, with everything seemingly.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Canterbury Tale</title>
<link>https://www.thevideo.me/embed-go46czgt0mzt-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kmvtTJxcU0nseD2gxxBDCM9rHg6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A  Land Girl', an American GI, and a British soldier find themselves together in a small Kent town on the road to Canterbury. The town is being plagued by a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Isle of the Dead</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fI4D8KokkWg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/acITU2Yzeg7PVo17vWuJwqVFWnv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On a Greek island during the 1912 war, several people are trapped by quarantine for the plague. If that isn't enough worry, one of the people, a superstitious old peasant.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lady on a Train</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jqhl95TmMlA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dpBKCWV6XOYs4pC4BgoJwFan6hx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While waiting at a train station, Nikki Collins witnesses a murder from a nearby building. When she brings the police to the scene of the crime, they think she's crazy.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Jade Mask</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gcTtjoSMkDQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8L15rX5jbvHYudaSS5h5zlLitAQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Eccentric scientist Harper lives in a spooky mansion with all the trimmings: hidden lab, secret panels, inscrutable butler, and greedy relatives with unusual talents. When Harper seems to be murdered,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Beast with Five Fingers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YGDqOwuJHlA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mddaxK5X1stcXrQSF1n1Ow6HFJD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Locals in an Italian village believe evil has taken over the estate of a recently deceased pianist where several murders have taken place. The alleged killer: the pianist's severed hand.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>She-Wolf of London</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/d1gDWKUCnfs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5dY768Xo62b0Jec7DFQjn6jELVV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Several murders have been committed in a London park and the victims have been savagely clawed about the throat. The police believe that a woman is a killer, and perhaps.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deadline at Dawn</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rKsoqvI195U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gMLxfUBSpLzMUss9yGdKUq3Qff3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Alex, a sailor on leave, recovers from a drink-induced blackout with a large sum of money belonging to Edna Bartelli, a b-girl who invited him home to ,fix her radio.,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Before I Go to Sleep</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NzpW6CsunDo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3UG2Pb122c7Va8MBtr1OHRB1YPh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman wakes up every day, remembering nothing as a result of a traumatic accident in her past. One day, new terrifying truths emerge that force her to question everyone.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Secret Beyond the Door.</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tvJRjPPQhhI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/f2CqQR8DF2I3DvmJFp5lRzRKD30.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this Freudian version of the Bluebeard tale, a young, trust-funded New Yorker goes to Mexico on vacation before marrying an old friend whom she considers a safe choice for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sorry, Wrong Number</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SDLfDfr4GIU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tkz4SJ93etwA7h0hPW1O0vwq11.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Leona Stevenson is sick and confined to her bed. One night, whilst waiting for her husband to return home, she picks up the phone and accidentally overhears a conversation between.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I Love Trouble</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/z_KIoGjidLg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bwraA2wqGEZXdCtrKSzqWTb210y.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A wealthy man hires a detective to investigate his wife's past. The detective (Franchot Tone) discovers that the wife had been a dancer and left her home town with an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Snake Pit</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1CBLJoNETqU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wLO2TVjM4UUQUwOq7RqfS8PCdMC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Virginia Cunningham finds herself in a state insane asylum.and can't remember how she got there. In flashback, her husband Robert relates their courtship, marriage, and her developing symptoms. The asylum.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Station West</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mZee6XQy0Ws\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j6WxGu37oAPStzJBw3UE0aoFqXR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dick Powell stars as Haven, a government private investigator assigned to investigate the murders of two cavalrymen. Travelling incognito, Haven arrives in a small frontier outpost, where saloon singer Charlie.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alias Nick Beal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5xS7B0vFXN8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/p06aQdoWyEkdfDERQ4XjLQLQc6k.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Righteous district attorney Joseph Foster's main goal in life is to rid his city of the gangsters infesting it. In order to be even more efficient in his war against.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thunder on the Hill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FA9TRHD3J8k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fHub0pS6UKkbhH9toSDWk05mtCz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Convicted murderess Valerie Carns (Ann Blyth) is being transported to Norwich to be executed when a flood strands her and her guards at a convent hospital. Nurse Sister Mary (Claudette.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 13th Letter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wK9qmzdjl6o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/60jelCYKH1rl1LIh2fO4GDTFmyY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Respectable citizens receive anonymous letters revealing their adulterous relationships.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Man in the Attic</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/a08TKkLq4C8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kTMpCivo3YD6yeCsBH3jGH7okee.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>London, 1888: on the night of the third Jack the Ripper killing, soft-spoken Mr. Slade, a research pathologist, takes lodgings with the Harleys, including a gloomy attic room for ,experiments.,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night People</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9_gU-EdW-lc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/akuo1zAPHoLswkf8sWnWkwPNRjC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Post WWII yarn about a young GI abducted by the Soviets in West Berlin and hauled off to the East. His recovery gets complicated as Colonel Steve Van Dyke (Peck).</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dangerous Crossing</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_yWBycLk2iE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7YmKUhedbu6RXQ1O5zkz8tyFoKN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young bride is set to begin her honeymoon aboard a luxury liner. Her happiness does not last when she finds that her husband has disappeared. Trouble is, no one.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Black Widow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eAfEmsIiynk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3Id4jDWT1mmC57oGNgseOxoYOQ5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A married Broadway producer is taken with an innocent young woman who wants to be a writer and make it on Broadway. He decides to take her under his wing,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bad Day at Black Rock</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qAm8uUJ-ok0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nFKCyy2MPTKr7xO6UhDLR3XzGxS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>From the time John J. Macreedy steps off the train in Black Rock, he feels a chill from the local residents. The town is only a speck on the map.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gorilla at Large</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tD2RvKHnlj8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ntTEGsCviXNM2dkXF8sEDeGTNFG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At a carnival called the Garden of Evil, a man is murdered, apparently by a gorilla.or someone in a gorilla suit.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Unguarded Moment</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y1wDws4TQ-k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sOqKA8uGK4EruBuPpcL9rV9lpD6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman has recently been murdered. A teacher at the nearby high school receives threatening notes from a student. Detective Graham is the only one who believes that she is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Haunted Strangler</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/I1foQ_x1wds\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sCv1SrUPN0NqHZKKMvMoAhAzCgO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A writer investigating the execution of a serial killer known as ,The Haymarket Strangler, 20 years previously begins to suspect that the wrong man might have been hanged. However, when.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Four Skulls of Jonathan Drake</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/erxKBBT0cvg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dPfXspC3cR3ivbdecCAcy8niCBc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jonathan Drake, while attending his brother's funeral, is shocked to find the head of the deceased is missing. When his brother's skull shows up later in a locked cabinet, Drake.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The House of the Seven Hawks</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/P-Fmb6apOAA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1uZlHxxfkxUC45mjdcbfuLkxbLE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film follows an American captain searching for sunken treasure who becomes entangled with criminals and is arrested by the Dutch police.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Take Aim at the Police Van</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BhTbyQkNfEE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ylN3kVHjCjzCwU3iq10K3Zebjlq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A sharpshooter kills two prisoners in a police van at night. The guard on the van is suspended for six months; he's Tamon, an upright, modest man. He begins his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 1,000 Eyes of Dr. Mabuse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KozsS5c_yJQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l7z5r1yAob8iEGADu8HN2FwNsPC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Reporter Peter Barter gets murdered while driving to his tv station. Commisioner Kras gets a phone call from clairvoyant Cornelius who saw Barter's death in a vision. But a dark.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Les Bonnes Femmes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qd3jxxf_OXg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9mUGt0z1PxPwnjn23xwEVivfvCq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ginette, Rita, Jacqueline and Jane try to find fulfillment and love in their lives. Rita has a fiancé whose family is obsessed with social distinction; Jane has a boy-friend in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Werewolf in a Girls' Dormitory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-bZpntzPJkM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/35tgQjabVZIHVUGFSHmwq4KerJA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The new science teacher Dr. Julian Olcott with a mysterious past arrives in an institutional boarding school for troublemaker girls. Along the night, the intern Mary Smith, who is blackmailing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Year at Marienbad</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yc6n2McMAnY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uv7OnxSzxY2h2kRCyaBK4ddpOi0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a huge, old-fashioned luxury hotel a stranger tries to persuade a married woman to run away with him, but it seems she hardly remembers the affair they may have.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dead Eyes of London</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MPyGYcICQ3c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hLU8BLYiRUTLwSt9myQpaADWCda.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Wealthy, heavily insured men are being murdered at an alarming rate. Scotland Yard investigates and finds clues that lead to a ring of blind men, led by a mysterious ,reverend.,</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Stop Me Before I Kill!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/12JLErYJzHI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tEbMLym8wHfRm6pVWsfg8qrgOqj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>High-strung race car driver Alan Colby is trying to recover from a serious head injury. Alan and his lovely new wife Denise go on vacation to the South of France.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sins of Rachel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/iaimbWDDnzw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ig29bDE5BkSdoYk7clE3sjb5maz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman is found murdered. The prime suspect is her timid son. She had an unhealthy fixation with him and he snapped when it became too unbearable. However, he swears.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Confessions of an Opium Eater</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6dcQNdw_j5o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/30WLWMqzrpzsJjrnXo8aXcbeEhc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Gilbert de Quincey is an early 19th-century adventurer involved with helping runaway slave girls and victims of a tong war in San Francisco. Garbed in black from head to toe,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Grim Reaper</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6Sptfiw4AC8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5vLDX6w3pwy6sUFlGkn0hPfKeQv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Near the Tiber river, in a Roman park, a prostitute was killed. The police tracks down people that were inside the park during that night. They are questioned and have.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Old Dark House</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sVyRYjJoZfc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5to7gDOX6jIk0VVOPCxyTvQ0BNi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American who sells cars in England receives a mysterious invitation from an old, eccentric millionaire to visit his house in which he lives with his twin brother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>High and Low</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wcALFnBJ54c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tgNjemQPG96uIezpiUiXFcer5ga.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An executive mortgages all he owns to stage a coup and gain control of the National Shoe Company, with the intent of keeping the company out of the hands of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Crimson Kimono</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NYjRjAKMxfY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/anNUxDXYV34AlRbAXRFb3CAh3K6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Classic, hard-to-find Sam Fuller pic is intriguing noir about two detective partners, one caucasian and one Japanese, who try to solve a complicated murder case. Unfortunately, trouble arises when along.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Black Torment</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/s--fCIDke4c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3sJpSEsl9UeAFLcYVky1DQDadAi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A lord returns to his manor with his new wife, to hear rumors that he had already secretly returned and had committed several murders. Has he lost his mind, or.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Night Walker</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GNCkeKjmSz0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r59Luf4njy2uY9D9DYqlLz2mfjh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A wealthy woman is terrorized by recurring dreams regarding her jealous, blind husband who supposedly burned to death in a recent fire. She tries to convince her attorney that the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tomorrowland (2015)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/P4k7XIdk7Vk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/69Cz9VNQZy39fUE2g0Ggth6SBTM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bound by a shared destiny, a bright, optimistic teen bursting with scientific curiosity and a former boy-genius inventor jaded by disillusionment embark on a danger-filled mission to unearth the secrets.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dark Intruder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/goFKNx1DkSA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/petzxxDop6hmOzoArFfgyRhZzXO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story takes place in 1890 San Francisco, where a series of gruesome murders attracts the attention of Brett Kingsford (Leslie Nielsen), a playboy detective with a secret crime lab,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Quiller Memorandum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FbLIbIXYxHc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/spMsYKX6WKn5e7wunLURHzwwpuB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two British agents are murdered by a mysterious Neonazi organization in West Berlin. The British Secret Service sends agent Quiller to investigate. Soon Quiller is confronted with Neonazi chief ,Oktober,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Kill Baby, Kill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lyqPlAzjrQw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nSxvQv5rT5VS1nh5xmzBSgO7u0W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dr. Eswai is called by Inspector Kruger to a small village to perform an autopsy on a woman who has died under suspicious circumstances. Despite help from Ruth, the village.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eye of the Devil</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/o_aF08u-eKE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8NmyAReQCqDIiPLQ2nYgtDyLWzW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vineyard owner marquis Philippe de Montfaucon is called back to his castle Bellenac because of another dry season. He asks his wife and children to remain in Paris, but they.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Man Vanishes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kt5OY7vnur8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xs63LhwO0nLmvRZ2GdzWAvx1pvZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Plastics salesman Oshima disappeared without a word to anyone, and has been missing for two years. Shohei Imamura and his crew follow Oshima's fiancé Yoshie and actor Shigeru Tsuyuguchi as.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Double Man</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-w8xf4vus9db1-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4Layn44z1sCDyFYthlJQP2q1m49.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following the death of his son, in a skiing accident in the Austrian Alps, the cold and emotion-less Dan Slater travels to Austria for the funeral. In the face of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Gruesome Twosome</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/REfLwWP4km8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eHzJBkfEV4fUVxAfspt1jOxBIc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mrs. Pringle and her son Rodney run a wig store which they stock by scalping young coeds who show up to look at the ,room for rent., Meanwhile at the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Young, the Evil and the Savage</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/veK6JEYLvXE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/s08qM4E2xhmsOOokZidLrpWlrOA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The corpses are piling up at St. Hilda's School for Girls, leaving top cop Michael Rennie with more than the usual suspects. Is the killer Mark Damon? Peeping Tom Luciano.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Magus</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/T7C_XmcJPjA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jj0rjPeUrcsoVMWW2WJg1qFscB2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An English teacher arrives on a sleepy Greek island to take up a vacant teaching post. The last man to hold the post committed suicide under mysterious circumstances. Slowly but.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Un soir, un train</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/I5TK1rKhTX8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jtHqWJz9EH37nPbxSL1oLwJS58w.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mathias is a Belgian linguist, living with French theatre producer Anne. After a quarrel about moral questions, they take a train to attend a congress. While Mathias sleeps, Anne disappears.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sadist Erotica</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Two Undercover Angels\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1A81yuSNfrKmNrvpaym1EOrpY0f.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Red Lips, are two female detectives trying to find missing models and dancers. A pop artist called Klaus Thriller and his werewolf-like assistant, Morpho, are the main suspects for the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/K4BfyrjOS1M\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lUV9CxWilp5nmWNEvWX5fopMesj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As Aunt Alice, Ruth Gordon applies for the job of housekeeper in the Tucson, Arizona home of widow Claire Marrable in order to find out what happened to a missing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fingers at the Window</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IDp5jMs2xtI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aXfyWrHSBCGPDlIlciftUEN82hm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The City of Chicago is gripped by an Axe Murderer. The streets are empty at night as there has been six murders and six people have been caught, but they.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Case for a Rookie Hangman</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-rsfur9a5x5bx-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fbGlqEJcNZjbwQ2IIy9D31xKTn3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lemuel Gulliver (Lubomír Kostelka) has had a car accident and continues his journey across the unknown countryside on foot. On the road he finds a dead rabbit dressed like a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Four Flies on Grey Velvet</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uzKAxXpgrGo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zVbpO45ZOZp1HXR6tzVnPUkpZ9I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Roberto, a drummer in a rock band, keeps receiving weird phone calls and being followed by a mysterious man. One night he manages to catch up with his persecutor and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Short Night of Glass Dolls</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DlMidH4tmvA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yT3nnuHNtexYw7yTDqaTscxfvWj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Greg Moore, an American journalist visiting Prague with his girlfriend Mira is found dead. However, he's actually only temporarily paralyzed, but the coroner fails to realize this and proceeds to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Lcoq6KDeOPI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pNl4t1S6Rxp5IBziWlqnKd7ii43.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A wealthy English lord is suffering a mental breakdown following the death of his red-headed wife, Evelyn, whom he feared was cheating on him. He tours local bars and dives,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fifth Cord</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ky-QyWAMWe8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xavb8iOvzo1VphFnxq25pUVsEEB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After a high-class party in Rome, there's an assault. The victim is injured but lives. Andrea, an investigative reporter who drinks too much, is assigned the story. Then, always on.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Case of the Scorpion's Tail</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8a5LNXAGY2A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tSf2dASiLwpG3TJD6zTxHwMYxcA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A plane explodes; one passenger is a London businessman who's insured for $1 million. His unfaithful wife is the beneficiary. The insurance agency arranges to pay, but also assigns their.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La bestia uccide a sangue freddo</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2463\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lJJwBxf6OgSyKypi8k75y6qeNxB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a psychiatric clinic for rich women, dies murdered, one after another, a nurse and two patients, while an arrow hit another woman. The guilty is a masked man. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cry Uncle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1uOXGX3Hj7g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5JfD1OyEohBUezSNiZa0ygO0vMx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Private detective takes on a case and gets mixed up in murder, sex and blackmail.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>See No Evil</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/e5Ao3Djg2Ig\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cFeuhRkE3dHLiy2SRHbtFFsy6Lf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young blind woman is pursued by a maniac while staying with family in their country manor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Seven Blood-Stained Orchids</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YkyVpN0LpYg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8zUt3zIQqXjQhCgsXEZASKoYTuA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A woman, a survivor of a failed murder attempt by a person dubbed ,The Half-Moon Killer, by the police, and her husband must find the connecting thread between herself, six.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Case of the Bloody Iris</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JE-AFyvCePw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gx7L1zHsKT8UBGkL7pHYw7NLdxz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Beautiful young model Jennifer Lansbury and her goofy friend Marilyn Ricci move into a swanky high-rise apartment after the previous tenant gets brutally murdered. Pretty soon Jennifer is being stalked.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La fille de Dracula</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7py-qBXA9mw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zbJHlTMVAxGSHJ3zCyGQHSYtfsw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young woman visits her gravely ill grandmother at the family estate. On her death bed, the old woman reveals to her granddaughter the family curse: they're all vampires. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>My Dear Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/toYhBrLeV3U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ppzWTmTtMzqqamR7jj1nFFjEFw1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following a mysterious decapitation (via mechanical digger) of an insurance investigator, Police Inspector Peretti is put onto the case. Slowly more people are found dead. a man supposedly commits suicide,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Knife of Ice</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/T5L5yCbsQBM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aeHHwJPzCY8iVJDIGboWvMfgwFr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As a thirteen year old, Martha Caldwell witnessed the death of her parents in a terrible railway accident. Barely surviving the tragedy herself, Martha was struck dumb due to the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Home for the Holidays</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9IKUrm_EbP8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iX8hyPXbkcUCnwqdiPeG3o1ECht.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four sisters reluctantly return home to the country to visit their ailing, embittered father over Christmas. Their father believes that his current wife has tried to poison him but Dr..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ecstasy of the Angels</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yq7p1XxqPVA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zQDeOGUx4qi55XFY2TPP4KI3BCU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The movie focuses on the actions of a revolutionary movement.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>What Have You Done to Solange?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XyR_zK242M0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qjwA6QM0xNi3ST7OZn93Lc2siyN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In London, the Italian gym teacher Enrico  Henry' Rosseni is having a love affair with his eighteen year-old student Elizabeth Seccles, who is the daughter of the owner of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Torture a Duckling</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/M_M3a3m6wOc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oVBbqz0e86M598fdY3cnk0LuMwd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the backward village of Accendura, the boy Bruno Lo Casio goes missing and the police inspector and the local commissioner and the village Captain Modesti investigate the case. When.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Aces Over Eights</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-u45ms66nqvet-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A home inspector gets more than he bargains for at a late night poker game.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Darkstar: The Interactive Movie</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-frxrmfay7f2o-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>You are Captain John O'Neil, awakening from suspended animation aboard a battle damaged starship on a lost mission. You've been asleep for over 300 years, a period of time that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In the Devil's Garden</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vM6ajIUdbjA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h2pREUTqesd91jsEG59aDwPj2Gd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After one schoolgirl is raped while taking a short cut through the local woods, and another is murdered in the same woods a few days later, the local police are.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wicked, Wicked</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XmEFYTYXTKU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/v9rdohao7BciF2KHZh1DL03ko2M.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A tongue-in-cheek psycho movie in ,Duo-vision., The entire feature employs the split-screen technique used in parts of Brian De Palma's ,Sisters, that same year. As a handyman at a seacoast.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blue Eyes of the Broken Doll</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AVxoiIZ8l0o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jKXIMBlCfG3Bp0tcxMPlmIXdqCZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An ex-convict, troubled by dreams that he strangles women, is hired as the caretaker on an estate owned by three very strange sisters. Soon after his arrival, a serial killer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The House on Skull Mountain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ykpOgPi0bQU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4D3Q9JbPeIasiyRaSaxwkcFfyJK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four cousins who have never met are invited by their Great-Grandmother Christophe to visit her mansion outside of Atlanta. When they arrive, they learn she has just died. They stay.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>What Have They Done to Your Daughters?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nav2M2r59lU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mChUYWCz4pnlhxNBwAFUQeAdx4x.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death Cruise</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Kl1QO7ljUIQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4BUSjsyJMWu6VnaDmolrlX1alnl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An ocean cruise is set for murder involving several couples, who believe they've won a trip. Unbeknownst to them they've all been lured on the cruise to be murdered by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Beast Must Die</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/050HRFf69Rg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/brKbkJo1WEVQghDduXODTqzb2lL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tom Newcliffe, a rich businessman and expert hunter summons six guests to his huge country estate which he has rigged up with video cameras and a high-tech security system. He.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Man on a Swing</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/51RSxYo1mhU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yas7z9HLudvFKUIQ4a78DICBDbQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A small-town police chief investigating a murder is offered help by a self-described psychic. However, when the chief discovers that the ,psychic, is in possession of information known only.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Christmas Rose</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-025vxud9c7lo-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uyJSgZOuGiVT2eIDi0gLtv5ZDRX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Tim (Kwok) is a defence attorney with a heart of gold. Refusing to be simply a hired gun for his clients, he quits his high-powered job to become a prosecutor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Sister's Nightmare</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-0ks4opjj581n-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lLEUX7tLrpJ8BZi3Z1bKo4fsys9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sibling rivalry returns to torment Jane, a young police officer, after her older sister Cass is released from the state hospital for the criminally insane. Cass begins showing an increasing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Taken: The Search for Sophie Parker</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-lrrov4968twn-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4Ydywqdlx9Vu7t9rtqHpuAWoXhv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>18 year-old Sophie Parker goes on spring break to Moscow with her friend Janie Hillman, daughter of the American Ambassador to Russia. When a reluctant Sophie is convinced by boy-crazy.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Platinum Data</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-gunssahyxq1v-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iPYpRhwn05JU3YXxF4cf5SJVoNg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a new system for mapping DNA called the Platinum Data is developed for all the residents of Japan, everyone is convinced it will create a better, saver society, free.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Brilliant Mistakes</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-92nrezz87oq3-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/e85UHg9SPiSdBLp2LatGgj4oZd3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Marcus Wright (Daniel Dambroff) is in love with Gabby (Elise McNamara). A devastating accident nearly kills her and renders her in a vegetative state. She can no longer walk or.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tractate Middoth</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-5hrn1m20mu0o-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/klQzX0hdntpISJxQKcESDHpNEX7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On his deathbed vicar Rant makes a secret confession to his niece Mary Simpson. Some twenty years later young librarian William Garrett is asked by elderly John Eldred to locate.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Satanico Pandemonium: La Sexorcista</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IbB0u8Fc0Sk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/elIsJIabW0qAs79bPM5mS7lFMXr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young nun is tempted by visions of forbidden sexual fantasies to cross over to Satan.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nothing But the Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hZUteqiZsvE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fKxzLnl2avoORTQQjwltclVLE3A.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Already three trustees of the Van Traylen fund have died during the last months, looking like suicides. However after a mysterious accident of a bus with the last three trustees.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Más negro que la noche</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DdESttCajgA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2zkjISGfzqSEJag7Gzl9IhBk06A.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When four women move into an old house left by one woman's aunt, strange things begin to happen. Bizarre voices, visions of ghosts, and mysterious noises lead them to discover.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>L'uomo senza memoria</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1zk0trXrxjc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cAjuzmO6Kawx1XrBwG8h6hqFN8M.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Luc Merenda plays a man who as a result of a car crash is suffering from amnesia and is trying to learn about his past, then a menacing individual accuses.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lords of London</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JDMr-iryM0E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w1Xn9zfGCLHaqWjadAUqCmmnNyo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>London gangster, Tony Lord, is the son of the notoriously ruthless, Terry Lord (Ray Winstone). After a standard shake down goes awry, Tony must confront his father's past in order.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The House of the Laughing Windows</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gb559bhuJjc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aB4eJPAsR8q2ughPRVSk0OezBJS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Stefano, a young restorer, is commissioned to save a controversial mural located in the church of a small, isolated village.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death at Love House</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/taDBzKf59J0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hhUJyxaV9nXQU0mhmfN9kJVU66O.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Donna and Joel Gregory are researching a book about long dead Hollywood goddess Lorna Love. They are staying at Lorna's estate while interviewing old ,friends, of Lorna. Joel, whose father.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hitch Hike to Hell</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_WL14gV6iI8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3s0vurNXymlJBP551mJMf64x847.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Howard is a mild-mannered young man who drives a truck for a commercial laundry. He's also a mother-obsessed psycho who picks up young female hitchhikers, rapes them and kills them..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Watch Me When I Kill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9h1ErrJT0rQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1aYokK2YVV96k8hGGPn5O1fbFjx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A pharmacist is murdered, and a woman happens to see the culprit leave the scene. She soon finds herself being stalked by the killer, and when her boyfriend tries to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Psychic</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_waxbH2oECc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4U8UMrxRbFVNmmc4Ym8CH8KY5mi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A clairvoyant woman, inspired by a vision, smashes open a section of wall in her husband's home and finds a skeleton behind it. Along with her psychiatrist, she seeks to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hotel Fear</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9MZ2Fz-l4LU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Y1CZXcCd3DG3Bza4Laeb0gxaIS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, young Rosa and her mother run a hotel in the Italian countryside, mourning over the death of her dead father. When the mother dies under mysterious.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Late Show</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BlVf6HZAbJg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6eJqMvv3gSVSKePQgqjRa0ORVoH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ira Wells is an aged retired Los Angeles based private investigator, who is slightly overweight, needs to wear a hearing aid, has a bum leg and an ulcer-laden stomach, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Clan of Amazons</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kfQWffVvPG8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uax8gRqNoGpXeneuPTStmLCwrXr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Swordsman and Enchantress</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VBxf7o9OcvI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ddlp7BLSvhLl3Iw7bNwrKnxXuU2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Master kung-fu choreographer Tang Chia leads the king and queen of Shaw Brothers' swordplay, Ti Lung and Lily Li, to the amazing ,Deer Sword, and escape from the insidious maze-like.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Legend of the Bat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xnnE4Y6OcR0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dQ9EXmcxnjGxe1i9cvAOWGzGti3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Once again we follow the ultimate playboy sword master, Chu Liu Hsiang, and his faithful friend, Yi Tien Hung, on another amazing adventure in Southeastern China. This time, our heroes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bermuda Triangle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/e3i7Yw_lrMU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aGzzVPJFbMmqhBGba9Y4I60ImQe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The passengers and crew of a boat on a summer cruise in the Caribbean stray near the famed Bermuda Triangle, and mysterious things start happening.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Toolbox Murders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CPt5h49SNc0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yUvEmwJnysnpmFm7A6S9mlaMH7X.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A lunatic runs around an apartment complex, apparently home only to attractive flight attendants with a tendency towards exhibitionism. While there, the lunatic tries to kill all the tenants with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murder by Decree</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IIVbRyiqROM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zRXOiNnJM9BnO29Jpx7dAaFXvCZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sherlock Holmes investigates London's most infamous case, Jack the Ripper. As he investigates, he finds that the Ripper has friends in high places.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Double McGuffin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4r15ptBkw0s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6Y1dzxJgdz48ptnB1oU2aahlT1j.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Some school kids stumble across a briefcase full of money, when they go back for it, they find a body instead. When they bring the police, neither is there, and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La tía Alejandra</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bO8FjkULpQ4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nKdSZ7QXHenpVo3o2iplC9769K4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Old aunt Alejandra goes to live with a Mexican middle-class family; she's bitter and the children tease her and make her life miserable, but the old woman is truly a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>To All a Goodnight</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/roWwH4ucDVk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kMle0V1ugmjkPXubTRb0u12Sa6a.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's Christmas break at the Calvin Finishing School for Girls, and the students are planning a big party while the president of the school is away. A group of boys.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Iron Chain Fighter</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dcSZ1W5Szlw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/53lx3aipVlpyciGuVwpkWLOiqyQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes and Dr. Watson: The Hound of the Baskervilles</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WaN5JAofop4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/q7OLbf8f6PAKgZ655V19T2GTI28.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Sir Charles Baskerville is found dead in his country house, Dr James Mortimer asks Sherlock Holmes for help to save Sir Henry Baskerville, the only known heir, from the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night School (1981)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SSXHeY1wKT8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yYQMLCFlgMYZANElS2kAMG1HG9Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Boston police detective investigates a series of gruesome decapitations of various college coeds commited by a helmeted, black-leather clad serial killer which leads him to suspect a well known.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bloody Moon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/g43AWZ6CZh0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mBoJUYD08K0im1wND6abtUy3ggU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Miguel, a young man with a horribly disfigured face, goes on a rampage at a masquerade party and rapes a girl. He then brutally hacks up the young woman with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Seven Dials Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6kEw2Wy7tk0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nHwXT1X4MwssG954XcCuYrOEMXC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lady Eileen  Bundle' Brent a pert, aggressive young aristocrat insinuates herself into a series of murders, stolen state secrets, and a mysterious secret society.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>El crack</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8JFuUpmExU8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8hV1RWfZZEhlf5MFe8pp86cBujw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Private detective Germán Areta gets a terminally ill client who wishes to see his long lost, runaway daughter before he dies. But when Areta starts looking into case, that leads.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Place to Hide</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/LovenuK3tIc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fVHyCce8YNDGBNX9FAks7ocrIDI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Amy is the Mannings only daughter. After the death of her rich father, she lives together with her stepmother. Recently she sees a man in black following her, waiting for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shen Sheng Yi</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-RChLD81zCA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8mCWM5XyF9toAPMoKRJMvjI3hmx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bastard Swordsman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xYykcbuJkBU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zIpnFqGQDYXaSrZjuB7Jg6dQZH9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hsu Shao-chiang stars as a veritable ,Spider-Swordsman, , master of the ,Silkworm Style, , in this eye-filling, mind-bending martial arts phantasmagorical which truly warrants the description: ,unforgettable.,</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 4th Man</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mUJRmw5b2oA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hn0gqb6JUKPcXOhb8FZBl2LYMAP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The morbid Catholic writer Gerard Reve who is bisexual, alcoholic and has frequent visions of death is invited to give a lecture in the literature club of Vlissingen. While in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Open Till Christmas</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/q9oBgGk3VLg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aq1gQXAUq8zma4dPxgbgtC2PEt5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A murderer is running loose through the streets of London, hunting down men dressed as Santa and killing them all in different, and extremely violent, fashions. Inspector Harris has decided.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Girls Nite Out</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6ccdJKfei_o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mT9mi8u2rK66M5TE0XdglBdxZLs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The day after a huge party a scavenger hunt is held. Every college-age kid in town is out for the grand prize. One-by-one they are all dispatched by a killer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Agatha Christie's Miss Marple: At Bertram's Hotel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2_j-A8t0xyA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jUFqfmqaaFGPBMilollCoDJUpoC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Miss Jane Marple is staying at an elegant hotel from her childhood compliments of her nephew Raymond. Also there is international adventurer Bess Sedgwick and Lady Selena Hazy (Joan Greenwood.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Track 29</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/C71Df240VZE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3V9PpZyxg9vzs6VW1vTrZ6x5Rvi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A doctor's wife tires of his obsession with model trains, and spends her days wondering about the son she gave up for adoption at birth. While eating at a roadside.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Agatha Christie's Miss Marple: Nemesis</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Miss Marple: Nemesis (Extract) 1987\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zcPVRQcVyMWFWaaZ9bIB3JGOvGN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Miss Marple receives a most interesting request from Mr. Jason Rafiel, with whom she'd struck an acquaintance some years before. He would like her to solve a crime but, does.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Perry Mason: The Case of the Sinister Spirit</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/N8RwApF_I9E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yLZFw78zMHtIiEkvNLjgWKD3ITU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jordan White, a publisher friend of Perry, is called to a hotel where a guest, famous horror writer David Hall, has cleared out the hotel for a weekend and has.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Killing Birds</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/g4K1cXNY3YE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/81p1Ze1irjTpeTQozng1FAfhF2u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In Louisiana, a soldier returning from Vietnam finds his wife in bed with her lover and he kills them both as well as a couple of friends, but he is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mask of Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/j7tuSGooZfc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ghqcwisEcCLRVCul9Gcb3MNJInx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a Canadian village are women being killed by a psychopath. Chief Rich and Inspector McLane have no clue until McLane shoots a suspicious man. Now the killing seems to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Everybody Wins</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tbSzvvT056Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cLWz9PszZoKLOerQgwIrZ8ST6o6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A seeming good Samaritan (Debra Winger) hires a private detective (Nolte) to prove a teen sitting in prison on a murder charge is innocent. His investigation discovers deep corruption in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Till There Was You</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7TH95S9RJFw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qd6YjYoOEvGDkAkzpYomI4oBGMI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>New York sax player arrives on the island nation of Vanuatu to find his missing brother. He learns that his brother had teamed up with a powerful shady foreigner and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Double Threat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2IGh4T9p8gk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9HdfyNDP5ddcwgpxLoQj2KjayrX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A former movie star, Monica Scott, returns to the big screen along with younger boyfriend, Eric Cline, after a long absence. Monica is very jealous of the attention Eric gives.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Massively Mixed-Up Middle School Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0So1yPDSUjA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ibTD4SjT9DjiYH0qcaXMQnMldZj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When the ultimate prank sends their principal under water, it's up to Everett, Alyssa and Riley to put their super detective skills to the test, catch the perp, and save.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La Cérémonie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5eIiJksgwy0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/13ERRUQYR5Mz6YChJEH0RlPpaBN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The upper-class owner of a gallery, Catherine Lelievre, hires the efficient and quiet maid Sophie to work in the family manor in the French countryside. Her husband Georges Lelievre, who.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shinjuku Triad Society</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/odZx8N-veHA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dQIB8k6RLIKqMwSMfORO3aREPHh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Amidst a Chinese and Japanese mafia war, a lawyer for the Chinese mob finds a rift forming between him and his corrupt police office brother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Apartment</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/49L3Y3cP8io\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1sqrQdQTn8jKLhUcPKfRVj639zA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Max is on his way to Tokyo. He lives in Paris and likes to flirt but has decided to get married. By chance, he seems to have seen Lisa, his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Damien's Seed</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/p3wzNdEGlPw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iFjX67a20P0y0heL5FA4vgzpQaZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The mysterious Jane Janzen hires private detective Barry Haven to find her younger runaway sister Jessica who has been missing for the last three months. He travels to a remote.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Fever</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/a5l6MbXu6AQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4aytLuIicECojFIJCqaLk1fj1rf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hirata finds himself canceling his vacation plans to Hawaii when his grandfather reminds him of his duty to his parents. Seven years earlier, Hirata's parents had been killed in an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Illusions of Sin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mFFkf0hNgVw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9OuWmxiHowmh1aRosWPEohisTlS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a mysterious incident nearly claims the life of a beautiful actress during rehearsals for her upcoming play, everyone deduces that her ambitious understudy, Elizabeth (Mellara Gold), is the guilty.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Herod's Law</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qx7Ylt-Bwwc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4dQ7kVzH11hzZH5nOlGx0PVTqwA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After the corrupt former Mayor is killed by the peasants, poor janitor Juan Vargas is appointed new Mayor of a desert town in central Mexico. Although he tries to bring.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Monkey's Mask</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JNNp6vMUomk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aGcp6THPH0xdnWePO54SBNxv464.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jill Fitzpatrick is a 28-year old, street-smart, out-of-work private investigator wishing she wasn't celibate. Eager for the taste of adrenaline, she accepts a job investigating the disappearance of Mickey, a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Werckmeister Harmonies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nSY7rxr0n04\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7Hqy3GDNl5irPiDlBEKrJD02Qkb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This story takes place in a small town on the Hungarian Plain. In a provincial town, which is surrounded with nothing else but frost. It is bitterly cold weather ,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mysterious Object at Noon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Csg4v6Lzxmw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pVq8GT23E0kv6MUNf5IGMtbcrNT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This film is an experimental mix of documentary and fiction. The film crew travels from the Thai countryside to Bangkok, asking the people they encounter along the way to continue.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>3 A.M.</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DblJJIME5s4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/30W7c30zrpPO50T9Fb9KX6jiAU7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The feature film directing debut of Spike Lee protege Lee Davis takes the viewer into the world of taxi drivers. Developed in the Sundance Laboratory, this film offers dove-tailing stories.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Skeletons in the Closet</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OVL-gCiH0gQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vNqK70BVwUARFqrNmDKGbvkP238.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A father (Williams) suspects his son (Jackson) to be a murderer.or is he just paranoid and trying to cover up his own past which involves his wife being killed in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Body</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FZllO9w0DKA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ip3rWK8wBddpfmaBW86KlJ0gEiP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An ancient skeleton has been discovered in Jerusalem in a rich man's tomb. Colouration of the wrist and leg bones indicates the cause of death was crucifiction. other signs, include.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Detective Conan: The Phantom of Baker Street</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/B5JKxAx-H0s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lIOaU8bFC5coM1A7c64NXGIXje4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hiroki Sawada was a 10-age kid who got into a US college and even graduated. One day, Hiroki finished A.I. Noah-sue-ark and suicide to end his life. 2 years later..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Talk to Her</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cWuMYPOYTAw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/klsBB1YEGRyC7YjiLYCKIqkU6pY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After a chance encounter at a theater, two men, Benigno and Marco, meet at a private clinic where Benigno works. Lydia, Marco's girlfriend and a bullfighter by profession, has been.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Unborn But Forgotten</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/w94AKwEM_hw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/f83U6sF1BU00K9JdHzohOX4BTYZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A website is seemingly killing every woman who views it within fifteen days. While investigating the phenomenon, a female reporter begins an investigation that leads to the discovery of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Epoch: Evolution</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/DLuarvSvQa8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t5LI90R01XXD5S2ytQ9pANvWZJ9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>10 years since the the first Alien object called Torus arose, two more have risen. The first torus changed the worlds view dramatically not just political but even on a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Memories of Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pLEFn55bpR0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gawnVe9cFowdoDLo9Pok12NTw39.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1986, in the province of Gyunggi, in South Korea, a second young and beautiful woman is found dead, raped and tied and gagged with her underwear. Detective Park Doo-Man.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I'm Not Scared</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/atLGsOg6lBY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aNWNAwuGmTkRdVF9tg5RA0UssWo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While playing outside one day, nine-year-old Michele discovers Filippo, who is chained to the ground at the bottom of a hole. Michele witnesses town baddie Felice nearby and suspects something.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Big Empty</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JlPJNlW4PT0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9UYDD0sxoP4xPhRGNDRcrT3Nia7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Would be-Hollywood actor John Person always considered his bizarre neighbor Neely a conspiracy theory nut-case. Still he accepts a simple task to wipe out his over $27,000 debt: delivering a.</summary>
</item>
<title>Trance (2013)</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/gb0MRNSdj8o/\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cr1vVtymoiW23ETEycUgiAZYMur.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A fine art auctioneer mixed up with a gang, joins forces with a hypnotherapist to recover a lost painting. As boundaries between desire, reality and hypnotic suggestion begin to blur,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Detective Conan: Crossroad in the Ancient Capital</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vN48ht9hVlk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dkYzPHCkTLTf3QQSWJ1Z3UBd1SX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Genjibotaru thief gang members keep getting killed recently. Each member hold a Yoshitsune story. Sannoh Temple got its important Buddha statue Yakushi stolen for 8 years. it's getting to be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Jiminy Glick in Lalawood</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nERZw-Uvb5k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hrku1M0IrcWOYSB1ugUvAGfauby.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,La La Wood, follows the legacy of Jiminy Glick, first introduced on ,The Martin Short Show,, who went on to get (non)-critical acclaim for his talk show ,Primetime Glick,, where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Silver City</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/iTiIi3x-N4s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cFikozlPUtD5i3U9ajhMyj7RT2T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set against the backdrop of a mythic ,New West,, a satire that follows grammatically-challenged, ,user-friendly, candidate Dicky Pilager, scapegrace scion of Colorado's venerable Senator Jud Pilager, during his gubernatorial campaign..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Art of the Devil</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cCmXwD0vVDw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rxLlAzwihpsUQQXAbNVmKg2peBZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Boom, pregnant from an affair, is told by her lover to leave him and his family alone. Enraged, she goes to a witch doctor and has him use black magic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Red Lights</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hwEcwJ8BcNc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jdCpRWfPj3xt6LvSuXFyDYiidjF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Antoine and Helene drive to South France to return their kids from a holiday camp. The traffic is dense and the atmosphere growingly tense; he is an alcoholic and becomes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Walk on Water</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_ftZhiogzTY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5BH0k5pauAqywpr4NL9nKYcKC6O.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Eyal, an Israeli Mossad agent, is given the mission to track down and kill the very old Alfred Himmelman, an ex-Nazi officer, who might still be alive. Pretending to be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Saving Emily</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kk3kYigqVLY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7F9xEbsziEbTdW6mlrhUtZ3CYHm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Cheryl discovers that her daughter Emily has leukemia, she's forced to ask her ex-husband, Kurt, a shady ex-con, for a bone marrow donation that could save her child's life..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Maid</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-wokGQxKoAw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/deckm7MGSFOeezFARupbjIjUBn0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Every year, for thirty days during the lunar seventh month, the Chinese believe that the gates of hell are thrown open. Vengeful spirits or hungry ghosts wander among the living,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blood Deep</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TVKiUpWbx9s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nF0Ikn1IYl56uFncVwk1j3NF0y3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A reunion of childhood friends turns deadly when one of the guests unwittingly admits to murder. In 1985 a missing boy's charred remains are found in a vacant field. Nineteen.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Toybox</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/paIHksP9Ia8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dQcztG9sQg4V9IAKUYgspANOddY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It all began so innocently for two children growing up in the deepest countryside, their imaginations set ablaze by a book on local myths and legends. Berenice convinces her younger.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Blood Rain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7YRkTWamEVU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/A9J9iLiVODbMUZ2v4dGNsZ1zRlz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Blood Rain tells the story of a slew of grisly murders plaguing a small, fairly isolated island village. However, it's not just the mounting death toll that's causing residents to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Separate Lives</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XDD3SQt1ZuE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lVTcDb7VJQwgoZ6mN9DYxON2iBh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The ex-cop Tom Beckwith has just quit his police job in order to study psychology. But his professor, Lauren Porter, is more interested in his criminology abilities than in his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fine Art of Love: Mine Ha-Ha</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3GBgL-7Om8U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hWPY3qfspqYJxrqUOMwOzTdrOBt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Laughing Water , Mine Ha-Ha, is based on ,Mine-Haha or Physical Education of Young Girls, by German author Frank Wedekind (Spring Awakening, Lulu, Pandora's Vase). Thuringia, Germany, in the early.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Kyaa Kool Hai Hum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1933\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cRJg2pniB4zVa1B0MZ6lGaiBtLJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Karan Pandey and Rahul are two friends who work in a fashion designers office, and live in a rented apartment. When they are unable to pay the rent, they are.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Graveyard of Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SebzphKm_yU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wjrcb8EcRdTIxB0LTZFlM7ivKwD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A reporter from a small regional newspaper investigates a waste dump in which the military have been testing Infectious Diseases, it's not long before the Zombies are free and Killing,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Tell</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/c_262cH4ytk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eI59BiRLqIp9RD45L1by0grch1r.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sabina has a regular life. She is satisfied with her job and her love for Franco. Lately nightmares start disturbing her, and almost in the same time she discovers to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Stendhal Syndrome</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-fov1qzcdfoui-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hYGuGcIOBG4RRucfRB1m3PJLq3M.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Anna Manni is a policewoman trying to capture a vicious serial rapist and killer. The problem is that she suffers from ,Stendhal's syndrome,, a psychosomatic disease that gives her dizziness.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ever Since the World Ended</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CDYvNJHj8Sg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nMVjZMPZmx5iMYNyXCzBINuNtUX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Twelve years ago, a plague swept through, wiping out most of the population; in San Francisco, only 186 people remain. Two of them use jury-rigged batteries to power a camera.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I Know What You Did Last Summer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lEWv70QwU5o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cruOfvjIqMTbOQxld8SpM8OzVnf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After an accident on a winding road, four teens make the fatal mistake of dumping their victim's body into the sea. But exactly one year later, the dead man returns.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Follow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/J6rywKwJ0vw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/UJFieHAHnggFANaAi5d3nTR7eP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Driver is now spying on a celebrity's wife suspected of adultery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Domestic Disturbance</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bIwcZYlFR2o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2rD850CRE2kX9ZVFdkSTUccnpYj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Susan Morrison is getting married to wealthy industrialist Rick Barnes. Danny, her teenage son with ex-husband Frank, isn't happy about this; he stows away in Rick's car one night, planning.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death in Granada</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uRAffItBV78\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w9bGU5XsuSDE83J97r2Ciphd5ZO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A journalist (Esai Morales) starts an investigation into the disappearance of famed poet and political agitator, Garcia Lorca (Andy Garcia), who disappeared in the early days of the Spanish Civil.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Like Minds</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cmDNEiS7VlY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8PrNqUwC7S8jiwTcOCc0PWapz6l.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The forensic psychiatric Sally Rowe is called by Detective Martin Mackenzie to analyze the profile of the teenager Alex Forbes, who was found in a train station holding the body.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Unseeable</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2385\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9b0lAQBJF6ZD45huWibvcEglUSs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a pregnant country girl leaves home to search for her missing husband, she finds refuge at a mysterious estate whose inhabitants hold more secrets than she may wish to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sunrise (2014)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/93366061710\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rqqmBDa8ZWmd0OvKQlOPSXwRWFJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Inspector Joshi is a grieving father searching for his daughter Aruna, kidnapped years ago when she was six. In his despair, life converges with a recurring dream in which Joshi.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lost Souls</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uS2b8yZ_1cI&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2uUwgNEgpTtkNAIUBqMsyHD6FjD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Victor Robinson moves into a new country home with his family. Their son Jesse, discovers an old Edison invention. When they turn on the machine, they start to hear kids.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>29 February</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZXoxiX8Yv4s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/32ODRdywclFllruz8IJS7awiNpU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ji-yeon, a tollgate ticket girl, is frightened by a mysterious black car, which hands over a bloodstained ticket as a fee at midnight. Her fear deepens after her colleague, Jong-sook,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Colic: The Movie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AamTERibvqs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u6MUuYgGLjToOB18e9s4SbPsxpb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Colic is a syndrome found in infants, which causes infants to cry continuously for hours. The reason behind this illness is usually credited by medical expects to a number of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Films to Keep You Awake: The Baby's Room</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/doTD0AmfHok\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3U6F8njE7OF8bRPKtKtrP5kwneL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In Spain, the sports journalist Juan has a perfect life with his wife Sonia: they have just had a baby and moved to an old house that needs to be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Victim</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6SkMIpACk0w\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rI8qHrcgjeXk7UaNOwZrSuD41fL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ting, an actress for murder illustration is hired to simulate a real-life murder case of Min, a former Miss Thailand who was brutally killed. Afterwards, Ting can feel a strange.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Wives He Forgot</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/L6FgFtFmtX0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/61Ca5LJl64dbm3ns6FgiryR3wWg.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Into the small law offices of unlucky-in-love Charlotte St. John stumbles a handsome stranger, bloodied and battered, suffering amnesia. The good Samaritan, she cares for him, nurses him to health.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Her Fatal Flaw</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SLtpiYl9s7g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gz2Vrqj8V2xqyPQYeYwhkURvxoo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A lawyer defends her fiancée in court despite the objections of her friends, mentors and colleagues.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Film Noir</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MeCGri4Ahgk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qjYyMa5ZYoyln4EQtwCqduaLhGI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Private detective Sam Ruben's clever plan falls apart with the onset of amnesia. Everyone is trying to kill him and he doesn't know why. The classic film noir milieu now.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Suicide Song</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PT2vVgmwb10\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xE34oCnGZKeOZZKwi1qwA3llOcQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Anzu Natsuno is the leader of the triathlon team of her all-girl High School. One evening she hear a voice singing and following the voice, she finds her close friend.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Seventeen and Missing</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OjsTiosHobQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xGDu2ctYLJ1JEUhXFc6HoO0VbtM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Emilie Janzen has always had a strange intuition and talent for seeing the truth in people. But what Emilie didn't see coming is the disappearance of her 17-year-old daughter, Lori..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lethal Vows</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QmwuyAOw5kQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ricra0h7JEWwPDimmc8X8CVlb8p.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This psychological thriller, based on a true story, is about a seemingly upstanding, caring husband and father (Ritter) who is accused of foul play by his ex-wife regarding the mysterious.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Love of Siam</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jKjj9AYJe5E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/srujeIH7q4xcP70o53FVOTlHd2V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two young boys are best friends living quiet family lives in Bangkok. Their lives are disrupted when one boy's older sister goes missing on a jungle trip. The shattered family.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>My Kid Could Paint That</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/K5YH9zwleFM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/keqeIgHe3fkt12eRPRUj5Y3TLLx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four year old Marla Olmstead from Binghamton, New York became the sensation of the art world for her abstract artwork, which have sold for thousands of dollars per piece. The.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mad Detective</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rotL2JpoBcI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nJSc6rVPmi5obS0EFGb0idOJ8nS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A rookie cop teams up with a former detective with a supernatural gift to hunt down a serial killer.</summary>
</item>



<item>
<title>Ouija Board</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jNGGrvFha8o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1UjL11z04HjrEnL7v8m4a6KEdHC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Yu-jin and her blind mother move to a small village from Seoul. On her first day at the new school, Yu-jin gets picked on by her classmates. Along with other.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Monsieur N.</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fkGYVHlYJIk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/djrEmcYPtwkeYyZ1ww2sP2plZH2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>How can Napoleon, the man of war and pioneering military strategist, meekly accept being locked up on a storm-lashed rock in the middle of the Atlantic ocean? What system of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fermat's Room</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SJ9y4SCLvNc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3mGy3Lkd7FDcF3QN6PQDgxyd6Iy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four mathematicians who do not know each other are invited by a mysterious host on the pretext of resolving a great enigma. The room in which they find themselves turns.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Perfect Assistant</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rR4EiUSoCqQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/IkdnoGRcgKGESR660Eq4k66TQH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>CEO David Wescott greatly appreciates his trusted office assistant Rachel Parsons's efforts to help out in the Wescott household too when he loses his wife, leaving his child semi-orphaned after.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Inju: The Beast in the Shadow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JByofDeD_c4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3FQIqrK959eYv1a12An8dtNRHRl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The writer and college professor, Alexandre Fayard, researches and gives lectures about the gruesome literary work of the mysterious Japanese writer Shundei Oe, considered by him to be the master.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Song of Good</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dtO4HY5yghU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7d2PBvnzWRheHdH4qEtpnWD99uF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Song Of Good is the story of 28 year old Gary Cradle's struggle to redeem himself after committing a horrific crime. During a desperate burglary to get money for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Six Sex Scenes and a Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZNJ_GIzd2LQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a7VysPcCi5zCtSeZYw2ilLzE6YR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Nick's made poor choices professionally and personally. A man feared and envied by many, he's lived a life seduced by crime, money, beautiful women, and burlesque. Now he wants out.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tumbler</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QmMKd3pnygc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Secrets of the Summer House</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KHyUwbBbrag\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ydlCAgBWk2Oph1vGhN97e02Zsme.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>George Wickersham, a top Boston lawyer, returns to his ancestral summer house on a private island in rural Maine. Due to bad memories from his childhood, he has a dislike.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>1920 (2008)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5Mgj2nMoKN4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hZZg9wlAM3HydAgXpI8IaTGamcM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A devotee of Bhagwan Shri Hanuman, Arjun Singh Rathod is in love with Lisa, a Christian, who was sired by an Indian mother and Caucasian father, runs into problems with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Terribly Happy</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qkOUtxgwJJ8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uxsYNU26eVIqhPVKmLfXyxni7Ms.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Robert Hansen is a cop in Copenhagen who makes a mistake, is remanded for therapy, then assigned to a small town in South Jutland, where cows and problems disappear into.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bracelet of Bordeaux</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TKdeDpJM8is\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l50OjF3EXomGAa2zkW4W4SHpUP5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Someone is dognapping the canine citizens of Chem City, Texas! Two pre-teen girls overcome danger and conspiracies as they set out to solve the crime and administer justice with the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In a Spiral State</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ebPEc9IGT4Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5zh8nPC6JX0B9e3AXxQO5OVBd19.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the city of Los Angeles, millions of lives intersect everyday, but each individual is still isolated from the whole. A number of strange incidents occur to four men and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Noroi: The Curse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ilHmpETJgZ0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7qUFiNE8kWcptWGxiXgLLKY5iVI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary filmmaker explores seemingly unrelated paranormal incidents connected by the legend of an ancient demon called the ,kagutaba.,</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nebyt dnesni</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8I0uDuKd11M\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iuqX9XD46e2ZEzI2wdGEfWdAQFZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Gerard, Mara and Jiri are addicted to heroin. The trio's struggle to kick the habit is more complicated than they expected. And then something happens that changes everything.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La belle dame sans merci</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Xza6Xx73Gvc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>1819. A shipwreck survivor, the Navigator, recalls the events that brought him here. The Navigator is challenged by fellow survivor, the Doctor, into pursuing his true passion , art. While.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Prey</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/m5w7Nu1YjEI&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nR9Gqb50QB226nX7Npe2F9Am2tL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jannicke, Morten Tobias, Eirik, Mikal and Ingunn are on a snowboarding vacation in Jotunheimen. They are forced to take shelter in an abandoned hotel when Morten Tobias breaks his leg.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Haunting Villisca</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cvEiRvRh9WM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Professor David Salt's guilty secrets draw him to the fabled Town of Villisca, past and present collide as he is driven to help the trapped spirits, and to seek his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sleeping Murder</title>
<link>http://www.gorillavid.in/embed-9rfkd0yalnwi-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Miss Jane Marple is asked to help Gwenda, a wealthy young woman who has bought a house on the English coast, only to experience disturbing visions. Thanks to Miss Marple's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Prime Suspect 7: The Final Act</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-09lrm33iiiv3-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1xtLOiSJRLTdkOawoU6MDhYMUgU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Helen Mirren returns for the final time as Jane Tennison in the long-awaited Prime Suspect 7. Retirement looms for Detective Superintendent Tennison, but as her career draws to a close,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death Water</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XhEnujr5otw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6R66ZGz6UlotQdbEY6zF33TAAeu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Newspaper correspondent Kyoko Togakure (Haruka Igawa) visits a nursing home in the outskirts of Tokyo. She finds the dead body of a resident. It was an apparent suicide. He's holding.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Psycho IV: The Beginning</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/6MlMSXnh2Us/Psycho.IV.The.Beginning.1990.720p.BluRay.x264-%5BYTS.AG%5D.mp4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qE0Ah7xVvJeehVQUrL9WGFb6Pm1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Norman Bates returns for this prequel, once more having mommy trouble. This time around he is invited to share memories of mom with a radio talk show host, but the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The China Lake Murders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cpp5G8Xcezw&feature=plcp\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zLsHe8wYPTgtkNaz0htahaPBtHb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A small town sheriff (Tom Skerritt) has his suspicions in a murder case which involves a rogue cop who goes on a murder spree. Contains mild sexual situations and violence.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Crash: The Mystery of Flight 1501</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ZSCTtjhDxo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ihTtV0dzpo5zdxisMXBKOK9UHJe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a passenger plane crashes after a bomb scare, there are many unanswered questions, which can only be attributed to ,pilot error,. The pilot's wife, Diane Halstead, is convinced her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Temptation of St. Tony</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/C6U3fT2SBtI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8rRclVwreWrKf0NShxdHSlrC0BC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A mid-level manager who develops an aversion to being ,good, finds himself confronting the mysteries of middle-age and morality as he loses grasp of what was once his quiet life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Pornography: A Thriller</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CDIdSOliU7c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mCGN1OIP0PwrT5FBNHJlW25z2Ac.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A gay porn star's mysterious disappearance becomes an obsession for both a writer and another adult film star, leading them into dark supernatural corners that were never meant to be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nemesis Game</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0G9AHi0NRNM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vftpsSgzfqC3pgyDp2Gq1OL0ml.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sara Novak is an introverted college student with a few skeletons in her closet. Shying away from classmates, she prefers to spend time with Vern, an older comic store owner.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Creek Manor</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RqMwmVzhUB8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yIfGja2k9UCOm1ed8yiz9VKaJsE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Wanting to escape city life for the countryside, New Yorkers Cooper Tilson (Quaid), his wife Leah (Stone) and their two children move into a dilapidated old mansion still filled with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Slim Susie</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-pkxW5SpBkI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zK55cwwdS3THvfSgUaZMQsExtq7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Erik has to return to the rural village where he grew up, when he is told that his younger sister Sussie has disappeared without a trace. On returning, Erik gets.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dragon Head</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jj_mSvn6dME\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9uhJitxCUlA3svgiB2miRLpvWbU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A teenage boy wakes up and finds himself on a train. He vaguely remembers being on a class trip when something terrible happened, and he is one of the few.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Midnight FM</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hpI9sYzKfSI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hrBLGsCbUySm6t4z9eonYrcpBAj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Popular TV anchorwoman and late night radio host Sun-Young (Soo-Ae) prepares to work her final radio program. After this program she will prepare to take her ill daughter to America.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Twisted Path</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/K36jgtJzT98\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/w4rYBWzY1emaHsQ7Bbrnv6fSZiC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Darrin is traumatized by a horrific event he witnessed as a child. Now 25, he and his brother Sean travel to Italy to visit an old friend, but the trip.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Incite Mill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/S4cCuvDjK6Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ajO84qG3C6OAsuXOO9e5v9VzGmV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ten people who agree to take the same lucrative ,job, find themselves locked in an underground complex and forced to play a murder game for seven days.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cold Weather</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jji4NM_c0vU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7fQLgybFSIIfMFe6iO5pkuDIB9n.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A guy who moves back to Portland, Oregon becomes involved in the mystery of his ex-girlfriend's disappearance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Valdemar Legacy II: The Forbidden Shadow</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4Szp5VB1wx8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iZgULiOv3iQQViAUEvbFN4aFsAR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Second part of the Valdemar saga. Ana and Eduardo are sent to assist in the investigation of the disappearance of Luisa. In the middle of the road they find Luisa.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Red Shoe Diaries</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WQFt8-ydpQI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l9271rPyt7AHp9fB8BGpjPRdNmF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Jake following the suicide of his girlfriend Alex seeks answers as to why she did it through her diaries. Jake discovers that although she loves him, she felt as if.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Jennifer 8</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-dgvbubor2hnc-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kXYGrgE99FMAupMYHkSPHRqo5Jy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A big-city cop from L.A. moves to a small-town police force and immediately finds himself investigating a murder. Using theories rejected by his colleagues, the cop, John Berlin, meets a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>House of Secrets</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5pk5rPpt5jk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uFeTVKYTg4oihKYXBctRjIXWrp1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Marion Ravinel is trapped in an abusive spousal relationship. She forms a plan with her husband's former lover to kill him. However, the outcome turns out to be more than.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Monster</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-lzdw5rgyw38m-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/frhnN2qMeZ3qoAjKiL0ieIlonj7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A vicious serial sex killer is on the loose, and landscape gardener and shop-window outfitter Loris is the prime suspect, thanks to his unfortunate habit of getting caught in compromising.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Angle mort</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RX51xZXkLOA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fqONQAqar5XctXIvUAyxStofI5v.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The relationship between Eric and Stephanie floundering. To meet and spend quality time together, they decide to leave for the Republic of Santiago in order to visit the famous ruins.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Cat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kNBP7pi5WXE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cYL5ykWhffOKucJjDSWkQdiZE7J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>So-yeun gets stuck with a Persian cat when its owner dies. From then on, she is haunted by a girl with green cat-like eyes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>That Girl in Yellow Boots</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FRDRfQ_mZnA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tioW4xmRPpHUvAbvMvUgSQG3avb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After the passing of her mother and the suicide of her 15-year old sister, Britain-based Ruth Edscer travels to Mumbai, India, to try and locate her father, Arjun Patel. She.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Messengers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BgmWqVIMRic\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/x2Z5iXhHaoK22vwfxju5vq25apS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's been six years since the Rollins family just up and left and now the troubled Solomon family has come from Chicago, to rebuild their lives following their sons hospitalization.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Me n Mr Jones, a love story on Natalee-island</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JhfdrJU50Tk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zMAm8cpWn4cHAX7xmwbcRUYhcR1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On sunny Aruba, an escort girl, that just heard she doesn't have long to live, falls in love with an undercover journalist, that wants to break in alleged murderer Joran.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Good Morning, Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6dbnNpoEn0k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kTYomIh50JBCYBhuXWS8gbGynlU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>follows FBI Special Agent Ana Gray as she hunts for a kidnapper. As Ana develops a rapport with the kidnapper's latest victim, the suspect suddenly changes his pattern. Now Ana.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Old Road Mistery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jQ2DJBxN610\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g41DZaay7FDyzHB9B3kFA5QNmSF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Monk</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/n1mVqAZiGV4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/y84mnmZHqeHM0XmukLPnHeI0gxH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Madrid, in the seventeenth century. Abandoned at the doorstep of a monastery, Ambrosio has been brought up by the Capucin Friars. After becoming a friar himself, he becomes an unrivaled.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Great Magician</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GEuDawf6PNM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wVPAi5cPZk9SMsitYSy0vhXajN7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the years after the Revolution that overthrew the Qing Dynasty in China and established the republic, China broken up into fiefdoms held by warlords, who are busy fighting each.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tenth Circle</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-0fvifhts4z5n-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3iBe4ZpItCJRcINq56g99e0udv1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Laura Stone is a college professor married to Daniel, a comic book artist. Their pride and joy is their 15-year-old daughter Trixie. But when Trixie comes home from a party.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Knock Knock 2</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GwMFblsEDiE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qLl4HJfYRAVw1Q3JULCpeTh2sEb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on found footage, the story centers on four friends in their early 20s. Last year, on the night before Halloween, they decided to go on a self made tour.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Emerging Past</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GzQ8DKgxBTM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>When you can't see the future, and the present seems to fade. You need to live for the past.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nobody Else But You</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ocjX8fXToYo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8Pt856GYco48SC6iVgtummTZrgU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Rousseau, is a Parisian bestselling crime novelist, working on a new novel but desperately looking for a good story. ,Candice Lecoeur, is a young, attractive, and vibrant woman who thinks.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Secrets of an Undercover Wife</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gkXHY86GknY&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uWqrvtBiHJpMlNoZWDnXzZgfoKF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Newlywed Wendy Crews has the shock of her life when her hubby is arrested by the FBI on their honeymoon. When he's convicted of murder and embezzlement, Wendy, frustrated and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Client</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/z1Jfe0ZG1es\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rz3ZVBztOfGQbJrYSxBeQBJ0qaG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Elite attorney Kang Seong-Hee goes up against a top prosecutor over a case involving a man accused of killing his wife.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Stone</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/LL741JAGJoE&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uE5jgqymkpeZXRiqDGt4dGdMwlI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A team of soul searchers uncover an ancient Stone and quickly all hell breaks loose as psychological and paranormal activity ensues.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>When They Cry</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2Sp6SkZ9Lyg&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ek4OZXLMbRotuWExhhRheKtKLN8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Early summer, Keiichi had just moved to a remote mountain village. As he becomes close friends with a group of girls, he was enjoying his life in the village. However.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Raaz 3: The Third Dimension</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HeMYsTS4JKU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mHXEypnPr7ri3K5dqDDw6fW9AMn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story revolves around Shanaya (Bipasha Basu), an actress at the height of her success. She gets offered the best roles and wins all the awards she's nominated for. In.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Puella Magi Madoka Magica the Movie Part 2: Eternal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZknpyKkHIvw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bab5yECvL86FPhPpPSkOlpIvino.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As the truth behind the girls' contracts with Kyubey is revealed, Madoka has to make the ultimate decision to either see those she love the most die before her eyes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Girl</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tf0mgVMQT8Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/51aXnxcia7aWsjsl39hJXKrIHcH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young Texan mother who loses her child to foster care begins smuggling Mexicans across the border.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Late Men</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4oeMQu43Faw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Three haunted men's lives violently interlock in a remorseless feud for survival and vengeance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Go to the Reunion</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/iICamqN58lU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dxav0XXgNUAPtLlT5E5YwerqdGk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Scott Rantzen (Brady Simenson) is a horror movie loving misfit who is teased by the popular students in school. When a date with the very popular and very beautiful Erica.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bridgend (2013)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kS7flyGKFw0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1srioLbGszuLdHsXsgdTvEtW5bo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Since 2007, dozens of teens and young people have been found hanged in Bridgend, South Wales. Most of them knew each other-they were friends, neighbors, even cousins. It's a mystery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Turist Ömer Uzay Yolu'nda</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rc3CfHfNmXg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/brPoNIg5CppaK8lVcr4Xeu4NhfN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Enterprise picks up a Turkish hobo.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Disappearance of Flight 412</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UqXdiZVXSME&tracker=False\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/osiDh4EKEwNPkFWBxa5GWbNc9fb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Colonel Pete Moore is commander of the Whitney Radar Test Group, which has been experiencing electrical difficulties aboard its aircraft. To ferret out the problem, he sends a four-man crew.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Night Strangler</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-an0f165ugnn2-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qK8RORVnj8SfsiXz6NmKVkPMWfL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Reporter Carl Kolchak is now in Seattle, Washington, trying to solve the mystery of several strangulations that recur every few years where the victims are drained of blood in this.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Reflections of Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fSUoLS5hDr8&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7XVeFkuKNj0jkC3G01XsOilRge6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The wife and mistress of the abusive headmaster of a boy's school plot and carry out his murder. They dump his body in the murky swimming pool at the school.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Devil's Triangle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RA6qtwfkO9A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2KF7LsXPy46AvP3X3PvtZ9PIp2L.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary exploring the mysteries of the Bermuda Triangle, an area of the ocean between Bermuda, Miami and Cuba into which many boats and planes have mysteriously disappeared over the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Reincarnation of Peter Proud</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KZ-AHb_29Pw&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pNsFSEmIyYsxXPVuqSjhe2LEjqF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When college professor Peter Proud begins to experience flashbacks from a previous incarnation, he is mysteriously drawn to a place he has never been before but which is troublingly familiar..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Who Is the Black Dahlia?</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y921yIpz4KI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9QCYH0a03dQYVBlnNUri0RPQgcw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dramatization of an actual homicide investigation. In 1947 Los Angeles, a police detective tries to solve the shocking and grisly murder of 22-year-old aspiring actress Elizabeth Short, whose nude body.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mrs. Amworth</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PMpwNOPFGN0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3e4aVz6jAUpwE9j4EUecPpAXRth.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A vampire terrorizes a quiet English town.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dead of Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b1xGIlbBp38\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8MUu9jtgpbSkOHod4jaL8yuHckQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This anthology tells three stories: one of time travel, one of vampires, and one of a mother wishing her drowned son back to life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>End of the World</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cRM3WGmuges\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gL8aFUP6nTd6aZ3yEQ7ejecdDo9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After witnessing a man's death in a bizarre accident, Father Pergado goes on a spiritual retreat, where he encounters his alien double bent on world conquest.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Strange Possession of Mrs. Oliver</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/x_TDs-UqXIo&feature=feedu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7r1MlcQj6DTNy2ie6bUvGzX1Y04.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A houswife, tired of her everyday routine, makes changes in her hair, her wardrobe and her makeup, and begins to take on the personality of a woman who had died.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alice or the Last Escapade</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MkWCsYLWxqA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wTIveJKz1oXHW9l0GUjnfBI7Shn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Alice Carol leaves her husband one rainy night, telling him that she does not love him anymore. She travels alone but when her windscreen breaks on a lonely road, she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murder in Peyton Place</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/EE4ZeUnDYwQ&feature=share\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/p382n90z8lwrxBDZoCWEZKH6OR8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Made for television movie that features some of the characters from the long running television series. In it Allison Mackenzie and Rodney Harrington go back to Peyton Place, and before.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sasquatch: The Legend of Bigfoot</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-ONP-sZkkL8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zU7F7wJOvPqBNRvcFKrS30lTf3K.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Scientists mount an expedition to find a Bigfoot-type creature.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Rosary Murders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UUq3golR5hs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gzxlFLppaua9GuzgghI45A9dulT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Life in the Catholic Church of the Holy Redeemer in Detroit is upset by a series of killings whose victims are all priests and nuns. All victims are found with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Appointment with Death</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-imrxy6nnouze-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eJ9vwtRQeJu80P6g1o8hxALbUnm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Emily Boynton, step-mother to the three Boynton children and mother to Ginevra, blackmails the family lawyer, Jefferson Cope, into destroying a second will of her late husband which would have.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man in the Brown Suit</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/30mSaVjIVH0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oHwHrk82DfSm6CIRO92kMGhbmAB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American woman is getting involved in a diamond theft in South Africa.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ghost of Flight 401</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vJt0oSpYJM8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qypAyAXlG3yjJrnswTfNrrfNUX1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An aircraft crashes in the Florida Everglades, killing 103 passengers. After the wreckage is removed, salvageable parts from the plane are used to repair other aircraft. Soon passengers and crew.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Dark Secret of Harvest Home</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y_fJNfAIrBY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8LHTU4Wvq7oeRRQgEpUgCUTWxGr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young couple moves to a quiet New England village, only to soon find themselves mixed up in mysterious rituals.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man Without a Map</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VygmI01BPE0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6E1t1HG5D09WM2EoxCEwm9FjV9V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A private detective is hired to find a missing man by his wife. Contradictory evidence and the lack of clues soon render the case as virtually unsolvable, as the detective.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Big Job</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-y0n1owkfptzo-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/b0GZKi9d2OjLjI8wjS8gjhYWn8b.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An inept gang of bank robbers, led by George The Brain, are caught and sentenced to 15 years hard labour each. When they are released from prison they start out.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Vulture</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZILfQ1DeT3Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/11Rhs9v9I5oBFJHB7djuaGQJ2TN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A mad scientist turns himself into a half-man, half-bird monster to avenge the death of his ancestor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Flesh Feast</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/QMLUua1Xv_s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hmDsPz5EYMwMDpNq4H5qWTu4k4J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dr. Elaine Frederick has just perfected a way of using maggots to make her test subjects not only look younger, but actually become younger. When they hear of the results.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Night Slaves</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9A3ILAXBozA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/emXwSvzUZB959g4PVtHZuzqR2l3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man and his wife find themselves stranded in a small western town. He discovers that a strange force has turned the residents into zombies, and runs into a beautiful.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Evening of Edgar Allan Poe</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZzyYzK94UU4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xtPFo9tCn3y30DwxlwqGwInD5gZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vincent Price recites four Edgar Allen Poe stories: The Tell-Tale Heart, The Sphinx, The Cask of Amontillado, and The Pit and the Pendulum.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Spider's Stratagem</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RqQ0TzKqY3k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iLg8x6id7BSBzoJfPmkcOm6c7vy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Athos Magnani, a young researcher, returns to Tara, where his father was killed before his birth, at the request of Draifa. The father, also named Athos Magnani and looking exactly.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Will to Die</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FkcU1NkIMNw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kNXp2PM4TlkaxZsKw9OEb0xaY1P.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In order to qualify to inherit the family fortune, the four heirs must spend the night in the family estate. However, during the night someone starts killing them off.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Little Game</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_XkZVz0HG1Y&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4A6UOng9tLSAgoROTJ3eLhsfQT6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A hostile youngster who will stop at nothing to break up his mother's marriage is suspected of homicide, and his stepfather fears that he may be the boy's next victim.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Place Like Homicide!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xUvanNjCqrY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4zhR3WKHQPz5iHvSSkapBioscC7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ernie's uncle Gabriel has just died but to claim his inheritance he must spend the night in the ancestral home with the rest of his relatives. Before long the guests.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Naked Edge</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kHIPfVrjlns\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hg5iIiGAnnnlG6ypx0WXV9bRYx0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>George Radcliffe's testimony sends Donald Heath to prison for murder and the theft of over 60,000 pounds. Soon after, Radcliffe invests a large sum of money in an ultimately profitable.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Deadly Duo</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dunzodf72K4&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aa6xJsXX623fTRvKi23iHhZJS1V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two identical twin sisters.one is very,very good,one is very, very bad. The good twin is due some big bucks. The bad twin wants 'em. Since they look just alike.look out.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Birds</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nLUFIXxKwKg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oFmlUPoPKFAzA9avylrEUs1FLj0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Melanie Daniels is the modern rich socialite, part of the jet-set who always gets what she wants. When lawyer Mitch Brenner sees her in a pet shop, he plays something.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Vanishing Act</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mQ0Q1hw5YxY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yQmFDc2mMJLRyZwgYo2EHvgr8oD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the Rocky Mountains, Harry Kenyon seeks out his missing wife Chris in the Winter Parade. Harry meets Lieutenant Rudameyer and tells that him he is from San Francisco and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dark Purpose</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-pCBvE9urRo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lbUI0f7ZJBWI9vaNH47OCpZDqDr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Shirley Jones plays an innocent young American abroad (Italy, specifically), assistant to the cynically sarcastic art historian Sanders. She becomes romantically involved with Sanders' current employer, the always charming Brazzi,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Don't Answer the Phone!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7z8gbfBLaLs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mMcYURyw6KpVwtSzjqSGzC3uApX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A deeply disturbed photographer and Vietnam veteran, named Kirk Smith, terrorizes Los Angeles by going around strangling lingerie-clad young women in their homes while taunting Lindsay Gale, a young psychologist,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sign of Four</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/J6ZDecbyJLc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mMsYCxzDXEtvgMEaXiccCj94aBk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sherlock Holmes and Dr. Watson try to track down the Great Mogul, the second-largest diamond in the world.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Eight Escorts</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZcGl2N8x9x8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/unSfO8vph5nBBLXEtZ32AC5ikIh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A new bandit with superb kung fu causes panic and fear among the merchants of Wuiyang County. The merchants hire Wu Chin Ping to escort boxes of beautiful and previous.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Revenge of the Stepford Wives</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gvPOn_MPVcQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/21MFpx0kjgw5XceD4etk4NYzRKd.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A TV reporter arrives in Stepford to do a story on the American town with the lowest crime and divorce rates and the tightest real-estate market (no one ever leaves)..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bermuda Triangle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b61HadTCSmA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ldcPtzUrEa1VpEQIO9GVzxcR4ma.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary that explores the legends, facts and folklore about the dreaded ,Bermuda Triangle,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cutter's Way</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/y7XemLk-0Zs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nNtW7xwpP3fwGWqgBYCm564S7zq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Alex Cutter (Heard) came back from war minus an eye, a leg, and an arm and mad as hell. He lacks direction, drinks too much, and abuses his wife (Eichhorn)..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beauty and the Beast (1978)</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UW519mpOlA8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u9QnrRADpVwUtnSSVacrmf6UVQM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A more horrific and gloomy version of The Beauty and the Beast. Julie is a bankrupt merchant's daughter who as the only one of the three daughters chooses to save.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>K-9 and Company: A Girl's Best Friend</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sQ3oV_yECX0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wE03FHC3cTHu6QIjw8z5yBKQkx8.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Spin-off from ,Doctor Who, which, despite good ratings, didn't get past the pilot stage. One time companion to a mysterious and body-changing alien known as ,The Doctor,, Sarah Jane Smith.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cry for the Strangers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZCLyChvum9k&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u6CEh6u6W3BostPYLvDKYFh3Cf5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A psychiatrist and his wife move into a quaint coastal town only to discover that a sinister presence is lurking there.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Naked Face</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ylcCQFhawe4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fmjdv7XSqjhL3GRYBXiRNjWl90y.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Chicago psychiatrist Judd Stevens is suspected of murdering one of his patients when the man turns up stabbed to death in the middle of the city. After repeated attempts to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Agatha Christie's Miss Marple: The Body in the Library</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RTuooFb-sP8&feature=BF\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u5FChkJnAoGS2D4piCSdMjSzotF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>BBC Adaption of Agatha Christie's novel; in the small village of St. Mary Mead, Colonel and Mrs. Bantry, owners of the local manor Gossington Hall, are shocked when a young.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Second Woman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/iBIvOsL59BY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ed17fmCecfUrMuJkIQGqP2x9pTk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In flashback from a  Rebecca'-style beginning: Ellen Foster, visiting her aunt on the California coast, meets neighbor Jeff Cohalan and his ultramodern clifftop house. Ellen is strongly attracted to Jeff,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Flying Saucer Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/w-gobjVfFiQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>An early documentary examining reports and hypotheses about flying saucers.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Runaway Bus</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/g2cRhCFdzUo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z31uCrOalH2lU2Y7rm9pGUHzokC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When heavy fog prevents all aircraft from leaving London airport, a group of passengers take an airline bus to get them to an alternative airport. However, one among their number.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Btyx4zkgHpg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kuqbKnzULGFDZEBrOjQooBray5w.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mystery writer Cornelia Van Gorder has rented a country house called ,The Oaks,, which not long ago had been the scene of some murders committed by a strange and violent.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Behind Green Lights</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YUlYI4cHsU8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cP4ujZsjoMP3bebnsS6ffmjy8yP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Police lieutenant Sam Carson investigates a political murder after the victim is dumped at the door of police headquarters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dressed to Kill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pOsT3ssmIoE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9wsTZpzwNgTIwnnFD92lg9Sb9xK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sherlock Holmes is intrigued when Dr. Watson's friend, Julian  Stinky' Emery, visits and tells them of a strange robbery at his flat the previous night. Stinky is an avid collector.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mask of Diijon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cfJbBDHz_eE&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lTwcB4jwGRwVhFCUatPyPET0lqq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A magician neglects his career and his wife while he pursues the study of hypnosis. His inattention causes his wife to leave him for a younger man. The magician them.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Red House</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/L6HZnUTPyho\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/svLo3Cibzv2BqSlvoLYUcCIQRmL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Pete and Ellen have reared Meg as their own, ever since she was a baby and her parents took off. Now a teen, Meg convinces her friend Nath to come.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Murderer Lives at Number 21</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UsanS3b_BLU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/WAndVjzXOxzN8IGoOCqqutumku.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dapper Inspector Vorobechik ( Wens' for short) is assigned the case of a serial killer who leaves a calling card on his victims; Monsieur Durand. Wens' mistress, struggling actress Mila Malou,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Inner Sanctum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KMf8T-LZ_xU&feature=plcp\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dUrUKvxgqjiewcrkDcGq8bcopPW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A man accidentally kills his fiancée as he exits a train. Just as the train pulls out, he drops her body on the rear platform. No one saw him do.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>One Body Too Many</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TjsnEVBCtT8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ar1o379ttQI2vNTuacx1l3J4oIC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Insurance salesman Albert Tuttle arrives at the Cyrus J. Rutherford estate to sell the millionaire some life insurance. Rutherford is already dead and his heirs have gathered at the mansion.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Frightened Lady</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/j42JV06eJB0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/aNgWhAXTBWUJLe67Pvwz0AqvRol.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>,Mark's Priory,. the family seat of the Lebanons, is a house of terror to Ilsa Crane, secretary and niece of Lady Lebanon. The strange behavior of two sinister butlers, Gilder.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Charlie Chan at the Wax Museum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Ztg5wAf0Wo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9KE4EDhheNnol4woN8JIEV9Idhy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A wax museum run by a demented doctor contains statues of such crime figures as Jack the Ripper and Bluebeard. In addition to making wax statues the doctor performs plastic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Charlie Chan's Murder Cruise</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Af2De6_26RM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3vnJxafQ9CBX5G4dRGyPUXVZPPy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On a cruise ship from Honolulu to San Francisco, the famous Chinese detective encounters four more murders while trying to figure out the murder of a Scotland Yard friend.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Charlie Chan in The Chinese Cat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/e2-wuVmkwWU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qJOpI3JmyiqmWjdVc8DdtNCkoqa.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Thomas P. Manning, businessman and chess expert mysteriously shot in a locked room, dies clutching some chess pieces. Police are baffled, and finally abandon the case. Six months later, victim's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Panther's Claw</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BnSxPJqqZxw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2uyTJG19PKUQ9dFnn5asPrN9B92.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The police arrest a man climbing over the wall of a cemetery after midnight. He claims that he is being blackmailed and is following instructions he received by mail to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shake Hands with Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fwHIIQChDO4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/e9JfOcM4LPoamBsF6jtWguFMIDD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A female bail-bond broker and her partner help an accused embezzler prove his innocence. Having the body of the embezzler's late business partner pop up doesn't help matters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Castle in the Desert</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mBtPu2qF2so\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lRcc4BGzJlD2lPb3xQFESH2H9Oo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paul Manderley, eccentric historian, and his wife, descendant of the Borgias, live in an isolated castle-like mansion in the Mojave Desert. When a guest suddenly collapses, Charlie Chan is invited.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tell-Tale Heart</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YlTCXIJEj-c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rQcrtDKgndWNZat2kuBJGJoSIl4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this classic Edgar Allan Poe story, a man commits a murder, but afterward the victim's beating heart torments the murderer's mind.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Black Cat</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-ncdzsih5muyn-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h7aF2waORT2zvZHefz0ToKSoUfA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Greedy heirs gather to wait for the death of Henrietta Winslow. Murder, thunder claps, howling cats, gun shots, screams in the night, hidden passages &#8212; all the proper ingredients.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Horror Island</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-9ipgqm5dyghr-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iamqgOQdsWU8jtLXo6SBQ7ZH4fG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Down-on-his luck entrepreneur Bill Martin and sidekick Stuff Oliver try to stay one step in front of creditors in their seedy waterfront office when they meet ,The Captain,, an idiosyncratic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sherlock Holmes and the Voice of Terror</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/p1yUB2Mc8fg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/44QrE1wQnbzlbFzpWvXYWKxO5jF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a Nazi saboteur jeeringly predicts to the nation new depredations, via their radio  Voice of Terror', the Intellegence Inner Council summons Sherlock Holmes (Basil Rathbone) to help in the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Today I Hang</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/aAo5M0tOMs0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rozQ5gEOQCENSiSuralV2VD5Vao.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Henry Courtney, a wealthy importer is found murdered and the famous DeNormand necklace has been stolen. The false testimony of two witnesses, Rand and Hobbs, puts Jim O'Brien in the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Boss of Big Town</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Rt6YH8M1kU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/llBRJtCchZTWlKgrbZjLG5Kr88I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Diligent City Market official Michael Lynn resists overtures by well-to-do gangster Kenneth Craige to fix produce and dairy prices during wartime. Lynn seems unable to stop the resulting sabotage and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lady of Burlesque</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WCa1qNPINgE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ry8Uask7c7cK1LFE5jGzs9xExic.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sassy Dixie Daisy is the hot new attraction at a former opera house that's been turned into a burlesque theater. She's popular with the customers, although not with Lolita La.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sherlock Holmes Faces Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TSlijzn0Vlo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/45m42VSciijt2YEXXL6ccnl6kGj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During WWII several murders occur at a convalescent home where Dr. Watson has volunteered his services. He summons Holmes for help and the master detective proceeds to solve the crime.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Scream in the Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rGt2MD0drc0&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uMzEzecAqeEHZTgD0WVmkewkZ3W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A colonial police detective in an Eastern seaport seeks a stolen gem, and infiltrates the underworld by posing as a look-alike wharfside bar owner.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Phantom of 42nd Street</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zz-ulHliKkY&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9StxyTWgKokfXIt4ugXkKR2FieL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An actor is killed during the performance of a play and critic Tony Woolrich (Dave O'Brien) undertakes to solve the crime. Claudia Moore (Kay Aldridge, in her last movie role),.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Great Flamarion</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PoE3quTGp5g&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2Gtvb1dX7SwLTyYTW5cGHseSx1S.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Flamarion, expert marksman, is entertaining people in a show which features Connie, beautiful woman and her husband Al. Flamarion and Connie fall in love and decide to get rid of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Scarlet Clue</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nNHn3Ri8wUo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dKOQV96pKOc2FGF5QZybSwaLTFr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Charlie Chan investigates the theft of government radar papers (the laboratory is located in the same building as a radio station!) with the help of Number Three Son Tommy and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Terror</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/movie/the-terror?feature=mv_e_rel_b\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/953op07Gu8hP0ym4oZzEVbizYGZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A mysterious criminal mastermind plots a spectacular gold robbery, then after the robbery is completed he makes sure his gang is caught by the police, keeps the gold and disappears..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Scared Stiff</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OjXJmb4y4q4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xAJcaAtNLSe2K3Up2hOkGEtwp6z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The jumpy chess editor at a newspaper accidentally gets involved in some murders at a sleazy tavern run by a pair of bizarre brothers.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Duck Pimples</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1Qzkofwt4_c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ts3XXNXdeutuUvFTJGG6Moo2VSu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Donald Duck becomes a suspect in a whodunit of his own imagination.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Copper Beeches</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tlmOLRjeqa8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ace of Hearts</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1OSqiFG1qPs&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/v5dOVJc0AkDK0FkW2LIXrVLyD4p.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A secret society holds a meeting to determine what to do about a powerful and dangerous man whom they have been studying closely for the past three months. They all.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Devil's Foot</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/onbEsGCQ0xQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4e23mKEJzlVYtNtZ4s0WtcK9QK3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A family is at their dining room table, sitting upright and dressed for dinner,except they're all dead. Sherlock Holmes must figure out how,and, more importantly, why,they were murdered.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Cat and the Canary</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ePhpx9kKa0s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tg1tCzNdUpZCKMdTuOXlanhFe4C.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Relatives of an eccentric millionaire gather in his spooky mansion on the 20th anniversary of his death for the reading of his will.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Bat</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/15zlF9obMEg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/paGeDyal4SuZlYMNm1JNMlsSh8O.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A masked criminal who dresses like a giant bat terrorizes the guests at an old house rented by a mystery writer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Big News</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/l_IXfCTiagw&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zL3Pqb498ZfegR6xKjv2sW0TbzC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Steve Banks is a hard-drinking newspaper reporter. His wife Margaret, a reporter for a rival paper, threatens to divorce him if he doesn't quit the drinking that is compromising his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Locked Door</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZdmP3OHoALk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/azh533Nq0jDgvf27E0b3FhPaC05.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While Ann and the son of her boss are out on a ship beyond the 12-mile limit, which allows liquor to be consumed, the son, Frank makes unwanted advances towards.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murder at Midnight</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AkEYwF5DtG8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xpx2CeX33e722KQZ2KL1x9ppTLK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Wealthy Mr. Kennedy shoots his secretary, Channing, during a parlor game, but it turns out the gun was loaded with real bullets. Luckily, criminologist Phillip Montrose is on hand to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Black Camel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qwkTewuR_HM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a8xVuOGTzPpt6QcGdTQoJiSBL5T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Movie star Sheila Fayne is seeing wealthy Alan Jaynes while filming in Honolulu, Hawaii, but won't marry him without consulting famed psychic Tanaverro first. Tanaverro confronts her about the unsolved.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Thirteenth Guest</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7VoRVmoW0Os&feature=fvwrel\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pPCdvAIqsUx1mEtq5S9ZMJo8jJC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>13 years before the movie opens, there was a dinner party, at which the 13th guest failed to show up. The master of the manner has died, and left the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sinister Hands</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UnmeIxMhzLY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rWY1Ae2nMsSHoXYIVHynqXo0sne.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During a séance at an elderly millionaire's house, the millionaire is murdered. The detectives investigating the crime discover that everyone who was at the séance had a motive for killing.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The King Murder</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KlPrMFg-E5I&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rF5JoIsQBWaBclAg3l5cQq2Ex7w.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A beautiful blonde makes a career out of seducing and then blackmailing wealthy married men. She is found murdered after demanding a $5000 payoff from her latest victim, and the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Strangers of the Evening</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wwT18-48zuU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u0YLf5DgWhsbdNrc0QfwZdsEgJU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Bodies start mysteriously disappearing from the city morgue. An investigator tries to determine what is going on.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ten Minutes to Live</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jETn4R9BpKA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lPLHlG0cwnO5vhZlwyrZSssFV9Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A movie producer offers a nightclub singer a role in his latest film, but all he really wants to do is bed her. She knows, but accepts anyway. Meanwhile, a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Secret of the Blue Room</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hXPfd5B7ylo&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7756AuhpsCbvQAqVeXz58RXd5JJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Twenty years after 3 murders occur in a castle's ,blue room,, three men who each want to marry a beautiful girl decide to spend a night in the room to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Phantom Broadcast</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YEyy6g_MLVg&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A handsome radio singer has it all,fame, money, adoring fans,but what no one knows is that his accompanist, a hunchbacked piano player, is actually the voice behind the arrogant, abusive.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ghost Walks</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hTNE8zK-M8A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sXhWsxAyu13eUq4JQJ1ZxiDOamw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On a stormy night, a theatrical producer, his secretary, and playwright Prescott Ames are stranded when their car skids off the road and gets stuck. The three take refuge in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mysterious Mr. Wong</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pvS3C-qf6rU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8X3tm2YPhenqEO1PBJL7h2AcJ8g.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Investigating a series of murders in Chinatown, wise-guy reporter Jason Barton is captured by the megalomaniacal Mr. Wong, desperately trying to complete his collection of the twelve gold coins of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Condemned to Live</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gsCUtt_oTNk&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dG0cs4vqWxYnHmnaSCPpeWSxFOh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After a series of murders, a man finds out that his mother was bitten by a vampire bat during her pregnancy, and he believes that he may be the vampire.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rocky Mountain Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fk-8Xrg0bLY&feature=fvwrel\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nTNjATMjY2FF9jADsJwRgBCgSsf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A mining engineer teams up with a crusty deputy sheriff to solve the mystery killings at an old mine where the owner's family waits for him to die, and where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mandarin Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RFAmMs83aCo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8LRrZlgUWNoCj9uQ3j3yQweKwhp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A very rare and priceless Chinese postage stamp is stole as its thief claims two victims in a hotel,, both of whom are murdered in inexplicably locked rooms. Young Ellery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Death in the Air</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Wme9EEj8qaM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xg5VrNdbSJweJdddirh09df0nOU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Planes are being shot down by a large black plane with a large ,X, painted on the wing. The chief suspects are invited for the weekend to an old dark.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Face in the Fog</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sZnFLSo3HVo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/biYbJONW3WWfwnBu24KOPKANf3Z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cast members of a show at the Alden theatre are being terrorized by a hunchback killer known as the Fiend, using frozen bullets, and two have been killed. Newspaper reporters.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The President's Mystery</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6FuQ_D2ycHU&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rcLOOvHxrcu05cxFd4OPa5og17e.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A millionaire with a crumbling personal life comes up with an idea on how he can disappear, start a new life without anyone knowing who he is and be able.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Charlie Chan at the Olympics</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MABZpflS-qE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2tmyjzZSIsSTQ3ejLwCxoznfgzs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When an experimental plane is hijacked and its pilot murdered, the new guidance system that will allow it to fly unmanned is stolen. Charlie traces the strategically important invention to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bulldog Drummond in Africa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rxwWujJpuRE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/s7AAUOcwWz2BxCfbWcv4LcvQqGe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the eve of his wedding Captain Hugh Drummond is off to Morocco when Scotland Yard's Colonel J.A. Nielson is kidnapped by international criminal Richard Lane. With his fiancée Phyllis.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sunset Murder Case</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bUfaIRA9fzg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vmEtEGjAdXQyrX48l1nhXsQwHo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Small-time showgirl, loved by two decent men, poses as a stripper to infiltrate a nightclub whose owner is believed responsible for her father's murder.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bulldog Drummond's Secret Police</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dmfpuSMkLoU&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nUaQHdZcAwKOv0AKH2J6cV4CkX0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Captain Drummond and his girlfriend want to marry but a hidden treasure in the house in which they want to celebrate their marriage is complicating the situation.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lORiysfv-Vg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6CMJC5FlagO9HM4YT5W3df9k5Nh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Professor Moriarity has a scheme for stealing the crown jewels from the Tower of London. To get Holmes involved, he persuades a gaucho flute player to murder a girl.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Invisible Killer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9-5V5CkTRlc&feature=relmfu\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5M2NQr8oaBGzmes7T7CoYlqumZR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A fiendish killer uses sound waves to commit his murders.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nancy Drew and the Hidden Staircase</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-9tdx3326a6m5-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uRGv8MDHy7mRjwCf1GsExRfNTqm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Nancy Drew and Ted Nickerson solve a murder and save two elderly ladies from losing their family home. The old mansion is complete with a moving wall and a hidden.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Panama Patrol</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qHWfJ-ye0jc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gp9bnaRoyOiIwBeTZnsee59DuGk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>THe head of the cipher bureau, Phillip Waring, is about to marry his secretary, Helen Lane, when he is informed that the state department has discovered a message that must.</summary>
</item>


