<item>
<title>7 Days in Syria</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1097216756449\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gGw40F3OlKIWwwWvcrDjm8jt8SQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Newsweek Middle East editor, Janine di Giovanni, submitted a proposal to cover the war in Syria. The magazine denied the request, deeming the situation too dangerous. She decided to go.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>100 Years of the RAF</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1071177075425\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h4crriug8sVaTZitmV0mrpc0Lrb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For 100 years the Royal Air Force's courage, perseverance and innovation have secured freedom, survival and safety for the many  at home and abroad. Since its infancy, the RAF.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>1945 From This Day</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1847473146449\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mX83VFjDknGQsV5Amfi2zKF3Tbm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In Germany's Hurtgen Forest, during the final days of World War 2, an exhausted and overwhelmed band of American army paratroopers fight for survival amid a deadly hidden threat, escalating.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ashes in the Snow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1809015966289\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wRMgle7vPFvSMq5R76JhsH54W4S.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1941, a 16 year-old aspiring artist and her family are deported to Siberia amidst Stalin's brutal dismantling of the Baltic region. One girl's passion for art and her never-ending.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>SGT. Will Gardner</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1809016359505\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3JDEQ7pF8cI0YE1o5srRPZVZ01J.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A troubled Iraq War veteran struggling to reintegrate into society sets out on a cross-country journey with the hope of reuniting with his young son.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Captain</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1807560346193\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/l1otiFXq8h8q9vsiY8Dsh4kihxv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the last moments of World War II, a young German soldier fighting for survival finds a Nazi captain's uniform. Impersonating an officer, the man quickly takes on the monstrous.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Where Hands Touch</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1802988161617\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kZwrC2A7WJ6wNMqigSZsDvaqNHi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Germany, 1944. Leyna, the 15-year old daughter of a white German mother and a black African father, meets Lutz, a compassionate member of the Hitler Youth whose father is a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Down River</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1747460950609\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjQyZDZhMmYtZDFmNy00NWNjLWFmZGMtYWI5OTgzNzYxYjg0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODg3MzY5MjE@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Four soldiers trapped behind enemy lines must confront their fears and desires.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Laugh or Die</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1739828300369\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7L0QhTjs5dmOxbPUt5GCsrn0OF1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a detention camp in 1918, a group of Finnish actors are sentenced to death. When an important German general arrives, the camp's vicious commandant forges out a cruel plan:.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bye Bye Germany</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1723945126481\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ucLCeiL3pdIusT5lbNpVBPMTAAm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>David Berman and his friends, all Holocaust survivors, have only one purpose: to go to America as soon as possible. For this they need money. Close to his aim, David.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alone We Fight</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1718648572497\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lp7Ylv3Ug8ah6xJkMvlJB0LaHSU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Facing mounting odds, a small but determined band of American soldiers venture into dangerous enemy territory on a mission to stop an advancing German unit from breaking through the Allied.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Chinese Widow</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1683109120593\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/g9nLgciMQ2iY02KjoIQ27r9eAhm.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1940s, the Japanese attacked Pearl Harbor and this destroyed the Americans morale. The president of America, Franklin Roosevelt, decided to risk it all to bomb Tokyo raising more hope.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thirst (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1604070279761\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4QOkqwhqFz8n5bd0aNZU7g4dHIa.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Two best friends are pitted against each other when a new girl comes to town, matters are further complicated when they enlist together in the U S Army to fight.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Resistance Banker</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1574198774353\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2yzvCVg44KCw3L9dBlBuP41AEjq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In Nazi-occupied Amsterdam, banker brothers Walraven and Gijs van Hall face their greatest challenge yet when they decide to help fund the Dutch resistance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hurricane (2018)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1569852361297\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mTpmZORhYswd9YinB23wV9QE2cx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Hurricane (Squadron 303) is the story of a group of brave Poles who fought in the skies over England in WW2, not just to keep Great Britain free from the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Trench 11</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/1567092312657\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ecY0vTWNRfjc9DyMAjN7QASVpYP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the final days of WWI a shell-shocked soldier must lead a mission deep beneath the trenches to stop a German plot that could turn the tide of the war.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>This Is Congo</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/731015612991\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fnni4EGsD180uC3FgyhEprbXbIp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>THIS IS CONGO (working title) is an unblinking and unfiltered look into one of the world's longest standing, ongoing wars and those who are surviving within it. With over three.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Coming Convergence</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/685969181247\</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzRlNTI1YmUtNzQ5Ny00ZTExLTk1OGMtMzJmZDFiZmRlMmIxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Through newly discovered geological and statistical patterns, many believe it can be proven that the Tribulation is about to begin!</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>M.I.A. A Greater Evil</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/659894503999\</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzhhMzU3MDUtNjcwYi00ZWU0LTkzY2EtZjNlOGQ4Y2JlNjViXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk3NDA1NTE@._V1_UY268_CR9,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American college students head to the jungles of Vietnam to search for lost gold. They become hopelessly lost, and they may not be alone.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thousand Yard Stare</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/645826218559\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xszXGsSksjclGFX4V2z8gMHSPKM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Returning home after fighting in Africa during World War II, a soldier with PTSD finds reintegrating with family life increasingly difficult as he relives the battle of Kasserine Pass.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Unknown Soldier</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/611198962239\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zw5w15njhenm6Sq0Q6tjYOaRk7n.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film follows Finnish army machine gun company in Continuation War against Soviet Union, 1941–1944. Based on Väinö Linna's best selling novel Tuntematon Sotilas (The Unknown Soldier) and the novel's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Breadwinner</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/532945898047\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2d6qmkJz9AWqmk9wBWtd2uFX89t.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A headstrong young girl in Afghanistan disguises herself as a boy in order to provide for her family.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thank You for Your Service (2017)</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/482562607773\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z8OKWw6DAZAOyz8F421euawr3Hs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>DreamWorks Pictures' Thank You for Your Service follows a group of U.S. soldiers returning from Iraq who struggle to integrate back into family and civilian life, while living with the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Will Not End Here</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/gT6eFXJIeBo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lXb2VaJjsF5UGV8hn0H7CZvtpF1.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Djuro is a Romany, he has a large, happy family, and earns a living appearing in Serbian porn films. And it's through his sarcastic perspective that we follow the story.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The First World War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OSN3EaJPhvU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r2Pg78Chdlx7EYtFnEFxFOVOKYN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1914, decades of building European resentments and rivalries finally exploded into a massive total war that became much larger and bloodier for far longer than anyone could have imagined..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Generation Kill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8seylbvSRDI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/x5vVAvbyQ4GsbJClMMHdzbbjFPT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Following multiple recon marines during the invasion of Iraq in 2003, a group of mixed personalities, you see the dysfunctionality of the military, and on other times, how formalized and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Tree of Guernica</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/349716351630\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8GtxlAP80Essh2dF3I2KnzKZDmQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Spanish Civil War, as experienced by the town of Villa Ramiro. The local count and his Fascist nephews ally with the rebels; the count's son, indifferent to politics at.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I diavoli della guerra</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TiWzieedkYc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hncdihmJyKDfeXSx0rWF7eS27Wu.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A German Captain and American Captain help each other survive the North African desert during WWII. They meet again a year later during combat operations in France.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>How the States Got Their Shapes</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/F6p0YFJRfBs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Every shape on the map tells a story about our past. Why does Oklahoma have a panhandle? Because of shifting borders for slavery. Why does Missouri have a boot? Because.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>71: Into the Fire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/r9wY7llFnng\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1v4XKKlJJKpUVhaDKy5XWV3A9pG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of student-soldiers trying to protect a middle school during the early days of the Korean War.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Target for Today</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oqxYGVsiPHE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Ny8in3isHpmTvvf1OgSE9tX10X.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary about one bombing mission over Germany by the American Eighth Air Force, from the initial planning for the mission thru finsl completion of the mission, with all of its.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beating the Bomb</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b15INIVCs5Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>This is a film about the biggest weapons of mass destruction ever created. It is about the people who use them, more importantly it is about the people who fight.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dog Jack</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dv8Ye6E6J1k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Dog Jack is the story of a slave boy and his dog who escape the master's plantation, join the union army, and have to face their former master on the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Call of Duty: Operation Kingfish</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XY5bJxNb8hg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fUhTqWEWsC5oNyl7EojvJrXDRLs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A team of soldiers, with close air support and satellite surveillance, perform Operation Kingfish  the attempted capture of an international terrorist. They find a trap waiting, however, and are.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cluster Bombs: Banned in New Zealand</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mBHJ1DoRRtI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Cluster Bombs tells the story of New Zealand's central role in the global movement to ban cluster bombs and stop civilian harm caused by this weapon. Through the personal testimonies.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ottoman Lieutenant</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/335140293262\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c5E8KTDuGNdF4Lmv3OhsQ0W1zPw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lillie, a determined American woman, ventures overseas to join Dr. Jude at a remote medical mission in the Ottoman Empire (now Turkey). However, Lillie soon finds herself at odds with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rescue Under Fire</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/334988905102\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWQ0ZmJmYmQtMzZjNi00N2JjLWI2Y2MtZmZlZTRmNjlhN2E2L2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjY3MTkzMzY@._V1_UY268_CR3,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Zona hostil The crew of a medical helicopter suffers an accident when helping a joint force of USA and United Nations troops under Spanish command division in Afghanistan. The Spanish.</summary>
</item>
<title>Winter War (2017)</title>
<link>https://vidbom.com/embed-qwpe7w2wewu7.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTA3NWU4MzQtNTBlMC00NGMxLWFjYjItZjRhYjZiOWEwNTBlL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjA0MTk5NTQ@._V1_UY268_CR3,0,182,268_AL_.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>January 1945. The first French regiment of paratroopers to fight with an American unit to liberate Alsace in France. An Allied Division must take the forest bordering the town of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Heroes Don't Come Home</title>
<link>https://ok.ru/videoembed/333301222030\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vTnobAK7pAJzhgu7ZNxeg4ALg35.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Deep in the woods of Maine, a broken promise made after the September 11th attacks forces two friends to confront the teenagers they were and the men they've become.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Railroad Tigers</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/T_CMbh2VNCg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1aSkP9geZCbqIoxjF7Jy9dT8UfY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In December 1941, The railway from Tianjin to Nanjing in East China became a key military transportation route, heavily guarded by Japanese soldiers. Ma Yuan, a railroad worker and his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Attack in the Pacific</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/w5gi873N844\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>There are over 10,000 islands within the Pacific Ocean located between Asia and America, the vast majority of which possess little geopolitical importance in periods of peace  but during.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Carter's Army</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_aC3e6WucSM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ioXwCFFaaXR18ZWCol2LCrXphOe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A racist officer is put in charge of a squad of black troops charged with taking an important bridge from the Germans.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Keep Em Flying</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1peQ5iagq7s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/osKVNokysC4lhkfX2Yv5rjEhW6D.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a barnstorming stunt pilot decides to join the air corps, his two goofball assistants decide to go with him. Since the two are Abbott &#038; Costello, the air corps.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Purple Hearts</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/y85giOl5VtE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zf5IjFzEoK3YsdsUUXNiYxb77Tl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In middle of the Vietnam war a Navy surgeon and a nurse fall in love while serving in Vietnam during the war. Their affection for one another provides a striking.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>War Stories</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JIZl6vfA1O8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/f2CMGhIabigGtfC9leoF46OPUew.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A failed pilot for a drama about two war journalists, a cynical and disillusioned man and an idealist woman who must deal with the horrors of war as well as.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/b_sG5vRKcB0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/clJg2wsCCJj7ehk1tfvIZIKOFu4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Julio Madariaga is the Argentine patriarch of a wealthy family. He has two daughters, the elder wed to a Frenchman and the other to a German. He prefers the Frenchman.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Beach Red</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tzEm4go2lPE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8nIuspun4KPru3lcxvCvPviAx9C.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American Marines storm ashore on a Japanese-held island and push inland while their enemy plans a counterattack, in this look at warfare. Fighting men on both sides are haunted by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>How I Won the War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/logjz5y2Ots\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/whI4pAKrLeZjOC5qYnO6QJbEi2x.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This film features former Beatle John Lennon and Roy Kinnear as ill-fated enlisted men in under the inept command of Lieutenant Earnest Goodbody. The story unwinds mostly in flashbacks of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Winter War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7ELfMprEbrI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cdGgk9a8b6wctMoH11BMMBPwzuC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set during World War 2. After Nazi Germany invaded Poland in September 1939, Russia attacked Finland in November 1939. Finnish reservists leave their homes and go to war. The film.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Esther Raped</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3-zjIyZZdNo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>The film explores the relationship between a young, African American man, deployed to Iraq and the girlfriend who must bid him farewell. The narrative unfolds over a casual dinner where.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Town Like Alice</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/trJxV9909IE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/52uAbqA0AqfU87uwWEqgnW9E5wE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1941, The advancing Japanese army captures a lot of British territory very quickly. The men are sent off to labor camps, but they have no plan on what to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gandhi to Hitler</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/r1csUS0wLHk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5HU64iI1THSLSlIORXWG3Wr3Jwi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Chancellor Adolf Hitler assists Azad Hind Fauj, led by Subhas Chandra Bose, which include a group of Indians who are frustrated with the Gandhian manner of non-violence to compel the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Articles of War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WcHNjzD18to\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A young American pilot fighting in 1944 writes what may be the final letter of his life, bearing his soul to the man who inspired him to enlist. his father,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Murderers Among Us: The Simon Wiesenthal Story</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ISnyTh7Y2mY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cdChkylSq3lPjdKwS74zsqlCpki.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A biographical portrayal of Simon Wiesenthal, famous Nazi Hunter. From his imprisonment in a Nazi Concentration Camp, the film follows his liberation and his rise to become one of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Ungentlemanly Act</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8HgPba1iHas\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qR3cDshkYnyuafrzrV8cVJnBrhq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on actual accounts, this film portrays the days and hours before and during the invasion of the Falkland Islands by Argentina, which eventually lead to the Falklands War. As.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tai quan zhen jiu zhou</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tCm0lEGBkCE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3Vss0BZnXtuqGeKWS4WJbQCaHDv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the Japanese occupation of Korea in the 1930's, the leader of a small resistance movement attempts to get information to sympathizers in China.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Strike Commando</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UtAyJPuKuMY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yJ0fEQrDczgJ8519JCL3HfZmzL0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While operating behind enemy lines, Sgt. Mike Ransom learns of a Russian presence in North Vietnam. Ordered to obtain proof of this discovery, Ransom returns to enemy territory but is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Stand at Lang Mei</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sgm4nrBrVFg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/du6bWGx4agdOBrCpFINfexw9Hah.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Vietnam, 1968. Army Headquarters has written off Captain Fahey's men as Missing In Action after they were fighting deep over enemy lines. Cut off from their platoon, they must fight.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Young Indiana Jones: Attack of the Hawkmen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/q8YLpt-ed1E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j1l8JzhROQAMzMFGAGHqA3NWWaM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Indiana Jones transfers from the Belgian army to the French intelligence service, where his first assignment is as a reconnaissance photographer for the 124th Squadron, a group of volunteer American.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Swords and Hearts</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/22PMrAfh2cQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/evyWr2RC3GHR5oglDqiztiTMvSW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As Hugh Frazier, son of a wealthy tobacco planter, leaves to join his company in the Confederate Army, he becomes engaged to Irene Lambert, a beautiful, but cold and calculating.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ever in My Heart</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ffJuXTWh8Fs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vzb7N94os3oJuG3wju05mgoiUbM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1909 Mary Archer, daughter of small-town bluebloods, awaits the return from Germany of sometime beau Jeff. But Jeff brings with him a German friend, Hugo Wilbrandt, who loves and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La Grande Illusion</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hctrYzVYmfM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lWg41zE0FVixkNsFgxnlRyvDYv9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During 1st WW, two French officers are captured. Captain De Boeldieu is an aristocrat while Lieutenant Marechal was a mechanic in civilian life. They meet other prisoners from various backgrounds,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Dawn Patrol</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RGQYpP60J70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rc00pdpgGasng60HJIQS9ktAde2.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1915 France, Major Brand commands the 39th Squadron of the Royal Flying Corps. The young airmen go up in bullet-riddled crates and the casualty rate is appalling, but Brand.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Shopworn Angel</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yiSyDQxbtaM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bWql2xuG0uRu8XEw09DxKKOMTqU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During WWI Bill Pettigrew, a naive young Texan soldier is sent to New York for basic training. He meets worldly wise actress Daisy Heath when her car nearly runs him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Spy in Black</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IFLJRWi1fuk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nHh4KyHyCvHErIgqR1GNwuYMX7x.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When a German U-Boat captain is sent on a spying mission to the North of Scotland during World War One, he finds more than he bargained for in his contact,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Confessions of a Nazi Spy</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/y_wn9GLgbWU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jET8RlYdpjQVZkBtjqBLSSmIA69.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Prior to the United States entry into World War II, Nazi spies try to steal American military secrets. Among those whose passions are roused is Kurt Schneider who was court-martialed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>British Intelligence</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fftw-6iMggE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hGHgBpgaLvtAb2xHIhrrzlBajJv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During WWI pretty German master spy Helene von Lorbeer is sent undercover to London to live with the family of a high-placed British official where she is to rendezvous with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Caught in the Draft</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xw8eGq5bblA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qHSlneIfDfc3qKb2PNi8rZxru7y.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Don Bolton is a movie star who can't stand loud noises. To evade the draft, he decides to get married.but falls for a colonel's daughter. By mistake, he and his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>40,000 Horsemen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wqVV69qjszk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9m6Y5ZKBfWem9VB7k0tUBbecJ4V.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Three young Australians join the army at the beginning of World War I and are assigned to the Australian Light Horse cavalry, which is serving in Palestine. The three eventually.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thunder Birds: Soldiers of the Air</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eeuwcWFSnZM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eGeCrv4HjqywdsWCLuAHYtvKeps.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Technicolor tale of honor and romance. This drama from 1942 was directed by Oscar-winner William A. Wellman, and features stunning aerial photography, that was highly advanced for the time. John.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Report from the Aleutians</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/oHnX9_to7ww\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8IwmIbM1fXZANujMEDMwf8h3iL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A cinematic record of US military operations on the Aleutian Island of Adak to retake Japanese occupied Kiska.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Guadalcanal Diary</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3IaWMVI0aig\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8MLl1uJ62ChPmOXkSwM1YwxRgkF.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Concentrating on the personal lives of those involved, a war correspondent takes us through the preparations, landing and initial campaign on Guadalcanal during WWII.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>This Land Is Mine</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/og2quk1a3gM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eUKhCkM6pnd5b5A3ndK56AoqDHi.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a Nazi-occupied French town, meek and mild-mannered teacher Albert Lory lives with his mother. Few people, including his students, have any respect for him and he literally shakes in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Smilin' Jack</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WBMbxPZSZdQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Just before World War II, the Chinese and American governments mount a joint operation to prevent the Germans and Japanese from taking over the strategic island of Mandon.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Background to Danger</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/853zN_Ck5XU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/94bJfF8h09b7z50Q8dsuVtjiRI6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Ankara in neutral Turkey : World War Two. A town of intrigue and of provocateurs. The Germans are planning to leak maps apparently proving that the Russians are about to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Desert Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nuvWM2NqZ08\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9KuGLI7GMh5JkBIqRLtCAcT5Pmk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This documentary recounts the famous World War II battle of El Alamein, considered one of the key turning points in the war against the Nazis. The film uses actual footage.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>For Me and My Gal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vzkgohtAa9Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t5dRNV7Oqgwl4OaJbkn793WwctU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set during WW I, Palmer and Hayden team up as vaudeville artists. Harry Palmer deliberately injures his hand to avoid being drafted to the army. Later, he makes up for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Guy Named Joe</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kRKRb7qjCus\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tbM53yBwhoYK9JoPKRpUSVZtP8s.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Maj. Pete Sandidge is a very able pilot who seems to have a streak of luck as far as flying goes. World War II is raging and Pete has come.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The White Cliffs of Dover</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-wexb4rn5s4xh-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4J6Y3KFoJwxqB551IlnCrj82B6P.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>London based American nurse, Susan, Lady Ashwood, is at the hospital awaiting the imminent arrival of injured soldiers. She is hoping that her enlisted son, Sir John Ashwood, who resembles.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Price of Rendova</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HxNGJu4HSKc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary short subject depicting the battle for the island of Rendova, a vital part of the American campaign against the Japanese in World War II.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Battle for the Marianas</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FiQUCxbHgnI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary short film depicting the successful but costly invasions of the Japanese-held islands of Guam, Tinian, and Saipan, in the Mariannas chain.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Chance</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-5QREkbNsJ8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/u2XuEFIrBs9eckoprtgCnfe5oWn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Escaping a Nazi prison train in war-torn Italy, an American and a British soldier set out for the Swiss border and find themselves leading a multi-national party of refugees for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sleeping Voice</title>
<link>https://openload.co/embed/i9BsimlR7Uo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/asBTOphsvMcynNHf87HB8c5CdSh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Madrid, post-Spanish Civil War. Sisters Hortensia and Pepita are involved with an underground guerrilla movement. Hortensia is captured and forced to deliver her baby in jail. Pepita tries to find.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Front Line</title>
<link>https://estream.to/embed-5swxn2i5t6mq.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gMwoaKyFrS6WUFhvM3t3IFBoefJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Towards the end of the Korean War an uneasy ceasefire is ordered, but out on the Eastern front line of the Aerok Hills fierce fighting continues. A race to capture.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>From This Day Forward</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JM_KpDmdF98\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jONrDK5DyCi9u10VyTBdSTjnQSE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In flashbacks, the 1938 courtship and marriage of young machinist Bill Cummings and bookstore clerk Susan are recalled: newlywed bliss, unemployment and other tribulations, opportunity with a hidden drawback, war.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Germany Year Zero</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JM_KpDmdF98\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9AVeFqXDUNhR1HDkjiIYcKmunr3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Edmund, a young boy who lives in war-devastated Germany after the Second World War has to do all kinds of work and tricks to help his family in getting food.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fighter Squadron</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/a0Ji8gTAFHo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oIcgWnCbJzd71JKQMgOUxUmY7l5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At an American air base in England, 1943, is conniving Sergeant Dolan, who manipulates everyone, and insubordinate ace fighter pilot Major Ed Hardin. When Ed is promoted to commander of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Arch of Triumph</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Lftqjui2SxU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5tdxQOcppJrYrnkK9sA2zJp1san.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In winter of 1938, Paris is crowded with refugees from the Nazis, who live in the black shadows of night, trying to evade deportation. One such is Dr. Ravic, who.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>I Was a Male War Bride</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MrkN0q7Hs1o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c7WmVQdhJNOyBSe5fK8Gh0uxl7l.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Henri Rochard is a French captain assigned to work with Lt. Catherine Gates. Through a wacky series of misadventures, they fall in love and marry. When the war ends, Rochard.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Task Force</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOPeFi8XEes\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3dQBUwE70s51EQVazb954SieVCh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As he is retiring, Jonathon Scott reminisces about his long Navy career and the development of the role of the aircraft carrier from the early 20s.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Red Badge of Courage</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2-pRE8mgufI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sFb3Ik6IvIlbFVX1bmFN52je2mr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Plot centers around how a young recruit (Audie Murphy) faces the horrors of war. Character vascilates between wanting to fight and doubting his own courage. In midst of first bloody.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Force of Arms</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FYQ-rpbXyjQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kgoozK3YUfeiYIozGaAk8czdF0G.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Winter, 1943. The German army has halted the American advance in the mountains of Italy; back-and-forth combat decimates Joe Peterson's platoon. On leave in Naples, Joe meets WAC lieutenant Eleanor.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thunder in the East</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RzVKee6e9y8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/z7GoFapXwviIzPKuSPQFPjfxpRv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During India's first years of independence from Britain, Steve Gibbs lands his armaments loaded plane in Ghandahar province hoping to get rich. Pacifist Prime Minister Singh hopes to reach .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Springfield Rifle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8q7GxHjafn0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kvgTTCanMjDtEDVdv1rJ3ovxItt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Major Lex Kearney, dishonorably discharged from the army for cowardice in battle, has actually volunteered to go undercover to try to prevent raids against shipments of horses desperately needed for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thunder Over the Plains</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0dUwz9j4oGM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iZhNHGIpKEtKYvGTQMBkFFkdjqH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's 1869, Texas has not yet been readmitted to the Union, and carpetbaggers have taken over the state. Federal Captain Porter, a Texan, has to carry out orders against his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>War Paint</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2lpnZ2qrQYQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nJfGgpHAXcx754hD8Gxp3TNPVAP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lieut. Billings and his army patrol are ordered to deliver a new peace treaty to the Indian Commissioner, who is missing. They have nine days to get the treaty to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bengal Brigade</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yKooYkJ6tqE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9IPqtzBS30tBr2EDnuBuWyTQsWp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set during British India 1857, Captain Clayboune (Rock Hudson) is faced with restoring his reputation after being harshly disciplined for disobeying orders.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Crest of the Wave</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eyTPljDnAdw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r3ZCEmQpf8zCQnwsb9Inl1ax9R6.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Navy lieutenant is borrowed by the British to supervise torpedo experiments after one of their scientists is killed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sea Chase</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/70QyOGKEdr0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iDLkaOyZAy3F2mmVDimcJegIb4W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>As the Second World War breaks out, German freighter captain Karl Ehrlich is about to leave Sydney, Australia with his vessel, the Ergenstrasse. Ehrlich, an anti-Nazi but proud German, hopes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The McConnell Story</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4J4w0G0xpsE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mzNlb8XYyxVW2afJp9olHpUNZFO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mac's plans to settle down and raise a family are upset by the Korean War. He goes as a fighter pilot and returns a hero, the first triple ace of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Strategic Air Command</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WkQr2T83UJc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a7mZ985JqaG97Zi4KX1RijZxxPR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lt. Col. Robert (Dutch) Holland was a third baseman for the St. Louis Cardinals, not a pitcher. While at spring training a B-36 flew over the field and Dutch was.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Burmese Harp</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/x1ChSdFyxnk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6QJ4NPCeUfQEPZ0hLSVeZ6pKISb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Mizushima is a soldier in the Japanese army in Burma in World War II. He's a good soldier and frequently plays his harp to entertain his fellow soldiers. When the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Man Escaped</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/u1L9S3gHj2s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7f8ROxooI3fn85CVqIG5QwPFsdE.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Captured French Resistance fighter Lieutenant Fontaine awaits a certain death sentence for espionage in a stark Nazi prison. Facing malnourishment and paralyzing fear, he must engineer an extraordinary escape, complicated.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Cranes Are Flying</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qXCS9LlBAV0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xFE2hx2kGYcsQHttJobRajuyA6Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Veronica and Boris are walking in the streets of Moscow and they love each other. Veronica is laughing, cause they are happy together this morning. They see some cranes in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Quantrill's Raiders</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2cXz1sOVuMI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8nbha3vmyWgcJNwptZoflGL38Ck.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Confederate Captain Alan Westcott, posing as a horse supplier for the army, is ordered to infiltrate the Union lines and contact William Quantrill to arrange a raid on the arsenal.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Naked and the Dead</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zzN3f3a6U7I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cJHvloPJWLqA1MzIyvrBo0OiQVV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the Pacific during World War 2, the officers live a comfortable life with good food, good drink and good quarters. To them, war is a game which they know.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fires on the Plain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hOlV9YkQDD8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qO7sHluU3okb9Ytir5qgezjWXLI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It is the Philipines, 1945. The Japanese Imperial Army has been reduced to a ragtag mob hiding in the jungles. Among them is Pvt. Tamura. The situation goes from bad.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ballad of a Soldier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Gw6omDDF7Gg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5Yciar2UYDkmXIhA1LnXnkrD2vJ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, 19 year old soldier Alyosha gets a medal as a reward for a heroic act at the front. Instead of this medal he asks for a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Yesterday's Enemy</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CduY6jEoRsY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/erz95IWibdO1Z3U59eOeL5jwnUY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Cut off by the Japanese advance into Burma, Captain Langford (Stanley Baker) and his exhausted British troops take over an enemy-held jungle village. Despite the protests of an elderly padre.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lafayette Escadrille</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OuDKnNtRNNs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AvKlvYWJPw431fMPzNPqApYD7lO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>American youth and flying ace flies for France in World War I; meets &#038; loves a French girl &#038; prostitute.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Soldiers of Pancho Villa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/U3x0svcDkAA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lERX39txVHq5GiBJpVpYd5ITt5v.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Cucaracha is a brave woman soldier who leads a group of similar women into the fray against the forces of the Villa colonel, Zeta.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The River Fuefuki</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/sOPQx3NmApw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nk57AyxWJ0lNNfRf513cdB31vTL.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young man decides to become a warrior, causing trouble for his clan.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hell to Eternity</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mEuPUUB5Vek\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/sKwmqZOAoXckRdkgAw3bLvMMp4z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>True life story of Guy Gabaldon, a Los Angeles Hispanic boy raised in the 1930s by a Japanese-American foster family. Later, during the war, as his foster parents are interned.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Human Condition III: A Soldier's Prayer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZZLPybUl0B0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/svdKfhT9WLfrC8zgOWmZt4mgyK0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Part three of a trilogy. After the Japanese defeat to the Russians in the last episode, Kaji, the Japanese soldier and humanist protagonist, leads the last remaining men through Manchuria.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bridge to the Sun</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ieQFM55Igjs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/K9KzGSrBwZrigRwIOSgupEWSzH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on a true story, this compelling drama relates the difficulties of a young woman married to a Japanese diplomat during World War II, victim of suspicion and animosity from.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>PT 109</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/keZM2Y_-VZs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/t4YlXygBb3YfN5y7Ffcx8lzWIlQ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Dramatization of President John F. Kennedy's wartime experiences during which he captained a PT boat, took it to battle and had it sunk by a Japanese destroyer. He and the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Legend of a Duel to the Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XDwrUSk-VgQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1vFoV4eYkfCAWwFPOPPiyyWtv0n.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young woman who has been evacuated to Hokkaido with her family during wartime receives a marriage proposal from the son of the village head, but declines on account of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hill</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ww4_ZbsDK1M\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/y8hb5jLzSUk3FEdO0LuxMUOa15I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>WWII, in a British disciplinary camp located in the Libyan desert. Prisoners are persecuted by Staff Sergeant Williams, who made them climb again and again, under the heavy sun, an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Triumph Over Violence</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fw1G1jgK4aA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a7iuT5vxlVVe7P4AsniCLPs6AfZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary about the rise and fall of fascism and the effects of Nazism on German society.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ship of Fools</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AaViXh361Fc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/59GZljqMj9ivDIBGy08cAVk0orU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1933: An ocean liner belonging to a second-rate German company is making a twenty-six day voyage from Veracruz, Mexico to Bremerhaven, Germany. Along the way it will stop in Cuba.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ambush Bay</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/siSiEsGQzlA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hJZ5q1fZrSj91k2TtuneSawzjKv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Marine unit on a Japanese-held island in the Philippines tries to hook up with local Filipino guerrillas.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La Grande Vadrouille</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/SEckVvnZw8A\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xjdCbFvLKcqEWRzyY0a9qmntT1L.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A RAF Bomber is shot down over Paris by the Germans. Its crew land there by parachute. With the help of some French civilians they try to escape over the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dark of the Sun</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VUBqmmGGudY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kLrxWUihY5EBD9DbeisBm8Kne1b.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A band of mercenaries led by Captain Curry travel through the Congo across deadly terrain, battling rival armies, to rescue $50 million in uncut diamonds.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Battle on the River Neretva</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cLJeOgkSQ7c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/f5kliqLDzZcd7kFDhVy6eU8IDd3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Battle on Neretva known as the fourth offensive the most humane battle in World War II led by Yugoslav partisans. In January 1943 German army, afraid of Allied invasion of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Colonel Wolodyjowski</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0OZSTter5H4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c0YUZbBlGUrIFzeZVxtYb0V2MkH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1668 the Ottoman Empire decides to attack and invade the Polish-Lithuanian Commonwealth which is one of the few major European powers to still stand in the destructive path of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Submarine X-1</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/WaZ88lMA1mk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/d7yUeoOwsZV91pqW3Qc8Yhyv9VC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After losing a submarine and fifty crew in a battle with a German ship during WWII, a Royal Navy officer gets a second chance in a daring raid with midget.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Army of Shadows</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/GYl2I0vVok4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2YVUZRJjuVERSBLG18YSqxPkVx5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>France, 1942, during the occupation. Philippe Gerbier, a civil engineer, is one of the French Resistance's chiefs. Given away by a traitor, he is interned in a camp. He manages.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Oh! What a Lovely War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UUHh5uAcaBw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/i3g0900iwRgF9o8HZIR1si7ec3W.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A movie about the First World War based on a stage musical of the same name, portraying the Game of War and focusing mainly on the members of the Smith.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Winter Soldier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3262\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bOeXRPH0NjwSrad98fJYNAHhQWo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For three days in 1971, former US soldiers who were in Vietnam testify in Detroit about their war experiences. Nearly 30 speak, describing atrocities personally committed or witnessed, telling of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lacombe, Lucien</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ekSHBWYlJao\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/56QiLCFsWlDXDMwvSRZujN0wbNI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A small town in the south-west of France, summer of 1944. Having failed to join the resistance, the 18 year old Lucien Lacombe, whose father is a prisoner in Germany.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sandakan 8</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8h5yqpAVH24\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/csT18jpVGhRpX8ujTFLOZpa240i.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A journalist interviews an old woman who was forced into prostitution, just like many other Japanese women working in Asia outside of Japan during the first half of the 20th.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Place on Earth</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-nbbjeir63l5t-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yB3LFLh2lRkD5PyBgA3FYlM4tyA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While mapping out the largest cave system in Ukraine, explorer and investigator Chris Nicola discovers evidence that five Jewish families spent nearly a year and a half in the pitch-black.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bless Me, Ultima</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-nhqi4e1lbpur-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kYUcvI4RUzimerSP7cCCPuISVBb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A drama set in New Mexico during WWII, centered on the relationship between a young man and an elderly medicine woman who helps him contend with the battle between good.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Unmanned: America's Drone Wars</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-wa240m3sjjf7-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Unmanned: America's Drone War, the eighth full-length feature documentary from director Robert Greenwald and his Brave New Foundation organization, investigates the impact that U.S. drone strikes have across the globe..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The 18 Bronzemen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ACzfwF3e2aw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yjAc39znY1eDUYdtlSXycc9mlN4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the Manchurian invasion of China, the son of the Ming Dynasty General takes refuge in the Shaolin Temple to learn martial arts, so that he may seek revenge for.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Passage</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2DZBFc7tWI8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kE8dEfO8OjUvirvFCPVlLXEqhLV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During WW 2, a Basque shepherd is approached by the underground, who wants him to lead a scientist and his family across the Pyrenees. While being pursued by a sadistic.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Partizanska eskadrila</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9cNPq_RM2ps\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kP2kDveJ4NDsnaiBeln6LpMfrII.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An epic film of all time. It is one of the greatest spectacle that was filmed in Yugoslavia in the 20th century. In the spring of 1942, the German air.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>From Hell to Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/V4XW-L2Uq50\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/axWUtinzK6rCIYQD6uz0vgUhVq5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On August 24, 1939, at a small French cafe, six friends are about to go their separate ways. They vow to reunite on that day each year at the cafe..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hunter of the Apocalypse</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/k9_Uy8SyteE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cMISbpKB6a4cllhkaxeUwi30Bzw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the Vietnam war, an American soldier gets trapped behind enemy lines. A squad of his buddies sets out to rescue him.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Sea Wolves</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BTUkODzl4DI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4wv3LpQ14SDnKpFIxMZHn1MWqKv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In March 1943, in the World War II, the Germans use the neutral harbor of the Portuguese colony of Mormugoa to transmit information to a U-Boat about the allied ships.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Metro</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0N2BfFD1QTo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/njA3RAhkYdqZQFgVoUMw76nkSbO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paris, 1942. Lucas Steiner is a Jew and was compelled to leave the country. His wife Marion, an actress, directs the theater for him. She tries to keep the theater.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Last Plane Out</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1xmr5jWEl2E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uP1sw46Wr0mAfGfaXXCwGeUWAHt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American journalist covering the civil war in Nicaragua falls in love with a beautiful Sandinista rebel.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>November Moon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OZNEpq1R7aI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4T0OLTcVBCgtR6nBW0e1Cplpfpt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>November Moon is the story of two women in nazi-occupied France. November Messing is jewish, and from Germany. She has come to France to escape the Reich. Férial is french,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Zavtra byla voyna</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pO24xPzdjH4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eYJ94e7ZsVTmqG0A4RzAvJjnzTA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This movie is based on a novel by Boris Vasiliev and describes life in a small Russian provincial town in 1940  one year before Germany invaded the Soviet Union..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hanoi Hilton</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/aSBDyj0Ex4E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zDQVYdmvRQjTR8wCYxJXqbbxTh4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A drama focusing on the suffering, torture, and brutal treatment the American P.O.W.s had to deal with daily while in North Vietnam's Hoa Lo Prison, the most infamous P.O.W. camp.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eastern Condors</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vVBOFOXm1UA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8qmatysRcPAVa5nZeBruH68QVyl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A motley group of Asian prisoners held in the US are given one chance for freedom. They are to go deep into Vietnam and destroy a secret depot of missles.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lenin: The Train</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bGYRa-rTtzw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ztgfofQAnSvrEnyVhgfBhLzmlb5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>March 1917. The first world war is already a couple year to pace. A sealed train with Russian emigrants keeps on driving from Germany and Sweden to Saint-Petersburg. The outlaws.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>In Country</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xmgRF6is2Xg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gVfYLX0mynpIqK4PDZD05Loy9dC.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Samantha Hughes, a teenaged Kentucky girl, never knew her father, who died in Vietnam before her birth. Samantha lives with her uncle Emmett, who also served in Vietnam. Emmett hangs.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nam Angels</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NzJSWMneWGs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jdpDdMTfSjTewskWttkvvs3Nanf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Lt. Vance Calhoun takes on a dangerous rescue mission of American P.O.W.s in the treacherous Darloc Valley in Vietnam. His only chance to escape is with the help of five.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>¡Ay, Carmela!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6L_i0CLP0Co\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mGtRZXjerQfK6IOQjJENK4uhtmR.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Paulino and Carmela are husband and wife, troubadours touring the countryside during the Spanish Civil War. They are Republicans, and with their mute assistant, Gustavete, they journey into rebel territory.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Men Behind the Sun 4</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uAe6T19jcOg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/a2avb0JuqK7BFKZTxitVQMabj7C.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Black Sun: The Nanking Massacre is an uncompromising portrayal of the war crimes perpetrated by the Japanese Imperial Army upon the Chinese military and civilian population of Nanking during the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ulysses' Gaze</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/8VF48LWXCjU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3zP3ZEwt22cGQ4zThNIZ5XLYcgX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A, a Greek filmmaker living in exile in the United States, returns to his native Ptolemas to attend a special screening of one of his extremely controversial films. But A's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Anne Frank Remembered</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/HFMnh-n7U7w\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/x2n4YIVsms3JL8qCfzrbOg2yx0x.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Using previously unreleased archival material in addition to contemporary interviews, this academy award-winning documentary tells the story of the Frank family and presents the first fully-rounded portrait of their brash.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mother Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KYbXUWw61ug\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1U6OkXtr4WuOlQe4FmCbznIExtK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Howard W. Campbell, Jr., an American expatriate playwright, Nazi radio propagandist, and Allied spy, writes his memoirs during his pre-trial confinement in 1961 Haifa and learns that people are what.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>For the Moment</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/rnpIvNykI3I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mtfwuX9dyIKSWcg8hWsrGn8c4jX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The story of airmen training in rural Manitoba in the summer of 1942 to go overseas and become bomber pilots in World War II, as well as the romantic entanglements.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Prisoner of the Mountains</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1NLfEnfKBmw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4S0VyYoGpXQqlWag5pWKOCgAYia.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based upon a short story by Leo Tolstoy, two Russian soldiers, Sacha and Vania, are ambushed by Muslim rebels in the grandly forbidding Caucasus and taken prisoner. Although complete understanding.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Land Girls</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JEMBTo0r5dE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xRfq92wLifGawMvFf6BPCHoL457.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, the organisation The Women's Land Army recruited women to work on British farms while the men were off to war. Three such land girls of different.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last Days</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9UlBo3GFgWY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yAjtrBR42qz6QmSCoPa7TKEId8o.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In late 1944, even as they faced imminent defeat, the Nazis expended enormous resources to kill or deport over 425,000 Jews during the cleansing of Hungary. This Oscar-winning documentary, executive.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Talk of Angels</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/f8HvaXsVq3I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ipDXrPjOLDBlBA4qB6Lo7Gm3jlI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This is the story of a young Irish woman who comes to Spain to escape from the pressures she feels about her impending marriage to a political activist in Ireland..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Marcel Proust's Time Regained</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bGpcZJ8obEI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ylTWJkN5GkwxOCsJPaDmeOv87Ep.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Marcel Proust (1871-1922) is on his deathbed. Looking at photographs brings memories of his childhood, his youth, his lovers, and the way the Great War put an end to a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Goya in Bordeaux</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5WaM5WwsMIc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7qtsv8N5gwD59ubY1nRjNNWjaDn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Francisco Goya (1746-1828), deaf and ill, lives the last years of his life in voluntary exile in Bordeaux, a Liberal protesting the oppressive rule of Ferdinand VII. He's living with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Adventures of Young Indiana Jones: Daredevils of the Desert</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4SqbLZJhtoY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j1l8JzhROQAMzMFGAGHqA3NWWaM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Working with a beautiful lady spy, Indiana Jones is assigned to assist the British forces in their attack on the Turkish-occupied town of Beersheba. With a regiment of the Australian.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Devils on the Doorstep</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/zA2xGrL_Y2s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hBJD9olyXvj2ugw1AHllm3gZQWp.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the Japanese occupation of China, two prisoners are dumped in a peasant's home in a small town. The owner is bullied into keeping the prisoners until the next New.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Into the Arms of Strangers: Stories of the Kindertransport</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/J6asjV9r41s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/r439Z4Yp6HQe0nsVITUfc2H8OPA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>For nine months prior to World War II, in an act of mercy unequalled anywhere else before the war, Britain conducted an extraordinary rescue mission, opening its doors to over.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>No Man's Land</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bii3ru_gvas\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xW8d8kveUwFQaxVPZRw2MTln7JA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After various skirmishes, two wounded soldiers, one Bosnian and one Serb, confront each other in a trench in the no man's land between their lines. They wait for dark, trading.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sword of Honour</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/lpt5SD1gjsg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bmIXD425V316HqPfXhWIExmRnEt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Guy Crouchback,heir to a declining English Roman Catholic family returns to England from Italy at the start of World War Two and joins the Royal Corps of Halberdiers,along with various.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lover's Prayer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/z4nCRE6yZIo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/skC49YE5gCumT4h2TZTWG4N3PoI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A younger boy falls in love with a tragic girl who flirts with, and manipulates, her older suitors in 1800's Russia.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Pavilion of Women</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Wo3f8wsXjaY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bwc50aTNSDjax77mIhFqddWK7vS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1938, Ailian is the forty years old wife of a wealthy man, Mr. Wu, who belongs to the traditional Wu Family in China. In order to get rid off.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Good War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ilh0xXI2JQA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5LFxc5p4JMXGOdBacZjGECbhl4u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on a true story its the untold story of Italian World War II POWS in Jan 1946. Luca Zingaretti stars as one of over 50,000 Italian Prisoners of War.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Wicked Spring</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NHDpKSFe6tY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zzgOMpzk22QnmRvfPvSFPPGPCnU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During the 1864 battle of the Wilderness, three Union soldiers and three Confederate Soldiers get seperated from their units as twilight engulfs the ravaged battlefield. The men wander alone through.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Monsieur Batignole</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nAhNrC-42eo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n2dSoSl0IE6LxaZEmNYVqwl0d4T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1942, in an occupied Paris, the apolitical grocer Edmond Batignole lives with his wife and daughter in a small apartment in the building of his grocery. When his future.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>First Invasion: The War of 1812</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/c7Hh8W69cos\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5o9dlQQ1lP3yX2dUStosbf100Jc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Turtles Can Fly</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MM4WHowIeMA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/maoGbtfSERgqu6J9qvAz4fzse8Z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the Kurdish refugee camp on the Iraqi-Turkish border, the boy Satellite is the leader of the kids. He commands them to clear and collect American undetonated minefields in the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man Who Captured Eichmann</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XEH06oFfJSY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h5A2qbauzn4LP5ND63cjWkNdQ8Z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1960, the Israeli Secret Service learns that former SS-Lietuenant Colonel Adolf Eichmann, who was one of the key figures in the Jewish holocaust of World War II, is living.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sky Hook</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KUrnhVLhDV4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rjh4440x2QOl2bZX5lQKrFEtfda.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film tells the story of some folks in Serbia having to deal with the consequences of the war. Most of them don't have to go to the army (yet),.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Year That Trembled</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hdfejZYJDKI&feature=PlayList&p=31905248CDC1BE13&playnext=1&playnext_from=PL&index=2\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/TemyY0y76bagG0LZw3nN658QiO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Year That Trembled is a 1970 coming-of-age story set in the shadow of Kent State that focuses on a group of young characters facing the Vietnam Draft Lottery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Daughter from Danang</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ueTwnMb8dI&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ckFeaBWzZcxUFRYnO6TCqxkzSM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1975, as the Vietnam War was ending, thousands of orphans and Amerasian children were brought to the United States as part of Operation Babylift. Daughter from Danang tells the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hitler's Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ih5GGKQUd6E\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pT4N0LJc6SQOfQ6NjgqaoQhsxzf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>London, Spring 1941. Columns of Wehrmacht soldiers make their way along the Mall, swastikas hang from Buckingham Palace and Junkers scream low overhead-a potent symbol of Nazi victory. The Germans.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mother of Mine</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3055\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jlcCeC32UReWwkm3a1zLD2EMWfA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, more than 70,000 Finnish children were evacuated to neutral Sweden to avoid the conflict. From the award-winning Klaus Härö (Elina: As If I Wasn't There (2002)),.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Occupation: Dreamland</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PklpivQLB7k\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hvV3JwpSQEtnKXDCxIt2bKHg45n.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In January, 2004, in Al-Falluja, Iraq, a documentary film crew follows an infantry squad of the 82nd Airborne, US Army. Cameras accompany the squad of seven on day and night.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Shot Through the Heart</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BEJdS7_RC4Q\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n7bK9BNcaF7Xai4eXcuYqO2beWS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The horrors of war are examined from the view points of lifelong friends (Linus Roache, Vincent Perez), who end up on opposing sides in the war in Sarajevo. One is.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Rape of Europa</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tK55VI23uXs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8fzUE7GieCSwBvJFZdFQElLJGx7.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>THE RAPE OF EUROPA takes the audience on a journey through seven countries telling a story of greed and warfare that threatened the artistic heritage of Europe. For twelve years,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Under the Bombs</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/J_456UN2HPI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tcGsThrloSJHD4oLhVN4hwRIjtv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Under the bombs, a woman searches for her son. A man accompanies her. They have nothing in common. Toni is Christian and dreams of leaving the country. Zeina is Shiite,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>On My Last Breath</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y0tBSx98knE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Two men trying to find themselves in the midst of WWII Germany. This tale is not about the war that rages around them, but the struggle inside the heart. Lieutenant.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The End of Suburbia: Oil Depletion and the Collapse of the American Dream</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q3uvzcY2Xug\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kGsjGnNcowf8dT5dGxtAZcU7fAy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The modern suburbs have ultimately become an unsustainable way of living. They were originally developed in an era of cheap oil, when the automobile became the center of the way.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Preventive Warriors</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/eb33c5HGoHA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Preventive Warriors examines George W Bush's foreign policy &#8212; specifically in the National Security Strategy of 2002. The NSS states that the US reserves the right to attack any nation.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>A Separate Peace</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wdq7YxGhMhs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iyCY1uEFCaUZQ6Spe8OGY1cZfKc.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Strong friendship between students slowly turns into bitter rivalry with fatal consequences.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Johnny Mad Dog</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4m465VOV1_c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5ra9Ww0FoJpz45hMQ5rpu5TeepX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Johnny Mad Dog, maybe 15, leads a band of boy soldiers in a civil war in an unnamed African country. Don't want to die? Don't be born is one of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Flipping Out</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/nUL6d73mVt4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xgYGfKU7TutJJqAcviTTHTLTZ9M.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Military service in Israel is compulsory for all able-bodied Jewish men and women. Once their years of service is up they are granted a bonus which many use to travel.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Standard Operating Procedure</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/InXqFEK6I00\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/A8uczFmLlaGIRuzK6GyNi92gZEH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Errol Morris examines the incidents of abuse and torture of suspected terrorists at the hands of U.S. forces at the Abu Ghraib prison.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Winter in Wartime</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YrtnYwQXr6Y\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5U48dtSLUTRwg1he8Ggbl67N8wI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Near the end of World War II, 14-year-old Michiel becomes involved with the Resistance after coming to the aid of a wounded British soldier. With the conflict coming to an.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>City of Life and Death</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9td_3P3w1S4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zCzNvesRkmkmlK0g2Abp4y4zhb0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1937, Japan occupied Nanjing, the Chinese capital. There was a battle and subsequent atrocities against the inhabitants, especially those who took refuge in the International Security Zone.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Zeitgeist: Addendum</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/IMRD3z_mTqI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8YT6FHOCj2xT9bnKerL5s6grAwD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Zeitgeist Addendum, attempts to locate the root causes of this pervasive social corruption, while offering a solution. This solution is not based on politics, morality, laws, or any other establishment.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sir! No Sir!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/c4M1IVOzq6g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qm9xRtdpNDYlnT1W1cq7OEEVAZI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This feature-length documentary focuses on the efforts by troops in the U.S. military during the Vietnam War to oppose the war effort by peaceful demonstration and subversion. It speaks mainly.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Great Water</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/U8Fz49Ue6WM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/mqExtyECrMxOezPGUlqrA62IrvM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An ailing communist reflects on his childhood in Stalinist Yugoslavia.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Road to Guantanamo</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MqQ9ZdgkKKo&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2ttqAXqS1kUGMLg7itTQ1jVCU6M.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 2001, four Pakistani Britons, Ruhal Ahmed, Asif Iqbal and Shafiq Rasul and another friend, Monir, travel to Pakistan for a wedding and in a urge of idealism, decide to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Somme: From Defeat to Victory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/S1q-Qp2Klws\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/m3DpA5RY4jjAa17E5TuQ9qg79ad.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on diaries, records and eyewitness accounts, this is the story of the two Battles of the Somme from the perspective of British and German soldiers. It shows how the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An American Girl on the Home Front</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ng6CDobSCDc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c5BHxqwIeffmrTL6MMUpjaKpH1I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on several of the Molly; An American Girl books, this story is set in 1943 in the fictional town of Jefferson, Illinois during World War II. Molly McIntire and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Cu Chi Tunnels</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/19ejFuEyHyk#action=share\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Man Who Will Come</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/YEsFlxacD-U\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/erqqhIZ3MbIPy4rTKl6OBKPI0nb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Winter 1943. Martina is small child, who stopped talking since the death of her infant brother some years before. She lives in a rural area of central Italy. Her mother.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sniper: Inside the Crosshairs</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RjAcF5pYKAQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cXrIf1t3MIcr6Gy5twlDH05xXFM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Sniper-Inside the crosshairs is a documentary based show profiling the worlds best Sniper shots and feats known to man. This documentary takes you behind the scenes to give the viewer.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Road to Moloch</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PlZC0WN4VYQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/y9hOmZm8pbmdEkNMA2ijrrXzBIW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While on a mission to locate three missing soldiers, a team of reconnaissance marines encounter a blood-spattered Iraqi stumbling through the desert. After following the distraught man into the depths.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>By the Will of Chingis Khan</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JeDIVeYYOxY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lWHY1BYP5a4DQpotAYnppTDdijt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Aviatrix of Kazbek</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jMww1UvGdlw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lEYdIRZpGkdFOuUvpnLdPCSxXqw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>On the island Texel, Marie dreams about mountains; she collects postcards of mountains all over the world. She would love to do something else with her life, but as the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>La Rafle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hW2GbaRswGk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iHJtP74X9hie5LZDwmFW7wugX1H.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1942. Joseph is eleven. And this June morning, he must go to school, a yellow star sewn on his chest. He receives the support of a goods dealer. The mockery.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Essential Killing</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_0CR2N4xbfQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/h5FIrLKrzTizUKBflxzpCrWlmbs.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A Taliban member who lives in Afghanistan is taken captive by the Americans after killing an American soldier and two contractors. He is transferred to Europe for interrogation but manages.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Outside the Law</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KiHTBTAfYoo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/n2P3mbuXGIZ1M3PeIGq6rYQuxuk.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>After losing their family home in Algeria, three brothers and their mother are scattered across the globe. Messaoud joins the French army fighting in Indochina; Abdelkader becomes a leader of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Kingdom of Solomon</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pOBwmC5XaGA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oWgAM3MuzUbym4DF7ZqGvSydOCS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Solomon, Prophet and the King, has asked God to give him an ideal kingdom which has never been given to anybody before. He is told to prepare himself and his.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Sarah's Key</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/w182qmadmbk\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lh6kZE8IFCmyufOBlH3a6PxYexe.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>One of the darkest moments in French history occurred in 1942 Paris when French officials rounded up over 10,000 Jews and placed them in local camps. Eventually over 8,000 were.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>First Light</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ir4fby55EzI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/VFClrDd0uloS9Qn969etXtlhrH.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In May 1940 eighteen-year old Geoffrey Wellum joins the 92 squadron of the Royal Air Force and is taken to the pub,where pilots who have seen action sign their names.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Two-Fisted Tales</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3kyYCy9IQUI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/walRAzpkYoAtm90FKIpIzD7Px1a.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Stories of an Old West gunfighter's last stand, a drag racer whose past comes back to haunt him, and a World War I soldier's cowardice are introduced by the foul-mouthed,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Standing Army</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BiPqBXO3xfU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pbKuZ4oLnzJNxtgMt5H7IxUZJ3S.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Today there are more than 766 US bases scattered around the globe, spanning across more than 100 countries and hosting more than 250.000 soldiers, in addition to the one million-plus.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Warring States</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fz_ncdiM8wo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hlkn7S4DVeL81slF0d3VjOawsza.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Rival Chinese military strategists Sun Bin (Sun Hong-lei) and Pang Juan (Francis Ng) clash in this historic war adventure set during the Era of Warring States.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Night Watch</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AUOxVAeb8Ec\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wCMXrVk0sPQD60PmmAtQfrotKxv.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In post-war London, Viv Pearce is dating Reggie and runs a dating bureau with Helen Giniver, who lives with her older lover, authoress Julia Standing. Viv's younger brother Duncan, a.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Border</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fXchSJA2wkI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jQQ0XC0OllDX1Ichqcmk7xhMPXV.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>December 1942. Two young soldiers leave their post at check-point 83 in Northern Värmland, Sweden, and make their way through the ice cold winter-night towards the border of Nazi-occupied Norway..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ballada o bombere</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/fVF8E2hN9Ds\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5vtPIiqSJv2lKemI5ftLzQEYUvA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Bomber (2011) / (Russian language title: Ballada o Bombere) Storyline During World War II, a soviet aircraft crashes on Nazi-occupied territory. But the pilot Grivtsov and his beloved radio.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Mark of Cain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0fENHHxbAOw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/c7s0UnUPeKXAfsdMrXNgtkpxHnX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>GULLIVER and TATE  nickname Treacle'  are two ordinary 18 year-olds serving in the British Army in Iraq. Their platoon is struggling to maintain the uneasy peace of 2003..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Counterfeiters</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-hysxiqn628q0-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bRQddrgVemZtFdnrPy9AxTpkhpj.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The Counterfeiters is the true story of the largest counterfeiting operation in history, set up by the Nazis in 1936. Salomon Sally Sorowitsch is the king of counterfeiters. He lives.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tovarisch, I Am Not Dead</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qQINs8yFPYA&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>Garri Urban, survivor of Holocaust and Gulag and author of the autobiographical book of the same title, revisits the sites of his horrors and triumphs, 50 years later.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nazi America: A Secret History</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hViE_lZ7rzg\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>In a feature length survey of Nazism in the USA, we trace the history from the fairly benign organizations that gave structure to newly arrived German immigrants to today's neo-Nazis.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Battle of Gettysburg</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ikFeQUMxIOI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Heart of Fire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dXC8Ur2YDUA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3XyyTGOOEyuzZ62pnJB66UNeLBI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Eritrea during the independence war against Ethiopia. Awet's mother left her when she was only a little girl and now she is growing up  in the midst of the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Battle Brigade</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/AIHtQ2OMGbU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iEoU2jWsbVS3kSEpCTQXlp9LdKP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>We follow a squad of American paratroopers as they struggle to carry out a mission only one of them knows the real reason for undertaking. As tensions become heightened in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>An Enemy to Die For</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/JUVGU2M32FY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eTcZKGt21Yd6pzSiMXZWYtygh40.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A German expedition is going to the Norwegian arctic islands of Svaldbard in late August 1939 (back then called Spitsbergen), trying to find proof of the theory that all land.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Captain Battle: Legacy War</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6qNHga-82v8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nORiuyaAhsn8im8XBr5yacAM0Tt.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>SAM BATTLE is injured during his tour of duty in the Gulf War. He loses an eye and is near death. His good friend, BRANDON STORM, who is a scientist,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Land of Mine</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4Kao3t0NBMU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7TOYH2VDnYbXpBKlrkdQZUSC3Du.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>SPOILER: In 1945, in Denmark, after the defeat of Germany, the tough veteran Sergeant Carl Rasmussen is assigned by Lieutenant Ebbe Jensen to defuse and remove 2.2 million mines in.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vuP6KbIsNK4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tviJ68Wj4glQk3CPMvdvExYHxX.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Insane General Jack D. Ripper initiates a nuclear strike on the Soviet Union. As soon as the actions of General Buck Turgidson are discovered, a war room full of politicians,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Massacre in Rome</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0mxQvqgi4Ho\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bFFdsi4gauEmo2COV2UrJqD6tWM.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In the Nazi occupied city of Rome, an assault on an SS brigade draws retaliation from the military governship. Massacre in Rome is the true story of how this partisan.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Seven Beauties</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ig-Ty0ltY6k&t=1027s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/Ad8acJ3Awb8I0uAA06YjKZSNdIq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The defense of honor, a strong value in Neapolitan society, and his effects on the life of everyman Pasquale Frafuso.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Ascent</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UEVZOj7uYps&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eZ2RqIznbQpogQtyKFsSQxoP2VK.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In a freezing cold World War II winter, two pro-Soviet partisans  Sotnikov and Rybak  head off to find food for themselves and their compatriots. They find a goat.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Hitler's Last Train</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/6o9pMEW6BZ4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/xGFLaPZOGuOvTHWq8OsCeyJyFs5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The SS puts a slutty nightclub singer in charge of a train car full of prostitutes whose services are reserved solely for senior Nazis.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Tears in the Rain</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/N-4Pifg07yQ\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kvQX64XdNMstIyWSpwwroyBhZf.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>When Casey Cantrell's mother died, her last wish was that her daughter would give a letter to Lord Richard Bredon, living in the UK. When Casey arrives in London, Lord.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Last American Soldier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/z3P_E_6Uyko\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/e27YxvC8Oo6t40bZlsMk5YDsHEy.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Commander and his small band of freedom fighters make life difficult for the VC after the Vietnam War is over. They free Vietnamese prisoners, and destroy enemy convoys every chance.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Too Young the Hero</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/mVSMncKEFF4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/icMifhFfCtOF5Q0UP6IwnBSd17Q.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The true story of Calvin Graham who at the age of twelve, but looking quite a lot older, succeeded in joining the navy during World War II. In spite of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Iron Triangle</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/a5ug-byBe_o\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6PpHcYuDBTMUCRWWb1JVqPRURPq.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Based on the diary of an unknown Viet Cong soldier, this film provides a sympathetic look at a Viet Cong soldier who protected a captured American soldier whom he believed.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Age of Stupid</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Gs9nVKbC-F4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pbY7CxwXQ6MnVqilWb6paDJqJQ5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This ambitious documentary/drama/animation hybrid stars Pete Postlethwaite as an archivist in the devastated world of the future, asking the question: Why didn't we stop climate change when we still had.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Red and the White</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/user/BerlinDesire75#g/c/C9C0FA0E63178080\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uQ8ibpzogPsroMu9tg0UX0FqQPG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1919, Hungarian Communists aid the Bolsheviks' defeat of Czarists, the Whites. Near the Volga, a monastery and a field hospital are held by one side then the other. Captives.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Human Bullet</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MDIKVcpF-T0&cc=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/AmHeWLV364jsHgp0lxObVJYMoXW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, a Japanese soldier finds himself assigned to a kamikaze mission against a U.S. battleship.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Testa di sbarco per otto implacabili</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tJD5xigC0Kw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wMrfIf0Pa2YHEQ03Xs66PfDgWzb.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The movie is set during World War II in the days just prior to the D-Day invasion. A special parachute unit is sent to destroy a German flame thrower installation.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Carriage to Vienna</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/user/oneleggedwomanqueen#g/c/397F12D1BA6C4AFF\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/3jY2t3D4JdL7phBJi1iAa0VuXI9.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A WW2 story of a young Austrian soldier running from the Russian army and a woman whom he forces to come along in order to save his wounded mate.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Desert Commandos</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dFLB9j5LGVo\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ctAElvpr553KXA7AiOPRw651iqx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>German commandos are dropped behind enemy lines in the Sahara Desert tasked with getting to Casablanca in an assassination attempt on allied leaders.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Damned</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XtMocFKzwxY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/yGXjlobGO1YFhRfNEgjMX2nhJsP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The power and fortune of the Von Essenbeck family remained intact even when Germany lost the great war and during the depression that followed. Now it's 1934 and the baron.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Republikata vo plamen</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qpUw1Z7XEqM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9h5VmTcGDM99BH3ec5gbCIW9HVD.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Records one of the most important events in the history of the Macedonian people: about the Ilenden Uprising and the Krusevo Republic of 1903.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Alfred the Great</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-sasyw4a53xul-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cmx1RSD2E5YUM6gaByzkmShHT2g.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While Old England is being ransacked by roving Danes in the 9th century, Alfred is planning to join the priesthood. But observing the rape of his land, he puts away.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Army Medicine in Vietnam</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/W5I8EBW_eM4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Rainy Day Woman</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_T0XffIaEVg&feature=results_video&playnext=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>A fascinating dissection of a remote rural community's descent into barbarity as a result of WWII invasion fears.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Universal Soldier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9iqMgiqjTkA\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/emDEbf1EnZpFD1HeBvdYjiC3FMZ.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A lifelong mercenary commander and weapons expert played by George Lazenby is commissioned to train an army for an exiled African leader. But as his conscience finally catches up to.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Third Part of the Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/user/TheSanatorium#g/c/4563D88ACE9091C0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oiDXPUdoKTeevI1ITT251qMOR8B.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set during the occupation of Poland during World War II. Some German soldiers, slaughter a woman, her son and daughter-in-law. The husband and his father escape by being in the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>5 Branded Women</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/CjKE06xayjA&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/7di2wiawLB9N773bgl3gCIwTQBo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Five Yugoslav women who consorted with the German occupiers are publicly humiliated and banished by the Yugoslav partisans but they take up arms to fend for themselves.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Conspiracy of Hearts</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_xjSgBA8xag&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/i7gieDmvNgoa2UfcENiJBvxgeSl.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In wartime Italy nuns in a convent regularly smuggle Jewish children out of a nearby internment camp. The Italian army officer in charge suspects what may be going on but.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Clear Skies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/xWBsKDLzq20\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kYfB7XsKlkmehrz35PSTdrduAy5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At the outset of the War, Alexei,an airman, marries Sasha Lvova, a young factory worker. One day, Alexei does not return from his mission and he is thought to be.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Best of Enemies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/e6XhT3VZfJI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rjlasXW6L9dewfDchprvm4vImkU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1941 the Italian and British forces face one another.Italian army Captain Blasi and his troops capture a British army Major Richardson and his pilot when their scout plane crashes..</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Every Time We Say Goodbye</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-ma1lk48oq3o2-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hDiKsSc3s5zyxjIa7eaQ2RWySOP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American flyer who joined the RAF before his country was in the war is recovering from a leg injury in Jerusalem. Through an English friend he meets a quiet.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Horizontal Lieutenant</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-8t24xg87yxrh-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tsgYOukPmLqKJuDwyOdpZSsMgrW.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1944. Hapless Second Lieutenant Merle Wye of the US army's intelligence service is dismayed that he has not seen any action  he imagining himself as a suave undercover agent,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Black Fox: The True Story of Adolf Hitler</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0PVLW53e4Cw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gjs10aZCBOfl8XjlY43fTBxUw0T.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Louis Clyde Stoumen's Oscar-winning documentary feature combines World War II newsreel footage with an adaptation of the European folk tale Reynard the Fox, illustrated by old-fashioned woodcuts. The narration by.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Pigeon That Took Rome</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cJHFiEFcXzc\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/gzKVsqP7wZ6RuqUbVm3PwDCVFHG.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1944, two American spies, posing as priests, infiltrate German occupied Rome to relay information to HQ but can only communicate via pigeons due to the imposed radio silence.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Ski Troop Attack</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wQyOZllVEsE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/cpx9YApC2ca7xjE6K1LgPCp8cJr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>An American patrol has to cross behind enemy lines by skis in order to blow up an important railroad bridge. The task is made harder by conflicts between the platoon's.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Gusarskaya ballada</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/hqjgS0hdrEc&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2oGgPrrBtIGxXxplh1Hr8BYjiPa.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A young girl decides to join a Husar squadron and fight against Napoleon. Dressed as a man she has a hard time adjusting to the rude Husar life styles.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Field of Honor</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/FcCjb6Ultw0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/bpCKPSAwCxzWTe5Z9CRWR6aaOS3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Korea: 1951. The Dutch mercenary sergeant De Koning has problems controlling his troops. They commit all kind of atrocities against the Korean population. After an attack by Chinese forces, De.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Optimisticheskaya tragediya</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/i82jKH2Dlps\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/eW5sNxoFwrmxr7IT39OxSTJibab.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Peach Thief</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/dPBalNuBxfE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/8QnhJEoyWsXWDf9QN4vc7o92M5u.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>World War I is coming to its end. Prisoners of war are coming into the town with Serb Ivo among them. During one of his escapes from the camp, he.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Iron Angel</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-8j18pn90npyd-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/9RGzBFGsBqj3LuAkPmGPMzBNgGO.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A green lieutenant volunteers five men to carry out a mission to take out a North Korean mortar position that's preventing supply convoys from reaching the front line. Afterwards they.</summary>
</item>
<title>Back Door to Hell</title>
<link>https://www.thevideo.me/embed-u9ojw6pbtvme-640x360.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zAeF17bleL82eTbmXolsyTNVZc0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In December, 1944, three US soldiers sneak ashore on Luzon to gather intelligence about Japanese troops in advance of the American armada. The three are to reconnoiter and report via.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Let There Be Light</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/kDNoaSMKx0g\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/wgcAMb5BLKFANzTDfKwnxeH1kYA.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The final entry in a trilogy of films produced for the U.S. government by John Huston. This documentary film follows 75 U.S. soldiers who have sustained debilitating emotional trauma and.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Decision Before Dawn</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/-pEfCo5uZLM&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dyWZAqoRK7aznoyM4N1s7ArcZ83.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>WWII is entering its last phase: Germany is in ruins, but does not yield. The US army lacks crucial knowledge about the German units operating on the opposite side of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Island Rescue</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/RzSWOzzjaTE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/qurehSmDdQNslDjjM0c8ly43x10.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>At the outbreak of WWII the British realise they can't prevent the invasion of the Channel Islands. However, someone realises that a prize cow is on the islands and the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Big Lift</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pSNwLFjvSYE\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lQ7MOU0ZXXCMlVLeut1zd7bIOts.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1948, the Soviet Union blockades the Allied sectors of Berlin to bring the entire city under their control. A semi-documentary about the resulting Berlin Airlift gives way to stories.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fall of Berlin</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/t-hZam8dXHU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lkjJgkWByrNYrRM9vGg93NcuSfn.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Surrounded by a few party officials, Alexei Ivanov, a stakhanovist smelter, is decorated by Stalin. The Little Father of the Peoples takes this opportunity to invoke threats of war.. One.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Red Ball Express</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q9T2m1k-8fI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/zEI4DQ6xQgm9Mr1xIk348CnH1qS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>August 1944: proceeding with the invasion of France, Patton's Third Army has advanced so far toward Paris that it cannot be supplied. To keep up the momentum, Allied HQ establishes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Miles of Fire</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0Kiml-N0ExU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pMmTEVRRHkr7EDWUdg2O7tEIR63.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Square Peg</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qPNZUpmrM5s\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/uxMpSBKt7UtKKuJspnYXkmcbPm4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Norman and Mr Grimsdale are council workmen mending the road outside an Army base when they come into conflict with the military. Shortly afterwards, they get drafted and fall into.</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Bridge</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1JHG2SD-9fI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/frZsN12LNj62nnW11D3I06eC5O4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of German boys is ordered to protect a small bridge in their home village during the waning months of the second world war. Truckloads of defeated, cynical Wehrmacht.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Meet the Navy</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/d2pFecD3Ug8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>During World War II, the Canadian Navy gathered a troupe of diverse performers (dancers, comedians, singers, musicians) from its ranks and sent them off to entertain their shipmates, and .</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Battle of the Rails</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yiWpolKBWXs\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2ZizudRcVYisSgqgiCS1WiUNsDS.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>This movie is a story about French railroad workers who were part of organized resistance during the German WW2 occupation.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Le Silence de la Mer</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/user/TheAuteurs71#g/c/ADA131AF4E788071\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/tKK6FvXub48BlbfZCSR8fCbplAT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>1941 in a small town in Nazi occupied France. Against the will of its elderly male and his adult niece residents, the Nazis commandeer a house for one of their.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Enemy of Women</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/wc_rqDj3XbQ&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/o9bL3sXU9Y94lnMWLM7VjbLMhGN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Young Dr. Paul Joseph Goebbels, an unsuccessful playwright, is forced, in order to support himself, to take a position as tutor in the household of Herr Quandt. His first attempt.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Navy Way</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/movie/the_navy_way\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/iEcmEUnhde3xfGPWii7j1xuZm0z.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The experiences of a disparate group of young men as they make their way through Navy boot camp.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Resisting Enemy Interrogation</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/LVrYb5NKpIM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/rOCuTiZ3L3Y01eWINP2C01WSszz.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A downed American bomber crew quickly falls prey to the clever interrogation techniques of the Germans in this dramatic training film.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fighting Lady</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/B5JbXRDOP60&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/4ZXkaIGv84P9lHErBiXuyXCfNtP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The film follows the WWII exploits of the Essex-class aircraft carrier USS Yorktown (CV-10) (unidentified in the film), in its first major operations following its commissioning in 1943. The life.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>London Can Take It!</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cS7R5fIUBjU\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/5834LfVFwkWK6kR6HnhdGWVfYGB.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A tribute to the courage and resiliency of Britons during the darkest days of the London Blitz.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>They Raid by Night</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/LRFu9XPVYF4\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ySxx74aKNuYyY6fzz3dZqWglLT0.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The British Commandos send Bob Owen (Lyle Talbot) to Norway to prepare for a raid. His mission also includes freeing General Heden (Paul Baratoff) who is being held by the.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eleventh Hour</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/_aVIO-u_1GY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/pyjFE4FZFfUSYupQpEXXP7Xk80E.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>While Clark Kent is in wartime Japan, Superman becomes a saboteur.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Lady from Chungking</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0xJ97UICjp8\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/2pwvmnzUkyZ0b9L3Ah6YX6SBVyh.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In Japanese-occupied China, Madame Kwan Mei is the leader of a resistance organization based in a rural village. When two American airmen are shot down near the village, she makes.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>All Together</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/KiRfFGIBb9c\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/kLboK8Z5ctQj268rdu0T1qCX0Y4.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The entire Disney menagerie appears in a parade urging the purchase of war bonds.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Secret Mission</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tinu7-L1zcs&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/6rzzKM3I1yCjIAZRQ9Hd4YEGwXN.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In this World War II suspense thriller, three British spies and a French resistance fighter sneak into occupied France to gather information about the German forces for a planned invasion.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Went the Day Well?</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-wuoeqkbz5sgf-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/1sdZVDF543EqPCxWiG6atBop9XU.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The residents of a British village during WWII welcome a platoon of soldiers who are to be billeted with them. The trusting residents then discover that the soldiers are Germans.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The More the Merrier</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ebqivnHyunA&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/dn0Wr0k2vAaYBQ1Zn7mlOF1gUC5.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>It's World War II and there is a severe housing shortage everywhere  especially in Washington, D.C. where Connie Milligan rents an apartment. Believing it to be her patriotic duty,.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Immortal Sergeant</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uuCSu6Y07_0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/501cjR1IYrdw8RyBk9yGhlm78a3.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Out on patrol in the war-time desert a Canadian corporal reminisces about the woman he has left behind in London and ponders whether she will fall for the charms of.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Get Cracking</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-z0vamepggo1j-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/jT8Rt2cd3oCSd8dPU7Yl4n68DSr.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>George Formby joins the home guard.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Corvette K-225</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/1MBzb5q8khY\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ne7koreyzjX6s64AdkAeVQfpXWY.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In 1943, Mac' MacClain, Canadian Navy, has lost his ship and many men to a German torpedo. While waiting for a new ship, he befriends Joyce Cartwright, sister of one.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Hour Before the Dawn</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/h7mLHJjEDg0\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/lIa4VzhvGkV0Hr2d0vgTraaJTWP.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A beautiful Austrian refugee in Englandwho is also a Nazi agentmarries a scholarly English pacifist. He lives near a secret military base she needs to get information about so she.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The True Glory</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9ifDqlRZh70\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/84m8ywR36LtIczjAxDbApeeqS8X.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A documentary account of the allied invasion of Europe during World War II compiled from the footage shot by nearly 1400 cameramen. It opens as the assembled allied forces plan.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>To the Shores of Iwo Jima</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2CMeGod3SJs&feature=watch-now-button&wide=1\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/vUAXZSnoFrG8acoN8AXN8Atvp1I.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary short film depicting the American assault on the Japanese-held island of Iwo Jima and the massive battle that raged on that key island in the Allied advance on Japan.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fight for the Sky</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/EG9zru3kFAM\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/oy4mLPcEOkxoirWtzNDUsF0rtmI.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Documentary short film produced by the American Army Air Forces extolling the exploits of the American fighter pilots who destroyed the German Luftwaffe and allowed the Allies to proceed with.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Fleet That Came to Stay</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bq06GgBI4qw\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185 </thumbnail>
<summary>N/A</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Independence of Romania</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UA9J6funJis\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/nyWHNZJa8DtNMsxEvAmkoKtpjgx.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>The movie depicts the Romanian War of Independence (1877-1878).</summary>
</item>

<item>
<title>Beau Ideal</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/UB5n7fafW4w\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/ixDUanyUQbqG4yZb3WIb2GITrIo.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>In England, Otis Madison learns from the girl that he loves, Isobel Brandon, that the man she loves is his best friend, John Geste, and so there is nothing that.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>War Babies</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/orq4LqX7WEE&feature=related\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/fvX10fF4tNimoHuBDtBnGO4Rl3w.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A group of soldiers in a café watch a dancer as she entertains them, but later two of them become rivals over her.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Lost Patrol</title>
<link>http://gorillavid.in/embed-cde6c50d1mf3-960x480.html\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/hgRUKYhjMpzJae9Ni6LYoZQ6u0n.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>A World War I British Army patrol is crossing the Mesopotomian desert when their commanding officer, the only one who knows their destination is killed by the bullet of unseen.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Becky Sharp</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/C6Jt2JqJ_HI\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/25ktT5mecPAeZvwsnAcpSlQY9aw.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>Set against the background of the Battle of Waterloo, Becky Sharp is the story of Vanity Fair by Thackeray. Becky and Amelia are girls at school together, but Becky is.</summary>
</item>


<item>
<title>Nurse Edith Cavell</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/embed/try7eIZLN8I\</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w185/j5GI8zG5K1vWjfeyKMfebb6OSsT.jpg </thumbnail>
<summary>English nurse Edith Cavell is matron in a small private hospital in German-occupied Brussels during WWI. When the son of a recently deceased patient escapes from a German prisoner-of-war camp,.</summary>
</item>


