<item>
  <title>Twisted</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt14201728</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://media.cm/7slp2rpcwx8a</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/rF6txsM6cgF9vg6Ra5sNbkvUwrw.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Two millennials make quick money by leasing incredible New York City apartments they don’t own to people who don’t know they are being scammed. The con works brilliantly until they run into an apartment owner with a dark secret who flips the game on them.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>The Wrecking Crew</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt33046197</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/aiskr8cklqfk</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/gbVwHl4YPSq6BcC92TQpe7qUTh6.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Estranged half-brothers Jonny and James reunite after their father's mysterious death. As they search for the truth, buried secrets reveal a conspiracy threatening to tear their family apart.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>The Rip</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt32642706</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/dd1ife65u4z3</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/eZo31Dhl5BQ6GfbMNf3oU0tUvPZ.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>Trust frays when a team of Miami cops discovers millions in cash inside a run-down stash house, calling everyone — and everything — into question.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Return to Silent Hill</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt22868010</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/i7lakuk1ysix</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/fqAGFN2K2kDL0EHxvJaXzaMUkkt.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>When James receives a mysterious letter from his lost love Mary, he is drawn to Silent Hill—a once-familiar town now consumed by darkness. As he searches for her, James faces monstrous creatures and unravels a terrifying truth that will push him to the edge of his sanity.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Shelter</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt32357218</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/aiskr8cklqfk</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/klvZs66SG19qmacdwxSRkdFQhQS.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A man living in self-imposed exile on a remote island rescues a young girl from a violent storm, setting off a chain of events that forces him out of seclusion to protect her from enemies tied to his past.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>The Millwood Murders: Buried Truth</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt39379819</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://k00.fr/5q8qryhp</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/jy789vYmOl0VQP7LutMs4szKMsm.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>A prosecutor condemns her husband as the Millwood Murderer. Years later, as his execution nears, their daughter disappears after finding evidence of his innocence - and the real killer still free.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>The Investigation of Lucy Letby</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt39389929</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/a6zy2otdv12t</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/qhNThwc72GqihJhXaP29Af5hJ2A.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>An engaging and thought-provoking look at Lucy Letby, the former nurse serving life in prison after being convicted of the murders of seven infants and the attempted murders of seven others.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>

<item>
  <title>We Bury the Dead</title>
  <meta>
  <imdb>tt29713093</imdb>
  <year>2026</year>
  </meta>
  <link>https://luluvid.com/707n1cecr1et</link>
  <thumbnail>https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/xZqo0yPARmyF8TACVNyaOACkYWG.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary>After a catastrophic military disaster, the dead don't just rise—they hunt. The military insists they are harmless and slow-moving, offering hope to grieving families. But when Ava enters a quarantine zone searching for her missing husband, she uncovers the horrifying truth: the undead are growing more violent, more relentless, and more dangerous with every passing hour.</summary>
  <fanart></fanart>
</item>











